<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 21:16:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CoinDesk: BMW, Intel Partner With Government-Backed Blockchain Accelerator -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bmw-intel-join-singapore-government-backed-blockchain-accelerator</link><description>BMW Group Asia, Intel and Nielsen are now corporate partners of the Singapore government-supported blockchain accelerator Tribe.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 12:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Changes to Tether’s Terms of Reserves Raises Fresh Concerns -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/changes-to-tethers-terms-of-reserves-raises-fresh-concerns</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jNDViMjU2MzRjODAzYzYzZjRmZmQwNWU2N2ZjMDIxYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrency community members are speculating that Tether is not being openly transparent about its reserves after changes to its website.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Binance Changes Launchpad Token Sale Format to Lottery -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-changes-launchpad-token-sale-format-to-lottery</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81MDAxZDQ4Mjg4ZThmNzhmYmVmMWI0YzJmODkzNGUyNy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Binance Launchpad format has been radically changed by the cryptocurrency exchange&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Crypto Futures and Institutional Interest: Looking in the Wrong Place -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/crypto-futures-and-institutional-interest-looking-in-the-wrong-place</link><description>Cboe's suspension of bitcoin futures highlights a mistake we're all making when it comes to institutional involvement, argues Noelle Acheson.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 11:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: US Institutional Crypto Exchange Seed CX Expands to Asia With New Partnership -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-institutional-crypto-exchange-seed-cx-expands-to-asia-with-new-partnership</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9mNTljMTViOTA5NGE2ZmZiZDgyMzZlOTllMDQyYjFmMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Singapore-based fintech company Hydra X has partnered with United States-based institutional crypto exchange Seed CX to bring its offerings to Asia&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Tor Digital Privacy Project Accepts Donations in Cryptocurrency -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tor-digital-privacy-project-accepts-donations-in-cryptocurrency</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jNGM0NzU0ZTRjNDgwNzJhMjg5ODY1YWY3YzhiZThlZi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The digital privacy project Tor is now accepting various cryptocurrencies on its donations portal&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: The Game Changing Factors — Sentiment Analysis For Cryptocurrencies -  Puntaje: 5700</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/the-game-changing-factors-sentiment-analysis-for-cryptocurrencies-e18d79899a20?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h3&gt;The Game Changing Factors — Sentiment Analysis For Cryptocurrencies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sentiment is a huge driving factor in the cryptocurrency market. But it is a metric which is very hard to measure. Sentiment analysis has been on the rise for the past few years. With the introduction of new packages, sentiment analysis can be done more quickly and efficiently than ever. In this post, you’ll see why looking at the mood on the social media is not a great idea for sentiment analysis. Also, you will learn how people’s interests in topics change over the course of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/678/1*9kX-mI7CrQxsR_rwntRe6w.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sentiment Analysis Using Social Media&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Predicting market sentiment using social media is tricky. From the analysis, it was found that when there’s an increase in crypto prices, people share positive messages across their social media handles. And when the prices go down, people go all negative and share negative posts on social media platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VADER is a great tool for &lt;a href="https://medium.com/analytics-vidhya/simplifying-social-media-sentiment-analysis-using-vader-in-python-f9e6ec6fc52f"&gt;simplifying sentiment analysis&lt;/a&gt;. Using it with NLTK Python package, we did mood analysis on Reddit. The script that used was in the form of a Jupyter Notebook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What the script will do is it pulls data from Reddit’s API. It then assigns a compound score to each post. Now, this score predicts the mood in the post. The score lies between -1 (very negative) and 1 (very positive). Given below is the distribution of Sentiment score:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/559/0*bXG2FLr9woPOsc4e" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The continuous spectrum was classified as follows: positive posts, negative posts, and neutral posts. To make this possible, it was important to decide the scores corresponding to each label. Also, it was necessary to come up with an appropriate classification boundary. Therefore, a classifier was trained using &lt;a href="https://www.statisticssolutions.com/what-is-logistic-regression/"&gt;logistic regression&lt;/a&gt; on a subset of data. Posts were labelled manually. After labelling a few hundred of them, a few things were concluded:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most of these posts were neutral or the posts by confused crypto-beginners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sentiments and its underlying meaning are different and it’s tough to separate them when you’re labelling the two as a human.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results are shown below. It’s clear that the results by computer labels and manual labels are not the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/363/0*SyhJYFgw9cOktHqp" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was difficult to separate the context and sentiment at time of labelling the headlines. The problem is people bet on either side of cryptocurrencies. A happy event for you can be a sad event for someone else. Consider two statements below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Bitcoin market crash leaves behind a graveyard of startups”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Bitcoin crash is a good news for investors”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now both these statements are about the same topic but the sentiment is opposite. Therefore, it is hard to analyze the sentiment using mood when predicting cryptocurrency price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what’s the other way to estimate cryptocurrency price? The number of crypto-related posts increase in times of intense interest in virtual currencies. Does the increase in volume lead to increase in price? Are both linked in any way?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get a better idea, it would be nice to check out the volume of posts on certain topics. Posts on different topics will have a different impact on crypto price. Posts about vulnerabilities in crypto would have a negative impact on price. On the other hands, posts like bitcoin’s high security would have an increase in price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Posts that we see on social media platforms like &lt;a href="http://reddit.com"&gt;reddit&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://mamby.com"&gt;mamby&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/login"&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt; etc. are very short and they do not provide a good set for sentiment analysis. There’s a &lt;a href="https://min-api.cryptocompare.com/"&gt;News API&lt;/a&gt; that combines articles from all the main news outlets about crypto. These articles have body text and the headlines as well which can be used for better analysis. It also saves the hassle of doing a lot of content scraping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, the question is how to classify these articles into different topics? Well, this can be with the help of &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@lettier/how-does-lda-work-ill-explain-using-emoji-108abf40fa7d"&gt;Latent Dirichlet Allocation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The basic concept behind LDA is learning topics from different words found in the text, and then figuring out which topic the document is about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are the stages of LDA:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create a distribution for every topic which tells your understand of word it contains. Also, create a distribution for every document that defines your understanding of topics it contain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Allocate topics to each document by drawing each of them randomly from initial distribution. Do the same for the words as well.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do an optimization and arrange most natural grouping of words to those topics and topics to documents.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;LDA is not supervised. One cannot know which particular words a topic will contain or which topics a document will have. To make it easier, it’s better to specify “uniform distribution” as a prior. Also, it’s hard to predict the number of topics in a document. So, the number was just a guesstimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The LDA system was implemented on approximately 48,000 news articles with 27 topics. Below are some of the topics which were discovered:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/626/0*JhL8q3Li06cICPfl" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be concluded that topic 4 is about ICOs. However, it’s not possible to predict all the topics using this. The goal was to predict the price using these topics. But the topics could not be explained easily. Thus, it was bit hard to make price prediction using LDA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of news about crypto that breaks everyday. And there are some main topics. To make a correct estimation about the price, it is better to decide on some topics rather than choosing a random number of these topics. When there are some common topics, it would be easier to tell the algorithm what words should fall in which category. So, there is no need to use a uniform prior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/677/0*yZFVPyGkypkr0tFu" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/614/0*CB6AOfB8HE1l7Zon" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Example topics from pre-defined topic LDA&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can specify some words which are likely to appear in particular topics. For example, we can specify that bitcoin is likely to contain words like BTC, Satoshi etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s some initial visualisations using these topics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/877/0*vdRTC518hij-a5Ny" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Topic allocations over time as a percentage of all articles published.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/867/0*9RVWiLoB8lhuYnQa" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Bitcoin vs Ethereum news articles over the last year&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/902/0*O0XLMIHX1y2CKr5J" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is perhaps some correlation with price. After doing some mood analysis on social media, and some unsupervised topic classification. Using LDA, it was possible to make a fair prediction about the prices. It was concluded from the study that mood analysis through social media is not as effective as LDA method.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=e18d79899a20" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/the-game-changing-factors-sentiment-analysis-for-cryptocurrencies-e18d79899a20"&gt;The Game Changing Factors — Sentiment Analysis For Cryptocurrencies&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 10:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: What is IEO Initial Exchange Offering? Is this the new phenomenon in Crypto Capital? -  Puntaje: 9700</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/what-is-ieo-initial-exchange-offering-is-this-the-new-phenomenon-in-crypto-capital-64fdd60a6e7a?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*N3y521EDK7rdVwOaCFdtCg.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Initial Exchange Offering&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;2017 &amp;amp; 2018 being the year of ICO, has come up with huge benefits in the crypto industry. But the truth is people have started pacing towards a new strategy named as Initial Exchange Offering. Crypto Enthusiasts across the globe suggest this neoteric alternative for ICO since it is feature-packed with boosted-benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ICO model allows the project to bootstrap themselves without the need of going through traditional venture capital without funding. While on the other hand, IEO&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;enable crypto projects to fundraise directly on digital exchanges!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most hyped news of recent times is one of the AI projects has raised around $5.5 million in just 22 seconds on Binance with IEO!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next five minutes will make you clear of all your queries regarding this platform!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is IEO Initial Exchange Offering?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Initial Exchange Offering&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;is a token sale hold on an exchange. IEO&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;works on different cryptocurrency exchanges depending on how it gets planned. The exchanges create a platform where the pool of developers can mint and sell the projects to crypto enthusiasts and investors!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the token sale gets conducted on the IEO exchange platform, both the exchange team and the project team will deal with an agreement. The exchange platform will do a thorough review of the project using certain conditions to make sure the project is worthy authentic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the exchange platform is comfortable with the project, it will unveil the date for token sale along with the fixed price per token. If in case the exchange has its own token, then the contributors have to purchase the units of tokens before they can participate in Initial Exchange Offering&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IEO Vs ICO! What would be the&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;difference between IEO and ICO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are planning launch IEO as your platform you will definitely have this question circulating in your mind!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the primary difference between both!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The major difference between them is IEO’s are immediately tradable when compared to ICO. If you ask an ICO Crypto Trader they would convey this as to be the worst part in Initial Coin Offering.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Yet another difference is that ICO’s can attract the investments while the IEO can make the stock markets actively participate in the fund-raising process which makes it the most promising field.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Initial Exchange Offering introduces an intermediary to the decentralized fundraising model, which gives the crypto traders a strong sense of confidence while participating. While ICO has turned out to be the area of scams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Another difference is that ICO’s mint their tokens once the funding gets completed. In the case of IEO’s, projects generate tokens and send them to the exchange platform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So, How to launch IEO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can invest in IEO’s by just having an account on a participation exchange. However, you need to pass their Know Your Customers&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;screening and should not be from the restricted country. Once you complete all these, you can initiate investing in IEO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, IEO’s are more user-friendly than ICO’s. All you do to partake in IEO’s is just to create an account on the exchange which supports the token sales, funds your wallet and purchases the token when it goes live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Initial Exchange Offering is preferred?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huge advantages for Crypto Investors has been the major reason why IEO’s are preferred and an alternative for ICO. Apart from being able to trust the crypto exchange to be as safe intermediary is the simultaneous listing of coins since the exchange acts a kind of partner organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you aren’t sure of which people to invest, anyone can invest rather than it is restricted in the country. As discussed, once you complete all the formalities which are stated above, you will be given access to the sale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, countries such as the United States, China, Venezuela, New Zealand, North Korea, and many other countries are barred from participating. One more thing is, the rules and regulations may change from one exchange to another but the basic steps for the users will remain the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantages/ Benefits of IEO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By hiring the right IEO developers&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;you can avail the appreciable benefits from their end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right off the bat, IEO&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;will allow the developers to take the complete advantage of the existing user base of a crypto exchange. By making use of the power of exchanges, IEO’s make it easier for more number of people to participate in the crowdfunding process.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This new strategy can eliminate scams in the fundraising process which has been the major issue in ICO process. By making contributions through cryptocurrency exchanges, investors will get to lower the chances of losing their funds to scammers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;By hosting IEO’s on the respective exchange platforms, crypto exchanges are directly affirming the credibility and reliability of the project. Exchanges need to carry out research on an IEO&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;project before they host it on their exchange platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Listing the project tokens on exchanges would be more comfortable after hosting on IEO&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;making the process less tiresome for all the parties involved here.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To Close&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Change is the path to a better market. IEO benefits are too good to be ignored by increasing the level of trust among cryptocurrency projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developing an IEO is not going to be a tedious process. But the truth is only few &lt;a href="https://www.zabtechnologies.net/blockchain-developers"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain Development Companies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have ventured into IEO development. The reason behind this is there is a limited knowledge spread on this to the crypto people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is still in the growing phase and can be a reap of profit for the traders in the future!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you ask me whether IEO is the alternative for ICO? Absolutely yes! IEO will be the future in the crypto industry which cannot be denied!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please share your thoughts in comment section!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=64fdd60a6e7a" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/what-is-ieo-initial-exchange-offering-is-this-the-new-phenomenon-in-crypto-capital-64fdd60a6e7a"&gt;What is IEO Initial Exchange Offering? Is this the new phenomenon in Crypto Capital?&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 12:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Malware Static Analysis -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82796/malware/malware-static-analysis-tool.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Malware researcher and founder of Yoroi Marco Ramilli shared a simple tool for malware static analysis he used to perform massive Malware analysis research. The following interface stands in front of a live engine which takes binary files and runs them against a plethora of hundreds of YARA rules. Some of them are publicly available [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82796/malware/malware-static-analysis-tool.html"&gt;Malware Static Analysis&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 09:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Payment wallets must improve customer grievance redress mechanisms: Expert -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/economy-policy/payment-wallets-must-improve-customer-grievance-redress-mechanisms-expert-119032400399_1.html</link><description>Cumbersome KYC requirements, issues of safety and security of personal information, and no incentive to maintain balance are some key concerns flagged by experts</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 22:05:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Streaming Service Twitch Removes Crypto Payment Options, Reddit User Reports -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/streaming-service-twitch-removes-crypto-payment-options-reddit-user-reports</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jYzkwNWE3N2Y5Y2RmYTgwMzdiYTM0MGYzNDg2N2FkMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin and Bitcoin Cash have been removed as payment options from Amazon-owned streaming service Twitch&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian top stories: Christchurch attacks: the media's rush to be first causes its own kind of harm -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/commentisfree/2019/mar/24/christchurch-attacks-the-medias-rush-to-be-first-causes-its-own-kind-of-harm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s AI may have failed the victims – but humans didn’t do much better&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rookie journalists struggling with their copy are often told by news editors: “Just tell the story”. An esteemed colleague once told me his first editor told him to imagine shouting the intro to an aged relative moving away at speed on a bus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boiling an event down to who, what, why, where and when is the basis of all news coverage for a reason – it tells the story. But what happens when being fast and crafting a simple narrative becomes misleading or causes its own kind of harm?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/media/commentisfree/2019/mar/24/christchurch-attacks-the-medias-rush-to-be-first-causes-its-own-kind-of-harm"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: “Managed services”: pushing performance boundaries -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/managed-services-pushing-performance-boundaries/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_644647744-min-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_644647744-min-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_644647744-min-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;by Eva Andren, Head of Managed Services, Ericsson Middle East and Africa&lt;br /&gt;
We are in the middle of the fourth industrial revolution. As new technologies like 5G, IoT and cloud gain traction, networks are becoming more complex. It is becoming challenging for humans to keep up with this complexity and keep networks operating at the level prescribed by the evolving services. The potential to change how networks are operated is as dramatic as the machines of the industrial revolution that changed the factory floor.&lt;br /&gt;
Leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI), automation and the power of data, the Ericsson Operations Engine is rewriting the rules of network operations. The solution is an end-to-end managed services operating model that reimagines network and IT operations, network design and optimization, and applications development and maintenance.&lt;br /&gt;
Managed services play a significant role in the service providers’ transformation initiatives taking place worldwide. Nearly 65 percent of service providers indicate that managed services are key in addressing their main operational concerns around customer experience – improving customer experience being the number one factor that will influence service providers’ use of managed services – revenue growth and cost efficiency.&lt;br /&gt;
It is also clear that advanced technologies like AI, automation, and analytics represent the underlying pillars for supporting and enabling operational transformation. With the ability to rapidly solve complex challenges, AI is essential to network design, operations, and optimization.&lt;br /&gt;
On the other hand, automation uses technology to remove monotonous, repetitive tasks from traditional ways of working and boosting productivity. With more than 6000 automation rules, the Ericsson Operations Engine drives efficiency at every level of the organization – evolving operations from being network-centric to user experience-centric and fundamentally changing our way of operating networks from reactive to proactive, leveraging data, automation and AI.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
From granular network measurements to aggregated customer experience indicators, data drives everything we do. Growth in data traffic and increased device complexity have challenged service providers on all fronts—demanding new levels of customer experience, efficiency, and innovation. Using AI and automation, the Ericsson Operations Engine processes large, complex data sets to uncover valuable insights and drive new levels of network performance, flexibility, and scalability.&lt;br /&gt;
Designed to help operators manage the networks of the future, the Ericsson Operations Engine has three building blocks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 	Service-centric business model based on business outcomes: Using AI, automation and data insights, the Ericsson Operations Engine addresses targeted business outcomes for service providers such as enhanced customer experience, revenue growth and efficiency. With deep insights into performance and reliability, service providers are able to pivot and adapt networks to meet the growing demands of customers and enterprises.&lt;br /&gt;
 	End-to-end capabilities: Delivering on business outcomes through AI-based design, planning and optimization, data-driven operations, dynamic deployment, applications development, and collaborative innovation. To power everything from dynamic deployment to collaborative innovation, many processes use closed feedback loops to learn and optimize over time, improving operations on-the-fly.&lt;br /&gt;
 	Components: Best-in-class tools and processes that leverage data, AI and automation as well as expertise and investments in the service provider domain. Powered by next-generation tools and expertise, it enables service providers to rapidly test, deploy, and scale new products and services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Networks are quickly becoming significantly more complex to operate as we introduce IoT and 5G at scale, and virtualize core networks while aiming to enhance the user experience at the same time. Engineered to meet the demands of increased network complexity, the Ericsson Operations Engine combines advanced components and capabilities into one powerful solution. It enables service providers to proactively manage the network and addresses service providers’ managed services complexity challenges as the industry moves to the reality of 5G and IoT.&lt;br /&gt;
The Engine not only enables service providers to impact existing operations but also provides a platform to innovate and nurture new businesses. The OpenWorks lab combines people expertise with best-in-class tools like AI and analytics to rapidly test, deploy, and scale new products and services.&lt;br /&gt;
Driven by business outcomes and with the destination in mind, this is your ultimate Engine to transform best-in-class components into real-world capabilities to deliver powerful results with speed, efficiency, and agility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/managed-services-pushing-performance-boundaries/"&gt;&amp;#8220;Managed services&amp;#8221;: pushing performance boundaries&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 07:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: How Lightning Makes Bitcoin Great Again (for Payments) -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/how-lightning-makes-bitcoin-great-again-for-payments</link><description>Lightning Labs' Alex Bosworth talks about how the lightning network provides bitcoin's best hope for becoming the payments network of the future.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 11:05:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin Holds Just Over $4,000 as Top Cryptos See Slight Losses -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-holds-just-over-4-000-as-top-cryptos-see-slight-losses</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82YmQ5OTVlM2NlZjUyZjdjYjMyYWYyNzQ2NzlhZDJjOC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin holds just over $4,000 as most of the top 20 cryptocurrencies report slight losses on the day&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Hodler’s Digest, March 18–24: Hodler’s Digest, Top Stories, Price Movements, Quotes and FUD of the Week -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hodlers-digest-march-1824-hodlers-digest-top-stories-price-movements-quotes-and-fud-of-the-week</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81ODY1ZTE5ZTQ3ZGQ3N2ZhODJmNTM2NzAxYzY3MjAzYi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Korean dissidents are selling “visas” based on ETH, Square wants to develop open source crypto contributions, and more in this week’s Hodler’s Digest&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Etisalat to make 5G dream a reality in the UAE -  Puntaje: 9000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/telecom/etisalat-to-make-5g-dream-a-reality-in-the-uae/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/AGM-Picture-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/AGM-Picture-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/AGM-Picture-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;What's the next big disruption that could change the way we use technology? The telecom industry is buzzing with talk of superfast 5G networks permitting for downloads of up to 10 Gigabytes per second, which could enhance the Internet of Things (IoT), artificial intelligence, machine learning and bring to our daily lives the use of augmented reality, 3D printing, autonomous vehicles and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etisalat, which was ranked the No. 1 most valuable telecoms brand in the UAE in 2018, is leading the way in bringing 5G to life. As part of its new direction "Together Matters", the company aims to use the power of technology to connect people and enrich their lives. The company, which completed its first 5G launch on C-band in MENA, has stated that it intends to invest 4 billion AED into digital transformation, mobile and fiber networks during this year. Apart from high connection speeds, the implementation of 5G will also lower latency issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Etisalat envisions 5G as a stepping-stone to unlimited potential, a technology that will enable new use cases, widen possibilities, and enhance value creation. Hence, we were the first to launch the first commercial 5G network in the UAE and the region achieving another technological milestone for the company. The fifth generation of the network will fuel digital transformation, IoT, smart cities and the fourth industrial revolution," said Eissa Mohamed Al-Suwaidi, Chairman, Etisalat Group, at the company's Annual General Meeting (AGM) held at the company’s headquarters in Abu Dhabi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Race toward 5G implementation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etisalat is working on enhancing its infrastructure with 5G towers and sites, in order to ensure that it provides 5G connectivity to fixed and mobile devices, as well as coverage across the country. Etisalat has already announced partnerships with Huawei and Ericsson to deploy 5G across the UAE. The company's prime competitor in the country, du has partnered with Virgin Mobile to build 5G infrastructure and deploy it in the UAE. Elsewhere in the GCC, Saudi Telecom has announced a deal with Nokia to bring 5G to Saudi Arabia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, du announced that it successfully conducted its first live 5G data call, while deploying 700 5G sites across the UAE. With the Expo 2020 around the corner, Etisalat is also aiming to provide innovative telecom solutions to the millions of participants and visitors, including an Etisalat 'smart site' at the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Etisalat is keen on staying ahead when it comes to next-generation technologies, our investment in the future has enabled us to achieve the first 5G commercial launch in MENA with EXPO 2020 as the first business customer. This achievement will redefine connectivity and support the full-fledged adoption of the Internet of things. As an industry leader, we have a role in driving change and expanding the telecommunication ecosystem, we are building a platform for the future, which will materialize the next generation of immersive experiences and power the digital economy," said Saleh Abdullah Al Abdooli, GCEO, Etisalat Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Driving financial success&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etisalat's efforts to lead in the digital space and transform its operating model has helped the Group's financials soar as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In 2018, we have delivered a solid financial performance, with consolidated revenues at AED 52.4 billion, and consolidated net profit at AED 8.6 billion, representing 2.4 percent year-on-year growth. This is an outstanding outcome considering the stagnant global economy and some operating companies’ specific challenges pertaining to currency devaluation, geopolitical instability, and elevated competitive and regulatory pressures," said Saleh Abdullah Al Abdooli, GCEO, Etisalat Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Etisalat Group continued to achieve strong financial performance and maintained its high credit rating reflecting its efforts to provide value to shareholders, which was the drive behind proposing a final dividend of AED 0.4 per share, bringing the total dividends for the year to AED 0.80, in line with our policy in previous years. This represents a dividend yield of 4.7 percent and dividends payout ratio of around 81 percent," said Eissa Mohamed Al-Suwaidi, Chairman, Etisalat Group.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/telecom/etisalat-to-make-5g-dream-a-reality-in-the-uae/"&gt;Etisalat to make 5G dream a reality in the UAE&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 10:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: 3 Promising cryptocurrencies under $5 to invest in for 2019–2020 -  Puntaje: 17700</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/3-promising-cryptocurrencies-under-5-to-invest-in-for-2019-2020-36b72fa32808?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h4&gt;From cross-blockchain transfers to a banking competitor cryptocurrency that targets over 2 billion users&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*R0O_nF7z9IF-8ci8rV7FyQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When investing in cryptocurrency, one overlooked but important factor to look out for is utility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forget the flashy ICO adverts and look instead at how a cryptocurrency will be used. A high utility provides the following benefits to a cryptocurrency:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Improves liquidity&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;A cryptocurrency that is constantly being used, transferred and traded allows for investors to easily buy and sell said cryptocurrency. A cryptocurrency with a high marketcap may make you wealthy (on paper) but if it is not being traded enough, who will buy it off you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Drives demand&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;A cryptocurrency with a legitimate use is a cryptocurrency that is needed and sought out by users who can benefit from it’s utility. It is also sought out by investors looking to profit from the cryptocurrency’s demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Creates scarcity&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The more a cryptocurrency is in demand the more it will be acquired by users, leading to less coins in circulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today we will look at three different cryptocurrencies with very ambitious use cases.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pantos (PAN)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*yQE_4hS32hQIGFpqxZy69w.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAN currently sits at a price of around $0.01, very early days for this project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pantos (PAN) is a cross-chain cryptocurrency developed by cryptocurrency exchange &lt;a href="https://www.bitpanda.com/?ref=3127933809251797450"&gt;BitPanda&lt;/a&gt;, which is also the only place where investors can currently buy this cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAN is being developed to work across all blockchains, being able to transfer from the Ethereum blockchain for example to the Lisk blockchain and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This will allow for cross-blockchain transfers of digital assets, a feat that has not yet been tackled by any cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To achieve this, PAN relies on Token Atomic Swap Technology (TAST), which is essentially Atomic Swap technology for inter-blockchain transfers between cryptocurrency tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To help bring this project to life, PAN is being developed in collaboration with researchers from various institutions which include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;University of Vienna&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Research Institute for Future Cryptoeconomics (RIAT)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Austrian Academy of Sciences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If successful, PAN will allow near instant cross-chain transfers, allowing users to transfer assets from one blockchain to another without having to use a third party medium such as an exchange.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAN is barely on the map, this cryptocurrency is still in the early adopter phase and no other exchange has access to this token yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For what they are trying to accomplish, the partners they work with (including Waves, Komodo, Lisk &amp;amp; NEM) and the low access to this token, I believe PAN is very undervalued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OmiseGo (OMG)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*8dvwMC3y_Zv1mgzgj5CIjQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;OmiseGo (OMG) is currently sitting at a marketcap of $248 million and a price of $1.75 which is unbelievable considering the huge demand this cryptocurrency had just last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OMG is a cryptocurrency created by a real world company, Omise, which provides online payment solutions to thousands of merchants. Omise has been featured in Forbes Thailand in 2016 and was also awarded “Digital Startup of The Year” by Thailands Prime Minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OMG is trying to solve 2 problems:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hundreds of million people in Asia, and &lt;strong&gt;2 billion people around the world, are unbanked, &lt;/strong&gt;meaning they don’t have access to a bank account.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;They want to make it easy to transfer value across many different networks and among many different currencies or assets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;OMG wants to provide the unbanked population with an easy to use system to store, send and receive money, in any currency or asset, for a very low cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To put it more simply, OmiseGo wants users, vendors and merchants to easily transfer money across the globe, across any network using any kind of currency of asset type.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This could be fiat money (GBP, USD,THB etc.), cryptocurrencies or any digitised asset through a secured blockchain network at a very low cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OMG are targeting both individuals and Electronic Payment Providers which gives the cryptocurrency a massive room for adoption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scale of the problem that OMG is trying to tackle is a really large one with hundreds of millions of potential users in Asia alone (where OmiseGo is based) and over 2 billion worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I believe they have a great opportunity to accomplish this, being one of the very few companies taking on this challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stellar Lumens (XLM)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*5P-JN1DsD7967bHUqbiZjA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;XLM is currently sitting at a marketcap of $2 billion and a price of $0.10, a steal in my opinion considering it’s potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;XLM boasts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Almost instant transactions (2–3 seconds)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Almost free transactions (0.00001 XLM per transaction)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partnerships with Stripe, IBM and Deloitte&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;XLM plans to takeover the global money transfer market, possibly replacing SWIFT which currently handles over $5 Trillion in transactions daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comparing SWIFT and XLM:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;SWIFT transaction cost at least $25, XLM cost less than a fraction of a penny&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SWIFT transaction time 3–5 business days, XLM takes 2 -3 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Stellar Lumens blockchain can also be used to develop decentralised apps (dapps) and deploy smart contracts with lower transaction costs and faster transaction speeds than the current leader Ethereum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This also allows XLM to serve as backbone towards the creation of new cryptocurrencies, just like Ethereum is the platform behind ERC-20 tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every time an ERC-20 token is used, transactions fees are paid in Ether (ETH), and now XLM’s blockchain can be home to new digital assets, from cryptocurrencies to even weapons and skins in a video game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have not even scratched the surface when it comes to digital assets yet, we are talking about digital goods with real, tangible and real world value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally Stellar have their own decentralised exchange, The Stellar Decentralised Exchange (Stellar DEX). This allows the peer-to-peer exchange of cryptocurrencies without a third party organisation or a need to verify your identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stellar/XLM is really undervalued in my opinion considering the scope and what they are planning to tackle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technology is already there, all we need is an on-ramp for the Average Joe to understand before we reach mass adoption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;These cryptocurrencies may seem be ahead of their time with the issues they aim to solve, especially to the average person who may not be aware of these problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However this may be the very same reason why they hold a lot of potential. If any of these cryptocurrencies interest you, here is where you can find and invest into them:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stellar (XLM) can be bought directly from &lt;a href="http://cex.io/r/0/up106280379/0"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CEX&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pantos (PAN) &amp;amp; OmiseGo (OMG) can be bought directly from &lt;a href="https://www.bitpanda.com/?ref=3127933809251797450"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BitPanda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; if you live anywhere in Europe.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All 3 can be bought using Bitcoin (BTC) or Ethereum (ETH) from &lt;a href="https://www.binance.com/?ref=11282713"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times like this, when the market is quiet, is a good time for accumulation in my opinion, I cant wait to see how these projects mature over the years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=36b72fa32808" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/3-promising-cryptocurrencies-under-5-to-invest-in-for-2019-2020-36b72fa32808"&gt;3 Promising cryptocurrencies under $5 to invest in for 2019–2020&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 15:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>