<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 23:42:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>finextra: Money 20/20 Asia: Blockchain, bitcoin and the intrinsic value of tokens -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33550/money-2020-asia-blockchain-bitcoin-and-the-intrinsic-value-of-tokens?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Money20/20 Asia 2019 kicked off proceedings in Singapore with Token Day, tackling the hype around bl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 06:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: TNW: Craig Wright Filed 114 Blockchain-Related Patents Since 2017 -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tnw-craig-wright-filed-114-blockchain-related-patents-since-2017</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80MTc5NDVmNGQxOTk1OTIxMTZlZmUzODk0MmYwYTljZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Controversial Bitcoin figure Craig Wright has reportedly filed over 100 blockchain-related patents since 2017&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Québécois Regulator Calls for Investors in Non-Compliant Blockchain Firm to Come Forward -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/quebecois-regulator-calls-for-investors-in-non-compliant-blockchain-firm-to-come-forward</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yNTA3NTkyZjQxNmViOTljOWM4YjZjYTNjNmU1NTJlMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Québec’s financial regulator has asked investors in Blockchain Lab to come forward, now that the entity faces injunctive orders over alleged violations of securities laws&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Galaxy Digital Backs $5.25 Million Round for Blockchain Staking Startup -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/galaxy-digital-backs-5-25-million-round-for-blockchain-staking-startup</link><description>Blockchain staking startup Bison Trails has raised $5.25 million in a series seed funding round backed by investors including Galaxy Digital.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: BitGo Launches Custody for Blockchain Capital’s Security Token BCAP -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitgo-launches-custody-for-blockchain-capitals-security-token-bcap</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9iYjIzZDkxMTFlYjdlMmYzZGRjYTgzZmM0Y2M0NWI2Yi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin security platform BitGo has announced support of BCAP, a security token that raised $10 million in a 2017 ICO from Blockchain Capital&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Blockchain Startup Bison Trails Receives $5.25 Mln Investment Backed by Galaxy Digital -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-startup-bison-trails-receives-525-mln-investment-backed-by-galaxy-digital</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82YjNjZDQ0ZjNmYTdmOTIyNjc2N2EwY2M2YjFiNjIxNy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;New blockchain startup Bison Trails has recevied $5.25 million in a series investment round backed by Galaxy Digital&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japanese Company Launches New Stablecoin Pegged to the US Dollar -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japanese-company-launches-new-stablecoin-pegged-to-the-us-dollar</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81NDQ0YzNiYmRhMWY1Y2Q4MTExNmIzZmZjNjBjZjM0MC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Japanese company is helping crypto consumers avoid price volatility through a new stablecoin that is supported by major Ethereum wallets #SPONSORED&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Archax partners with Quod Financial for digital asset order routing -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77711/archax-partners-with-quod-financial-for-digital-asset-order-routing?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Quod Financial, the advanced trading platform provider to the buy-side and sell-side, today announce...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 12:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Kakao Affiliate Dunamu Launches Blockchain Service Platform -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kakao-affiliate-dunamu-launches-blockchain-service-platform</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8wNjdkY2E1MWY4OGI0NjdmYjU3ODkxZWZlMTgzODdmMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kakao’s fintech arm Dunamu is rolling out a blockchain platform designed to help companies start businesses using blockchain&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Blockchain and AI: Leading the Way to the Fourth Industrial Revolution Against the Odds -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-and-ai-leading-the-way-to-the-fourth-industrial-revolution-against-the-odds</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xNDQxODZhNGFjYTg0NTY1NjBhZGRkZGI0MDhkMGQwNi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, AI and blockchain technologies are more complementary than competitive in their natures, and are used together in solutions where the personal data security is of great importance&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Digital Asset Names New CEO to Succeed Blythe Masters -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/digital-asset-names-new-ceo-to-succeed-blythe-masters</link><description>Enterprise blockchain startup Digital Asset has named co-founder Yuval Rooz as the company’s new chief executive officer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Japanese USDDex – New ERC-20 Stablecoin Claims up to 45% Profit to Crypto Investors -  Puntaje: 3100</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/new-erc-20-stablecoin-generates-up-to-45-profit-to-crypto-investors/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/new-erc-20-stablecoin-generates-up-to-45-profit-to-crypto-investors/"&gt;Japanese USDDex &amp;#8211; New ERC-20 Stablecoin Claims up to 45% Profit to Crypto Investors&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/staffwriter/"&gt;Staff Writer&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/stablecoins-1-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="32257" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/new-erc-20-stablecoin-generates-up-to-45-profit-to-crypto-investors/stablecoins-2/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/stablecoins-1.jpg" data-orig-size="760,392" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="stablecoins" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/stablecoins-1-300x155.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/stablecoins-1.jpg" /&gt;One month prior to the official offering on cryptocurrency exchanges, the Japanese USDDex team made the strategic decision offer a second token sale for their decentralized stablecoin on March 19, 2019. This will be a limited release with a 45 percent bonus structure. The main goal of this decision was to open up to a [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/new-erc-20-stablecoin-generates-up-to-45-profit-to-crypto-investors/"&gt;Japanese USDDex &amp;#8211; New ERC-20 Stablecoin Claims up to 45% Profit to Crypto Investors&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/staffwriter/"&gt;Staff Writer&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Digital Asset names company co-founder Yuval Rooz as CEO -  Puntaje: 3400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77713/digital-asset-names-company-co-founder-yuval-rooz-as-ceo?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Digital Asset, the creators of DAML and leading provider of Distributed Ledger Technology (DLT) solu...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: 17 Australian Blockchain Startups to Watch Out For -  Puntaje: 6600</title><link>https://gomedici.com/17-australian-blockchain-startups-to-watch-out-for/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/17-australian-blockchain-startups-to-watch-out-for.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;On Mar 18, 2019, Australia’s federal government announced a boost of AU $100,000 and its plan to develop a national blockchain roadmap. Efforts are in the right direction to position Australia as a hub for blockchain technologies – the Australian FinTech landscape will be interesting to observe in 2019. Here is a list of 19 Australia blockchain startups to watch out for: Sharering was founded in 2018. It is a system designed specifically to share/rent things with others. Havven was founded in 2017 and has raised $250k in total funding. Havven is a decentralized payment network designed to enable cryptocurrency purchases. The incentive mechanisms deployed by Havven encourage users to provide collateral, and/or use stable tokens to facilitate payments. ChronoBank was founded in 2016 and has raised $5.4 million in total funding. ChronoBank leverages blockchain technology to provide cryptocurrency wallet and cryptocurrency exchange services to the businesses and individuals. It...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:40:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bitmain’s Latest Zcash Miner Claimed to Have Tripled Hashing Power -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bitmain-launches-new-zcash-miner-touting-3-times-more-hashing-power</link><description>Bitmain has unveiled a new miner for the privacy-oriented crypto zcash, which it says, has three times more hashing power than its predecessor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 06:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Visa builds Crypto Team -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33553/visa-builds-crypto-team?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Visa is quietly building a 'Crypto Team' to execute the card scheme's strategy for the cryptocurrenc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Crypto app Donut gets sweet $1.8m seed funding -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/crypto-app-donut-gets-sweet-1-8m-seed-funding/</link><description>Bringing "convenience, trust and accessibility" to managing and transacting in crypto assets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 10:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Australia: Clients Take Crypto Fund Manager to Court, Cite $14.2 Million in Losses -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-clients-take-crypto-fund-manager-to-court-cite-142-million-in-losses</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lZTNhNGQyYmNiODcwY2NlYmI0NTllMjg2NWZjYWQ2Mi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stefanos Papanastasiou, a crypto fund manager, is being brought to court in Australia by clients who claim over $14 million in losses&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Road to Consensus with Amber Baldet: Crypto, Privacy and Profit -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/road-to-consensus-with-clovyrs-amber-baldet-crypto-privacy-and-profit</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 02:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: The world’s obsession with “lite”: Uber Middle East is next -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/trending/worlds-obsession-uber-lite/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/uber-lite-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/uber-lite-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/uber-lite-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;It’s Uber’s turn to go “lite” on us.&lt;br /&gt;
No, the taxis are still the same size, if you’re wondering.&lt;br /&gt;
What’s going on?&lt;br /&gt;
Some background may be in order...&lt;br /&gt;
First, a quick detour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world has been obsessed with the buzzword lite for almost a century now. Lite soda, lite dessert, and now even lite apps! If there exists a more diminished version of a product, it will be labelled lite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where did this obsession come from, and how has it come to transcend food products?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where did the word “lite” originate from?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously, the term comes as a form of colloquialism or slang of the word light, used as meaning less of something. Lightweight, light content, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the Online Etymology Dictionary, it began being consciously used as a contraction of “light” as early as 1917 in marketing speak, even if it has roots in Old English under the same meaning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Understanding the product marketing behind the buzzword&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a technical standpoint, “when a food label uses the term "light" or "lite," it indicates that a food has one third fewer calories or 50% less fat, or 50% less sodium than a comparable product (as regulated in the US by the FDA and USDA),” Toby Smithson, Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics, notes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a product marketing perspective, lite implies you are on the conservative side, considering your health and/or consumption. In an international culture that encourages and thrives on overspending and consumption, lite has emerged as the natural opposite to this, propagated by the same culture that pushes consumerism in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;‘Now that you’ve overindulged on our overpriced, fat-rich products, it’s time for us to remind you that you need to get that beach summer body before June arrives! Why not try our lite-offerings? 0-fat and 0-sugar, guaranteed! Don’t mind what we replace them with, though…’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a vicious cycle that encourages endless spending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weight-watcher craze of a few decades ago brought the concept of lite to the forefront, and the millennial culture of vegetarianism, veganism and wellness has served to make lite even bigger than it already was, bringing a more well-rounded health approach to it. As such, businesses have had to up their game by branching out their lite spiel to sodium and other nutritional content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Evolving beyond the F&amp;amp;B sector, and where Uber comes in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the word was used in the food and beverages industry primarily, it has come to pervade other industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“People might attach a “lite” label to anything (or anyone) simpler than the original version,” Grammarly explains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As is fitting with the digital age, lite has spilled over to app design. Things like Facebook Lite, Skype Lite and Instagram Lite are now industry givens, existing to serve users with limited data plans or in countries with less a than stellar internet connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just this week, Uber Lite launched in the UAE and Saudi Arabia. At 5 MB in size, it will allow usage of the app with low-tier smartphones and even through a weak internet connection. It is lite in data size and lite in the experience itself, offering a more basic Uber UX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As millennial culture continues to emphasize the concept of wellness, “lite” and all it connotes will continue to increase in intensity in the F &amp;amp; B sector, while continuously spilling over to other industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From lite foods, to lite-devices, to lite-cryptocurrencies, the sky is the limit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/trending/worlds-obsession-uber-lite/"&gt;The world&amp;#8217;s obsession with &amp;#8220;lite&amp;#8221;: Uber Middle East is next&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 12:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Largest Swiss Online Retailer Digitec Galaxus Now Accepts Cryptocurrencies -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/largest-swiss-online-retailer-digitec-galaxus-now-accepts-cryptocurrencies</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yYzlmNDA5MzBhYzEwYjIxMTg1MzhjZGVhMmI5OTM1MC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrencies are now accepted by the leading Swiss online retailer Digitec Galaxus&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Silvergate Bank Adds 59 Crypto Clients, But Deposits Down $123 Million -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/silvergate-bank-adds-59-crypto-clients-but-deposits-down-123-million-in-q4</link><description>Silvergate Bank added 59 crypto clients in the fourth quarter, but its deposits from the industry shrank by $123 million.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: 2gether adds crypto to pre-paid Visa card -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77710/2gether-adds-crypto-to-pre-paid-visa-card?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Following its successful beta launch in Spain, 2gether, the modern mutual banking platform, is annou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 11:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: US SEC Solicits Feedback on Crypto Assets and Custody Rules -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-sec-solicits-feedback-on-crypto-assets-and-custody-rules</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lNDg1MjliMTZkZmY2OTQwMzEzMzA5OWExMmMyMmJmOC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US SEC is soliciting industry input as it potentially reconsiders existing custody rules for investment advisers in certain cases of crypto trading and settlement&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Report From Former CFTC Chairman Calls for Advanced Crypto Regulations -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-from-former-cftc-chairman-calls-for-advanced-crypto-regulations</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9iMzFkZWViNTBhMDljOWMwMmU3MzUyM2VhM2NmNTBiMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a recent report, former CFTC chairman Timothy Massad called for more thorough regulations on cryptocurrencies&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bitcoin’s Share of Total Crypto Market Slips Back Toward 50% -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bitcoins-share-of-total-crypto-market-slips-back-toward-50</link><description>Bitcoin's share of the cryptocurrency market is on the verge of falling below 50 percent for the first time in over 7 months.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC business: Why are Venezuelans seeking refuge in crypto-currencies? -  Puntaje: 1125.0</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-47553048</link><description>As Venezuela staggers under political and economic crises, its citizens are embracing digital money.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Cryptopia Crypto Exchange Resumes Trading on 40 Crypto Pairs -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cryptopia-crypto-exchange-resumes-trading-on-40-crypto-pairs</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy84YTk2MjhmZDM4MzA0Y2RjNjlhMTgyYmViZWJkM2MyNy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following a mid-January hack, crypto exchange Cryptopia has resumed trading on 40 trade pairs&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 23:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Threatpost: Podcast: The High-Risk Threats Behind the Norsk Hydro Cyberattack -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://threatpost.com/podcast-the-high-risk-threats-behind-the-norsk-hydro-cyberattack/142954/</link><description>Threatpost talks to Phil Neray with CyberX about Tuesday's ransomware attack on aluminum producer Norsk Hydro, and how it compares to past manufacturing attacks like Triton, WannaCry and more.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>We Live Security: You should pick your Android security app wisely, test shows -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/eset/blog/~3/vi6hG4IgLtg/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s prudent to get a security solution for your device, but a test by AV-Comparatives shows why you need to choose judiciously    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.welivesecurity.com/2019/03/19/android-anti-malware-apps-ads/"&gt;You should pick your Android security app wisely, test shows&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="/" rel="nofollow"&gt;WeLiveSecurity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/eset/blog/~4/vi6hG4IgLtg" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Aluminum producer Norsk Hydro hit by a massive cyber attack -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82618/security/norsk-hydro-cyber-attack.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The giant of aluminum producers, Norway&amp;#8217;s Norsk Hydro, announced on Tuesday that it had been hit by a cyber-attack of unknown origin. One of the biggest Aluminum producer, the Norwegian Norsk Hydro, suffered an extensive cyber attack. &amp;#8220;Hydro became victim of an extensive cyberattack in the early hours of Tuesday, impacting operations in several of [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82618/security/norsk-hydro-cyber-attack.html"&gt;Aluminum producer Norsk Hydro hit by a massive cyber attack&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: A new development shows a potential shift to using Mirai to target enterprises -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82583/breaking-news/mirai-targets-enterprises.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;PaloAlto Networks researchers discovered a new variant of the infamous Mirai botnet is targeting IoT devices belonging to businesses. Researchers at PaloAlto Networks spotted a new variant of the infamous Mirai botnet is targeting IoT devices belonging to businesses. Mirai malware first appeared in the wild in 2016 when the expert MalwareMustDie discovered it in massive attacks [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82583/breaking-news/mirai-targets-enterprises.html"&gt;A new development shows a potential shift to using Mirai to target enterprises&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 06:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Threatpost: Cardinal RAT Resurrected to Target FinTech Firms -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://threatpost.com/cardinal-rat-fintech/142965/</link><description>A long-quiet malware family has been spotted targeting financial technology firms, armed with new obfuscation techniques to avoid detection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 21:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Report: Malware Targets Israeli Fintech Firms Working in Crypto, Forex Trading -  Puntaje: 5000</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-malware-targets-israeli-fintech-firms-working-in-crypto-forex-trading</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yNWU3ZGVkYmQ2ZDc0YmViODdlMjZlZGU1NTExNmE2MC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israeli fintech companies that deal with crypto and forex trading are targeted by malware, a cybersecurity company reports&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: China: Shenzhen Issues Country’s First Subway Electronic Invoices Backed With Blockchain -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-shenzhen-issues-countrys-first-subway-electronic-invoices-backed-with-blockchain</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83MTRlMDk5OTM5NjcxNDEzZGZlYzZlZDk4ZjI2NTE1NS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Shenzhen Metro and Chinese tech giant Tencent are now using the WeChat payment platform for electronic blockchain invoices&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Fortune 500 Company Avnet Works With BitBay to Add Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash Payment Option -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fortune-500-company-avnet-works-with-bitbay-to-add-bitcoin-bitcoin-cash-payment-option</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83OGQ3ZGNjYzJiOGQyNzBiMWZmYTMyMmQ0ZTQ1N2QzOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avnet, a Fortune 500 firm, now accepts Bitcoin and Bitcoin Cash after working with BitPay for cryptocurrency payment processing&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Fortune 500 Tech Firm Avnet Now Accepts Crypto Payments via BitPay -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/fortune-500-tech-firm-avnet-now-accepts-crypto-payments-via-bitpay</link><description>Avnet, one of the world's largest distributors of electronic components and services, is now accepting crypto payments through BitPay.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Mastercard venture aims to help small banks keep up in payments -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/mastercard-joint-venture-aims-to-help-small-banks-close-digital-divide</link><description>The credit card network has teamed up with an ICBA unit and the fintech Urban FT to offer a payments services program tailored to community banks trying to keep pace with bigger banks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 16:10:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: Rapyd Launches Local Payments Solution Rapyd Checkout -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/03/rapyd-launches-local-payments-solution-rapyd-checkout/</link><description>Fintech-as-a-service platform Rapyd today launched Rapyd Checkout, a hyper-local payments solution allowing merchants to accept over 500 local payment types including cash, bank transfers, local cards, and e-wallets, in 100-plus countries. This follows the company’s $40 million Series B funding in February. Helcio Nobre, Chief Product Officer at Rapyd, told Bank Innovation that Checkout allows [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: IBM Gears up to Challenge Ripple and SWIFT With Its Blockchain Payments -  Puntaje: 5500</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29567/blockchain/ibm-worldwire/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;IBM World Wire is the Big Blue&amp;#8217;s foray into real-time global payments network for financial institutions using blockhain &amp;#8212; a space where fierce competition is happening between SWIFT and Ripple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29567/blockchain/ibm-worldwire/"&gt;IBM Gears up to Challenge Ripple and SWIFT With Its Blockchain Payments&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 03:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Open banking: progressing to the summit -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/open-banking-progressing-to-the-summit/</link><description>Banks and disruptors alike are still trekking through the foothills of open banking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Accenture Banking Blog: Open Banking is a reality for some commercial banking customers -  Puntaje: 3125.0</title><link>https://bankingblog.accenture.com/open-banking-reality-some-commercial-banking-customers</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Open Banking is now a major global initiative. European Union regulations including the second Payment Services Directive (PSD2) are pushing banks to provide access to account information and to make it possible for third-party suppliers of payment services to make direct connections with banks’ customer accounts. Open Banking will transform commercial banking In the UK,…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://bankingblog.accenture.com/open-banking-reality-some-commercial-banking-customers"&gt;Open Banking is a reality for some commercial banking customers&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://bankingblog.accenture.com"&gt;Accenture Banking Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Binance Launchpad Hosts Its Third ICO With Celer Network Raising $4 Million -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-launchpad-hosts-its-third-ico-with-celer-network-raising-4-million</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jYTk1MGUyNjYyNjQ0ZDE1MDFlNGIyM2ZkZGQyOTM3NC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binance Launchpad completed another token sale, with Celer Network raising $4 million in some 18 minutes&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro News: Raw Politics in full: Facebook fallout and the EU's artificial intelligence race -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/euronews/en/home/~3/ObXU4GBUqFU/raw-politics-in-full-facebook-fallout-and-the-eu-s-artificial-intelligence-race</link><description>Watch Tuesday night's full episode of Raw Politics&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/euronews/en/home/~4/ObXU4GBUqFU" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 18:10:12 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Big Tech: Nvidia launches Jetson Nano Pi-alike AI boards -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/bit-tech/all/~3/PzHpE3EeoQQ/</link><description>Cheapest Jetson product yet.&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/bit-tech/all/~4/PzHpE3EeoQQ" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Grab Launches “Buy Now Pay Later” and an Online Store Checkout Plugin -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29601/mobilepayments/grow-with-grab-pay-later-pos-e-commerce/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;During Money 20/20 today, Grab made a few announcements along the fintech vertical, focusing particularly on areas that have historically proven to show high potential in the SEA region. Two&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29601/mobilepayments/grow-with-grab-pay-later-pos-e-commerce/"&gt;Grab Launches &amp;#8220;Buy Now Pay Later&amp;#8221; and an Online Store Checkout Plugin&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 08:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: How fintechs are revolutionizing the customer onboarding process -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16833/how-fintechs-are-revolutionizing-the-customer-onboarding-process?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>As per a recent CNBC report (1), In US, fintech companies accounted for 38 percent of all US persona...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 12:25:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Nordigen, Sensibill Earn Spots in Fintech Europe’s Incoming Cohort -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://finovate.com/nordigen-sensibill-earn-spots-in-fintech-europes-incoming-cohort/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A pair of Finovate alums &amp;#8211; including a Best of Show winner &amp;#8211; are among the nine companies chosen to participate in the incoming group of startups for Plug and Play&amp;#8217;s Fintech Europe. Nordigen, which made its Finovate debut at FinovateFall last year, and Sensibill, which won Best of Show in its FinovateFall debut in &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/nordigen-sensibill-earn-spots-in-fintech-europes-incoming-cohort/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/nordigen-sensibill-earn-spots-in-fintech-europes-incoming-cohort/"&gt;Nordigen, Sensibill Earn Spots in Fintech Europe&amp;#8217;s Incoming Cohort&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 18:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Finovate Live: Digital Week -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://finovate.com/finovate-live-digital-week/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the upcoming Finovate Digital Wek, 19 - 21 March, for 3 days of exclusive webinars, white-papers and thought leadership from fintech pioneers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-live-digital-week/"&gt;Finovate Live: Digital Week&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 01:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: StanChart’s new platform connects start-ups and investors -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/stancharts-new-platform-connects-start-ups-and-investors/</link><description>SC Ventures Fintech Bridge will serve as a nexus for industry players linked to the bank.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: Half of Global Firms Concerned Over Security Skills Gaps -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/half-global-firms-concerned-1/</link><description>Trend Micro finds growing demand for AI-powered tools to combat skills issues</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Copenhagen Fintech and the LHoFT sign MoU -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77707/copenhagen-fintech-and-the-lhoft-sign-mou?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Copenhagen FinTech (CPH FINTECH) and The Luxembourg House of Financial Technologies (The LHoFT) have...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 11:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Money20/20 Asia: Banks struggling to keep up with fintech innovtion -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33551/money2020-asia-banks-struggling-to-keep-up-with-fintech-innovtion?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Money20/20 Asia saw representatives from Westpac, Deutsche Bank and LumenLab discuss how legacy infr...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Finovate Alumni News -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-960/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Finovate.com Nordigen, Sensibill Earn Spots in Fintech Europe&amp;#8217;s Incoming Cohort. Jumio Unveils Automated AML Screening Solution. Community Access from Urban FT Brings Digital Tools to Small Banks. Around the web PayPal teams up with JP Morgan Chase to offer instant transfer option. Coinbase&amp;#8217;s Custody service completes its first over-the-counter trade directly from offline storage. &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-960/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-960/"&gt;Finovate Alumni News&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: ZestFinance Launches AI-powered Tool to Reduce Bias in Lending Models -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/03/zestfinance-launches-ai-powered-tool-to-reduce-bias-in-lending-models/</link><description>Alternative underwriting software provider ZestFinance today launched an AI-based tool it claims will dramatically reduce bias in lending. Founder and CEO Douglas Merrill, a former Google CIO, told Bank Innovation that ZAML Fair, an add-on to the company's existing ZAML (Zest Automated Machine Learning) platform, is a new algorithm that lenders can use to tune [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Community Access from Urban FT Brings Digital Tools to Small Banks -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://finovate.com/community-access-from-urban-ft-brings-digital-tools-to-small-banks/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Urban FT Group, a fintech provider, is launching Community Access, an agent bank program that delivers financial tools on mobile banking for community banks’ consumer and commercial customers, reports Henry Vilar of Fintech Futures (Finovate&amp;#8217;s sister publication). Richard Steggall, Urban FT CEO, said: “With Community Access, community banks can truly compete with the bigger, national &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/community-access-from-urban-ft-brings-digital-tools-to-small-banks/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/community-access-from-urban-ft-brings-digital-tools-to-small-banks/"&gt;Community Access from Urban FT Brings Digital Tools to Small Banks&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 16:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: 2019 U.S. Wealth Management Outlook: The Old Guard And Fintech Cozy Up -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://finovate.com/2019-u-s-wealth-management-outlook-the-old-guard-and-fintech-cozy-up/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;What is it millennials want when it comes to managing their wealth? Robo-advisors? Human interaction? A medley of  both?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/2019-u-s-wealth-management-outlook-the-old-guard-and-fintech-cozy-up/"&gt;2019 U.S. Wealth Management Outlook: The Old Guard And Fintech Cozy Up&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: This artificial intelligence predicts online trolling before it happens -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/this-ai-predicts-online-trolling-before-it-happens</link><description>(Sander van der Werf/shutterstock) How do you keep online trolls in check?</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: UK Parliament Presented Showcase of Real-World Blockchain Applications -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/uk-parliament-presented-showcase-of-real-world-blockchain-applications</link><description>The U.K. Parliament has been presented demos of real-world blockchain applications designed to educate policymakers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 18:10:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: 2gether expands its prepaid crypto card into Europe -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/2gether-expands-its-prepaid-crypto-card-into-europe/</link><description>Consumers will be able to spend crypto as easily as euros.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Major Cryptocurrencies See Slight Gains, Palladium Hits $1,600 for The First Time -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/major-cryptocurrencies-see-slight-gains-palladium-hits-1-600-for-the-first-time</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xNWQ4OWU4ZjY5MWM0ZmY5ZjE0Zjc3MTIxNTA2ZTY1Zi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most top coins are seeing minor gains on the day, with Bitcoin hovering over the $4,000 mark&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Major Crypto Exchange and Wallet Coinbase Adds Support for Stellar Lumens -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/major-crypto-exchange-and-wallet-coinbase-adds-support-for-stellar-lumens</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jZDMxNmE3ZjE1N2M2MzBhNDM5M2U1NDk3ZTRkZGI5Zi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. crypto giant Coinbase has announced support for XLM on the company’s iOS and Android apps, as well as its website&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: Apple, Microsoft Top Orgs Used in Spear Phishing -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/apple-microsoft-top-orgs-used-in/</link><description>Brand impersonation is used in majority of spear-phishing attacks, report says.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: InstaReM Raises $41M To Expand Into Latin America -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/investment-tracker/2019/instarem-funding-latin-america/</link><description>InstaReM, the Singapore FinTech startup that enables banks and consumers to send money across borders, raised $41 million in venture funding. According to a report in TechCrunch, the four-year-old startup raised the money in a Series C round of funding. In November it raised $20 million in capital from investors. The most recent round was led […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Hear It From the Experts: Why It’s Riskier to Not Take Risks -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://finovate.com/hear-it-from-the-experts-why-its-riskier-to-not-take-risks/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The fintech industry is full of innovation, and it's moving at a fast pace. We spoke with leading fintech minds on what they're keeping an eye in 2019, as part of the #FinovateLive Digital Week. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/hear-it-from-the-experts-why-its-riskier-to-not-take-risks/"&gt;Hear It From the Experts: Why It&amp;#8217;s Riskier to Not Take Risks&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Brexit hits ability of UK fintech to lure top talent: Report -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/technology/brexit-hits-ability-of-uk-fintech-to-lure-top-talent-report-11358620</link><description>LONDON: Leaving the European Union is making it harder for fintech firms in Britain to recruit top talent, a report said on Tuesday (Mar 19), threatening to slam the brakes on a £7 billion (US$9 billion)growth sector just as EU states step up competition.

The Fuelling Fintech report from TheCityUK ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 16:50:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: Capital One Trains Virtual Assistant Eno To Be Proactive with New Tax Feature -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/03/capital-one-trains-virtual-assistant-eno-to-be-proactive-with-new-tax-feature/</link><description>Most virtual assistants are reactive, but Capital One is training its virtual assistant, Eno, to be proactive, according to Ken Dodelin, VP of conversational AI products at the bank. “Most [virtual assistants] are chasing reactive customer questions,” Dodelin told Bank Innovation. “We are doing some of that, but the biggest update in our plan is [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 16:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IBM Blockchain Blog: How India can capitalize on its demographic dividend through blockchain -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain/2019/03/how-india-can-capitalize-on-its-demographic-dividend-through-blockchain/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;India is known for its demographic dividend which can propel it to become the next China-like story or even better. For those of you who don&amp;#8217;t know, demographic dividend as defined by the United Nations Population Fund means, &amp;#8220;the economic growth potential that can result from shifts in a population’s age structure, mainly when the [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain/2019/03/how-india-can-capitalize-on-its-demographic-dividend-through-blockchain/"&gt;How India can capitalize on its demographic dividend through blockchain&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain"&gt;Blockchain Pulse: IBM Blockchain Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : Norsk Hydro Shuts Plants Amid Ransomware Attack -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/iot/norsk-hydro-shuts-plants-amid-ransomware-attack/d/d-id/1334195?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>The cyberattack, first detected on Monday night, has shut down Norsk's entire global network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:20:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: New JNEC.a Ransomware delivered through WinRAR exploit -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82606/malware/jnec-a-ransomware-winrar.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new strain of ransomware tracked as JNEC.a is spreading through an exploit that triggers the recently discovered vulnerability in WinRAR. The ransomware was involved in the attacks observed by the Qihoo 360 Threat Intelligence Center in the wild, threat actors used an archive named “vk_4221345.rar” that delivers JNEC.a when its contents are extracted with [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82606/malware/jnec-a-ransomware-winrar.html"&gt;New JNEC.a Ransomware delivered through WinRAR exploit&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker News: Mirai Variant Adds Dozen New Exploits to Target Enterprise IoT Devices -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~3/dSdbRwhjUkY/mirai-botnet-enterprise-security.html</link><description>Security researchers have uncovered a new variant of the infamous Mirai Internet of Things botnet, this time targeting embedded devices intended for use within business environments in an attempt to gain control over larger bandwidth to carry out devastating DDoS attacks.

Although the original creators of Mirai botnet have already been arrested and jailed, variants of the infamous IoT malware&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~4/dSdbRwhjUkY" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:55:51 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: New Report Warns 87 Percent of Cryptocurrency Exchange Volume Is Potentially Suspicious -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-report-warns-87-percent-of-cryptocurrency-exchange-volume-is-potentially-suspicious</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xYzE0MTZjZGFlNDEzNjJmZjQ1ZDYxZTlkNTljYWFjOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another report has found highly untrustworthy volume statistics continuing to come from exchanges&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: BitGuards: Why the Crypto Elite Are Increasingly Relying on Personal Security -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitguards-why-the-crypto-elite-are-increasingly-relying-on-personal-security</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9kMWU1ZjUzZjQ3ZmY3YTI0MzMzMzE1ZmMxNTMwMWQ1Yy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto millionaires are hiring bodyguards, but new custodial solutions could make this unnecessary&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Japan to Tighten Rules on Cryptocurrency Margin Trading -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/japan-to-tighten-rules-on-cryptocurrency-margin-trading</link><description>Japan is lowering the limits for cryptocurrency margin trading from next year, and will also mandate registration of platforms offering the service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 10:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Who Makes Money in FinTech? -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16831/who-makes-money-in-fintech?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The world has become more comfortable with the faster pace of financial innovation, with institution...</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 10:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Standard Chartered Just Launched a Fintech Bridge and it’s Exactly What it Sounds Like -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29588/innovation/standard-chartered-sc-ventures-fintech-bridge-proof-of-concept/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;SC Ventures, the investment arm of Standard Chartered Bank, has created a platform to connect community builders such as startups, investors and accelerators. The SC Ventures Fintech Bridge connects and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29588/innovation/standard-chartered-sc-ventures-fintech-bridge-proof-of-concept/"&gt;Standard Chartered Just Launched a Fintech Bridge and it&amp;#8217;s Exactly What it Sounds Like&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 06:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japan Introduces New Regulations for Cryptocurrency Margin Trading -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japan-introduces-new-regulations-for-cryptocurrency-margin-trading</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81OTIzY2YyZmU4M2NhZDAyMzE5MDY2MTE3MjhjZDA3Yi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese financial regulators have reportedly introduced new regulations for cryptocurrency margin trading&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Discount student tickets still available for TC Sessions: Robotics + AI 2019 -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/q2OzNS8tijM/</link><description>Here’s a shout-out to students fascinated by the world of robots and artificial intelligence. There&amp;#8217;s a limited supply of discounted tickets left for TechCrunch Sessions: Robotics + AI, a one-day conference that takes place at UC Berkeley on April 18. Apply now to reserve your $45 student ticket, and spend a full day learning from [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: InstaReM Closes Series C Round, Bringing its Total Funding to US$ 59 Million -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29570/funding/funding-instarem-series-c-ipo-vertex/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Singapore-based InstaReM, a digital cross-border payments company, announced the close of a US$41 million Series C funding round. The company pulled in an additional US$20 million round led by Singapore-based&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29570/funding/funding-instarem-series-c-ipo-vertex/"&gt;InstaReM Closes Series C Round, Bringing its Total Funding to US$ 59 Million&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 04:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Report: Major South Korean Crypto Exchange Bithumb to Lay Off Up to 50% of Staff -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-major-south-korean-crypto-exchange-bithumb-to-lay-off-up-to-50-of-staff</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jYThhYmMzNzA4NDFlOTJlMzQ5MDg0OWQ0NmYxMDc3My5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unconfirmed: major South Korean cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb is reportedly cutting up to 50 percent of its staff&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: IBM debuts blockchain network for cross-border payments -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/ibm-debuts-blockchain-network-for-cross-border-payments/</link><description>Blockchain World Wire can transfer funds in 47 currencies to locations in 72 countries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 09:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: US firm FIS buys Worldpay for US$35 billion in payments deal bonanza -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/us-firm-fis-buys-worldpay-for-us-35-billion-in-payments-deal-bonanza-11355734</link><description>U.S. fintech group Fidelity National Information Services Inc (FIS) has agreed to buy payment processor Worldpay for about US$35 billion, in the biggest deal to date in the booming payments industry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 03:20:32 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Regional banks must merge to meet tech challenges -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/opinion/regional-banks-must-merge-to-meet-tech-challenges</link><description>As competitive pressures mount for midsize banks, more institutions are likely to follow the lead of BB&amp;T-SunTrust and amass more resources for investing in AI, digital platforms and other cutting-edge technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: BitGo Adds Custody Support for Blockchain Capital’s Security Token -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bitgo-adds-custody-support-for-blockchain-capitals-security-token-bcap</link><description>Cryptocurrency custodian BitGo now lets clients compliantly store the BCAP security token from venture capital firm Blockchain Capital.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Cluley: Why real-time intelligence matters for managing third-party risk -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.grahamcluley.com/feed-sponsor-recorded-future-2/</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.grahamcluley.com/feed-sponsor-recorded-future-2/" title="Why real-time intelligence matters for managing third-party risk"&gt;&lt;img width="100" height="100" src="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/recorded-future-esg-thumb-150x150.jpeg" class="attachment-100x100 size-100x100 wp-post-image" alt="Why real-time intelligence matters for managing third-party risk" style="float: right; margin-left: 10px; margin-bottom: 10px;" srcset="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/recorded-future-esg-thumb-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/recorded-future-esg-thumb-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/recorded-future-esg-thumb-45x45.jpeg 45w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/recorded-future-esg-thumb-190x190.jpeg 190w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/recorded-future-esg-thumb.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 100px) 100vw, 100px" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Graham Cluley Security News is sponsored this week by the folks at &lt;strong&gt;Recorded Future&lt;/strong&gt;. Thanks to the great team there for their support!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As leading companies in every industry today are undergoing digital transformation, the lines are blurring between any one organization and its partners, suppliers, vendors, and other third parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this new report, ESG examines how these business relationships can introduce new risks that need to be identified and managed “as if these third parties were part of the enterprise itself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.grahamcluley.com/go/recorded-future-esg/"&gt;Download your copy now of “Third-Party Risk: Why Real-Time Intelligence Matters”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Recorded Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recorded Future delivers the &lt;a href="https://www.recordedfuture.com/"&gt;only complete threat intelligence solution&lt;/a&gt; powered by patented machine learning to lower risk. We empower organizations to reveal unknown threats before they impact business, and enable teams to respond to alerts 10 times faster. To supercharge the efforts of security teams, our technology automatically collects and analyzes intelligence from technical, open web, and dark web sources and aggregates customer-proprietary data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recorded Future delivers more context than threat feeds, updates in real time so intelligence stays relevant, and centralizes information ready for human analysis, collaboration, and integration with security technologies. 91 percent of the Fortune 100 use Recorded Future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’re interested in sponsoring my site for a week, and reaching an IT-savvy audience that cares about computer security, you can &lt;a href="https://www.grahamcluley.com/sponsorship/" title="Sponsorship"&gt;find more information here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Kudelski Security Announces Partnership with Hosho To Secure Blockchain Ecosystems -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/kudelski-security-announces-partnership-with-hosho-to-secure-blockchain-ecosystems/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/kudelski-security-announces-partnership-with-hosho-to-secure-blockchain-ecosystems/"&gt;Kudelski Security Announces Partnership with Hosho To Secure Blockchain Ecosystems&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Clipboard01-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="32260" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/kudelski-security-announces-partnership-with-hosho-to-secure-blockchain-ecosystems/clipboard01-2/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Clipboard01.jpg" data-orig-size="1835,776" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="Clipboard01" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Clipboard01-300x127.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Clipboard01-1024x433.jpg" /&gt;Kudelski Security, the advisor and cybersecurity innovator for today’s most security-conscious organizations, today announced a strategic partnership with Hosho, a global leader in blockchain security and smart contract auditing. The partnership is expected extend the capabilities of Kudelski Security’s recently launched Blockchain Security Center, and makes the companies’ unique skillsets, market-leading services, and proven intellectual property [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/kudelski-security-announces-partnership-with-hosho-to-secure-blockchain-ecosystems/"&gt;Kudelski Security Announces Partnership with Hosho To Secure Blockchain Ecosystems&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 17:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Blockchain Goes Hollywood is Expected to Attract Blockchain and Crypto Experts, Investors and Celebrities to Epic multi-day Event -  Puntaje: 2500</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/blockchain-goes-hollywood-is-expected-to-attract-blockchain-and-crypto-experts-investors-and-celebrities-to-epic-multi-day-event/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/blockchain-goes-hollywood-is-expected-to-attract-blockchain-and-crypto-experts-investors-and-celebrities-to-epic-multi-day-event/"&gt;Blockchain Goes Hollywood is Expected to Attract Blockchain and Crypto Experts, Investors and Celebrities to Epic multi-day Event&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/bitcoin-hollywood-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="311" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2015/10/11/filmfund-io/bitcoin-hollywood/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/bitcoin-hollywood.jpg" data-orig-size="600,233" data-comments-opened="1" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="bitcoin-hollywood" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/bitcoin-hollywood-300x117.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/bitcoin-hollywood.jpg" /&gt;Blockchain Goes Hollywood is inviting people to pack their bags and head over to Los Angeles as the organizers are expecting the event to attract some of the world’s most exciting and innovative Blockchain and cryptocurrency experts, investors and celebrities for exciting multi-day experiences to be held May 30-June 2, 2019, in one of the [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/19/blockchain-goes-hollywood-is-expected-to-attract-blockchain-and-crypto-experts-investors-and-celebrities-to-epic-multi-day-event/"&gt;Blockchain Goes Hollywood is Expected to Attract Blockchain and Crypto Experts, Investors and Celebrities to Epic multi-day Event&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>