<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 11:19:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CoinDesk: How Ethereum Applications Earn A+ Security Ratings -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/how-ethereum-applications-earn-a-security-ratings</link><description>More than 1.2 million ethereum applications have used a little-known security tool from Amberdata to help avoid costly errors from smart contracts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 11:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coinbase Pro Increases Fees, Updates Market Structure ‘to Increase Liquidity’ -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-pro-increases-fees-updates-market-structure-to-increase-liquidity</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lZjJhOTYxNDRkNGY4ZTRiMzVhY2U5OTY0YzE4NTY3My5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new market and fee structure have been announced by major U.S.-based crypto exchange Coinbase for its professional trading platform, Coinbase Pro&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Crypto Investment App Donut Raises $1.8 Million in Seed Funding -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/crypto-investment-app-donut-raises-1-8-million-in-seed-funding</link><description>Crypto investment app startup Donut has raised $1.8 million in a seed funding round as the firm prepares to take its beta product live.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 12:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: Google responds after Trump, Joint Chiefs chairman accuse tech giant of aiding Chinese military -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/google-says-it-works-in-recruiting-cybersecurity-and-healthcare-in-response-to-trump-claim-its-work-benefits-chinese-military</link><description>Google responded Saturday to accusations by President Trump and military officials that its work in China it benefits the Chinese military, saying it was instead working in cybersecurity, recruiting and healthcare.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 04:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Experts uncovered a malspam campaign using Boeing 737 Max crashes -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82500/cyber-crime/spam-boeing-737-max.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Experts at the 360 Threat Intelligence Center uncovered a new malspam campaign that leverages the tragic Boeing 737 Max crash to spread malware. Crooks always attempt to exploit the attention of the people on the events that made the headlines. In the last days, two events captured the attention of the media, the New Zealand [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82500/cyber-crime/spam-boeing-737-max.html"&gt;Experts uncovered a malspam campaign using Boeing 737 Max crashes&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC technology: Courts and police are turning to AI to reduce bias, but some argue it'll make the problem worse -  Puntaje: 1000.0</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/16/artificial-intelligence-algorithms-in-the-criminal-justice-system.html</link><description>Increasingly, algorithms and machine learning are being implemented at various touch points throughout the criminal justice system, from deciding where to deploy police officers to aiding in bail and sentencing decisions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 13:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Security Affairs newsletter Round 205 – News of the week -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82513/breaking-news/security-affairs-newsletter-round-205.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new round of the weekly SecurityAffairs newsletter arrived! The best news of the week with Security Affairs. Kindle Edition Paper Copy Once again thank you! Jackson County paid $400,000 to crooks after ransomare attack Venezuelan Minister declares Venezuelas Blackout may be caused by cyberattack carried by US Crooks use The Pirate Bay to spread [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82513/breaking-news/security-affairs-newsletter-round-205.html"&gt;Security Affairs newsletter Round 205 – News of the week&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 12:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Will 3D printing disrupt the GCC construction sector? -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/real-estate-and-construction/construction/will-3d-printing-disrupt-the-gcc-construction-sector/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_104114849-min-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_104114849-min-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_104114849-min-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;The GCC construction industry has more than 27,000 planned projects in the pipeline which add up to about $2.38 trillion. Saudi Arabia and the UAE account for more than two-thirds - $1.61 trillion - of the planned projects as of late-2018, according to data released by BNC Projects Journal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although these numbers demonstrate strong construction activity, the BNC data for January 2019 showed GCC construction contracts coping with a 39 percent dip in value terms to $13 billion, with $2.7 billion worth of work put on hold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recent Deloitte GCC Powers of Construction 2018 report places the spotlight on the challenges facing the GCC construction sector, calling for faster methods of resolving disputes and alternative delivery models. In such an industry, which is struggling to cope with waste reduction and slow on-site operations, 3D printing is slowly finding the spotlight as a welcome disruption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3D construction taking shape&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 3D printing concrete industry has shown remarkable growth. According to the 2018 Markets and Markets report, the 3D concrete printing market is expected to grow at a compound annual growth rate of 317.3 percent from $0.3 million in 2017 to $1.48 billion in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[caption id="attachment_1381346" align="aligncenter" width="789"] Source: Markets and Markets research report[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The technology, which can 3D print large structures, offers flexibility in construction designs coupled with enhanced sustainability credentials at lower costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elite for Construction and Development Co., a Saudi Arabian construction company is leading the way. It has purchased the BOD2 3D construction printer, which is described as the world's largest, from Danish company COBOD International. The machine will be the first of its kind in Saudi Arabia, COBOD mentioned in a statement. This purchase is expected to help the kingdom meet its Vision 2030 economic mandate of delivering millions of homes. Earlier in March, Saudi Arabia's Ministry of Housing approved a deal permitting a local builder to use 3D-printed concrete for its projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;London-based Ai Build signed an agreement with Dubai-based 3DVinci Creations a week ago, which will see the disruptive technology of large-scale 3D printing expand in the UAE. This hopes to add to Dubai's groundbreaking adoption of 3D printing. The Emirate aims to have 25 percent of its new buildings constructed using 3D printing by 2030. This is expected to also bring down labor costs, promote the use of recycled plastics, and reduce production durations and material waste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3D printing is also helping the construction industry overcome budget overspends, delayed projects, and quality control troubles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/real-estate-and-construction/construction/will-3d-printing-disrupt-the-gcc-construction-sector/"&gt;Will 3D printing disrupt the GCC construction sector?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 13:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>