<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 21:37:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Fortune: Cyber Saturday—Denver Votes on Blockchain, Facebook Password Snafu, ‘LockerGoga’ Ransomware -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://fortune.com/2019/03/23/blockchain-vote-denver-election-blockchain-facebook-password-lockergoga-ransomware/</link><description>Your weekly brief on codemakers and codebreakers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Metamask Browser Extension Default Settings Broadcast ETH Addresses to Visited Websites -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metamask-browser-extension-default-settings-broadcast-eth-addresses-to-visited-websites</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8wMTVlZjc4N2M5NDczOWE4YTZkZjVlZmRlZDVhMDAxYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Users’ Ethereum wallet addresses are reportedly broadcast to all visited websites by leading ETH browser extension Metamask when privacy mode isn’t enabled&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortune: Denver and West Virginia Deserve Praise for Voting on Blockchain -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://fortune.com/2019/03/23/blockchain-vote-election-denver-west-virginia-voatz/</link><description>Paper-based ballots are an outdated technology.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 20:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: How Family Offices aka “muppets on steroids” are writing the future of Fintech &amp; Blockchain &amp; Wealth Management. -  Puntaje: 3600</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/03/23/how-family-offices-aka-muppets-on-steroids-are-writing-the-future-of-fintech-blockchain-wealth-management/</link><description>This is an update to the chapter on investing in The Blockchain Economy digital book. &amp;#8220;Muppets&amp;#8221; is the derogatory term coined by Wall Street for the &amp;#8220;dumb&amp;#8221; retail investors. The people who invested early in Bitcoin and Ethereum are retail in the sense of being individuals and not part of the Legacy Finance world. Yet [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 06:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin Stays Over $4,000 as Top Cryptos See Slight Losses -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-stays-over-4-000-as-top-cryptos-see-slight-losses</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lZmYwZDJiNmRmNWQ4YjUyNzQxNTkwMjFjYzA0MmNkNi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin stays over $4,000 as most of the top 20 cryptocurrencies are reporting slight losses&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Top 5 Crypto Performers Overview: ONT, ADA, ETC, BCH, IOTA -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/top-5-crypto-performers-overview-ont-ada-etc-bch-iota</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yY2FjNGJkZjVlZDVmYTNkM2E0NDBlZDI0NmFlODI4Mi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of this altcoin rally, Cointelegraph’s market analysis covers the top five performers this week with a market cap of more than $500 million&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Satoshi Square: How Bitcoin Took Over a Park (And Then the World) -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/satoshi-square-how-bitcoin-took-over-a-park-and-then-the-world</link><description>Before we knew whether bitcoin was legal or illegal, a group on New Yorkers created an in-person meetup for people to buy, sell and trade the cryptocurrency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 10:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: China’s 11th Crypto Rankings: EOS First, TRON Second, Ethereum Third, Bitcoin Fifteenth -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/chinas-11th-crypto-rankings-eos-first-tron-second-ethereum-third-bitcoin-fifteenth</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xMWNhYjA5N2RjNzBmYmQ1OTgwODE5ZTM3ZGY4NjE0YS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin comes in 15th while EOS keeps its top spot in the recently released Chinese official crypto rankings&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 11:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: How to spend your bitcoin and crypto on eBay items -  Puntaje: 3300</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/how-to-spend-your-bitcoin-and-crypto-on-ebay-items-dd6347b532ec?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h3&gt;How To Spend Your Bitcoin And Crypto On Ebay Items&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buying something on eBay is normal to most people. Now, there are ways to purchase eBay items using bitcoin and other cryptocurrency. Forra has tied eBay listings into its native platform. Allowing anyone to purchase something from eBay using bitcoin other cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You Can View Our Marketplace Here: &lt;a href="https://market.forra.io/"&gt;https://market.forra.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*Q-yq3DzNc1VEGkG6.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How Is It Possible To Buy Something On eBay Using Bitcoin Or Other Cryptocurrency&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://market.forra.io"&gt;Forra&lt;/a&gt; is responsible for allowing users to buy eBay items with bitcoin and other cryptocurrency. We want to develop the tools that allow people to use their cryptocurrency as a currency. We think that by building these tools we will increase the adoption of cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having businesses like eBay accept bitcoin or other cryptocurrency will not happen anytime soon. We charge people the amount of the item, and convert their cryptocurrency to USD for them, in addition to purchasing the item.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ordering on &lt;a href="https://market.forra.io"&gt;Forra&lt;/a&gt; is safe and secure. Your order is processed and delivered via eBay Your item will arrive, and if it does not we will give you a refund.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*fxzZLzWkNqnxP62ow5U9cQ.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How to buy something on eBay using bitcoin&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buying something on eBay using bitcoin is really simple. All you have to do is log on to &lt;a href="https://market.forra.io/"&gt;Market.Forra.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these items that you see for sale are actually eBay listings, meaning that someone who owns an eBay.com account listed them on eBay.com. You are able to make eBay purchases on Forra using bitcoin via an API.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you purchase something with Bitcoin on Forra you will be prompted to pay using our escrow system. Our escrow system will take Will process the entire payment workflow. Our escrow ensures a fair transaction happening between the eBay seller and the person buying the item on eBay using Forra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How to buy something on eBay using cryptocurrency&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buying an item on eBay using cryptocurrency is simple. When you buy an item on eBay using cryptocurrency all you have to do is log in to market.forra.io and buy something with the eBay tag. Items with the eBay tag are pulled from eBay.com itself using an API call.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The purchasing process is fast using &lt;a href="https://forra.io"&gt;Forra&lt;/a&gt;. All it takes is a few seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/310/1*SMPaAXKE1pQPjgNK0rzy6g.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Benefits of spending your cryptocurrency on eBay.com&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is actually cheaper to pay for your items using cryptocurrency. eBay will often be forced to apply taxes on each of their transactions. When you buy an item using cryptocurrency you will often not have to pay any tax. When you make a purchase using Forra we create a tax. This tax is still less than half what you would normally pay. Making it cheaper to use cryptocurrency rather than fiat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How to sell your own items for cryptocurrency&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to start selling your items on Forra as well, you can do so by signing up here: &lt;a href="https://market.forra.io/signup"&gt;market.forra.io/signup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forra is an amazing alternative to selling directly on eBay if you know you want cryptocurrency. We have 0 seller fees or listings fees. When you sell an item using Forra you are guaranteed the full amount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The majority of listings on our platform come from small business owners and individuals looking for an eBay alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people who browse Forra are looking to spend their cryptocurrency on eBay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=dd6347b532ec" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/how-to-spend-your-bitcoin-and-crypto-on-ebay-items-dd6347b532ec"&gt;How to spend your bitcoin and crypto on eBay items&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 12:06:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Comparing three popular wallets. The differences are greater than you might think. -  Puntaje: 19200</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/comparing-three-popular-wallets-the-differences-are-greater-than-you-might-think-bb6652c925de?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/745/0*cJaq4GhkR9Jcl6HV.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wallets are gateways to cryptocurrencies and, as the blockchain space has grown, the variety of wallets available has also grown. Most people who want to dabble with a small amount of crypto, start off their crypto journey by setting up hot wallets in the form of phone, desktop, or web application. Hot wallets focus primarily on convenience and are great for making coin transfers on the go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While hot wallets may be convenient, they force users to sacrifice security and the underlying basis of crypto: having complete control of one’s wealth. Thus, as people get a stronger grasp of blockchain technology and understand how to improve security of their Crypto assets, they either opt for hardware wallets, or even brain wallets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Experience is Important&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given that wallets are gateways to cryptocurrencies, the user experience they provide to new market entrants is of critical importance with respect to the growth of crypto adoption. This piece will take a look at the user experience of several popular wallets. Each section below will cover two main user experiences of a wallet: set-up and performing transactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s a summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Wallets: &lt;/strong&gt;To securely setup a wallet, users must download a brain wallet application from GitHub or use an online tool. Once they’re offline, user can enter a salt and passphrase to generate a wallet (private key). The private key will be exposed and must be immediately stored securely. Brain wallets provide a one-type transactional facility as transacting will expose the private key to some web front. Therefore, any time coins are sent from a brain wallet, a new one has to be made. Brain wallets can be challenging to (securely) set up for those who lack technical know-how and provide close to zero positive UX features in terms of transactions. In addition, for each coin and for each public address of that coin you need to have a separate brain wallet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hardware Wallets: &lt;/strong&gt;Hardware wallets, like Ledger, can be setup by connecting the wallet to a computer device that has downloaded the supporting software of the hardware wallet (like Ledger Live). After that, a pin is set on the hardware device to initiate its functionality. Next, users move along the steps presented in the supporting software till they are prompted to create a 24-word seed phrase that is typically written down somewhere. Once the seed phrase is approved, private keys are created and stored in the hardware wallet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, applications, one for each blockchain, are downloaded on the wallet in order to receive and send transactions. Transactions are initiated on the supporting software, like Ledger Live, and are approved through the hardware wallets’ button-initiated commands. Hardware wallets have a lengthy set-up process, but the process is well-explained by their supporting software. Receiving and sending funds for the first time requires a lengthy process as support for each coin has to be individually set-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitfi: &lt;/strong&gt;A new kind of hardware wallet. To set-up a wallet with Bitfi, users head to the Bitfi Knox Dashboard to synchronize it with the Bitfi device. The process requires users to enter their Bitfi device ID into their Dashboard. Next, user will be prompted to choose a salt and passphrase on the device to create the wallet; no private keys are stored on the device. All coins are automatically supported by Bitfi so users can use the Dashboard at any point to initiate a transaction; the transaction has to be approved on the Bitfi device by signing the transaction with the salt and passphrase (the device will then calculate the corresponding private key).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Deep Dive into Wallet UX&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Wallets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brain wallets, as the name may hint, provide users with memorable means of accessing their Crypto. Leading brain wallet providers like Brainwallet.io let users set-up a wallet in 3 ways:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Generic:&lt;/strong&gt; Users pick a memorable salt and phrase.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal:&lt;/strong&gt; Users can create a wallet that is accessible through personal information.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Login:&lt;/strong&gt; Users create a wallet with the same set of access-points used for account log-in: username and password.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set-up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve decided the memorable &lt;em&gt;keys&lt;/em&gt; to your wallet, you can generate a wallet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/327/1*Q2uZFidHO_rgI7LU7cexfg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Signing up to a brain wallet directly on a webpage, like brainwallet.io, is a mistake.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The point at which the wallet is created, the private key is visible on a web-page, making it accessible to malware. The only proper way of creating a brain wallet is by downloading the source code of a brain wallet generator and running the software offline. This will allow a person to secure the private key. Once the set-up is complete, funds can be sent to the address, but if the wallet is used just for storage, it becomes a cold storage rather than a wallet for transactions, which stands in opposition to the entire functionality of a currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly the brain wallet limits the user to just one public address. For example, let’s say you have 4 Bitcoin addresses, Ethereum, Litecoin, Tron, Stellar, and ten ERC-20 tokens. In this case you will need to create 18 different brain wallets (you will need to memorize 18 different salts and phrases). Therefore a brain wallet is only practical if you wish to store one currency at one address.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transactions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Using the brain wallet for transactions is a challenge.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Setting up a brain wallet on an offline software may be challenging to most people who have become adjusted to the conveniences of the digital age, however, the tech-savvy will breeze through the offline process. Using the wallet, on the other hand, will be a challenge irrespective of one’s technical know-how, and that’s due to the functionality of brain wallets: they are designed for a one-time use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever a transaction has to be made, you’d have to enter the private key on some platform on the internet. This immediately exposes the key and adds vulnerability to the assets that had been protected by that key. Thus, each time BTC (or any other currency) held within a brain wallet has to be transacted, a new brain wallet has to be created to store the BTC that’s not transferred. Therefore, brain wallets are not optimal for transacting BTC or day-to-day use of the cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brain wallets are realistically just a form of storage as transferring coins held within a brain wallet is extremely inefficient. It’s for this reason that brain wallets are not that popular; instead, most people that have become well-acquainted with cryptocurrencies opt for hardware wallets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hardware Wallets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a number of hardware wallets on the market, one of the most popular is Ledger. This hardware wallets is a USB stick dedicated to the storage of private keys and they come with a set of buttons used to feed commands to the device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hardware wallets allow users to store their cryptocurrency on a physical device and these wallets provide a somewhat convenient means for transacting. The drawback, though, is that hardware wallet secure private keys within the physical device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most hardware wallets have a similar set-up process and transaction facility. Here’s a look at the user experience of Ledger Nano X.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set-up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once a user unpacks his or her Ledger, the device has to be configured. Users must head to Ledger’s website and download a software called Ledger Live. Once the software is running, the Ledger wallet has to be connected to a computer to sync it with Ledger Live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/468/1*0nfrXMEaH9nm_Zz5NBinMQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following steps are undertaken for the synchronization:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The buttons provided on the USB stick have to be pressed simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Next, users choose a pin code and then reenter it to confirm the chosen pin.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;After that, users are directed to write and confirm their 24-word seed phrase.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the course of 15 to 20 minutes, users receive their 24 words, note them down on a piece of paper and store them in a secure location. Due to the volume of words, the seed is almost never memorized and users rely on either a household or third-party safety boxes for the security of their seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the seed phrase is collected, the Ledger provides users with a random selection of words and the users must correctly align each of their 24 words. The process can take at least another 15 to 20 minutes. This ensures users did not miss out on a word in case they get the seed confirmation wrong, they can go over the creation of a new seed phrase. If the seed phrase is properly confirmed, the device is ready for app installation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now users begin the app installation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The device is connected to the laptop and Ledger Live verifies the legitimacy of the hardware wallet. Prior to app installation, users are prompted to choose a password to protect their Ledger Live data. Now the device can download applications each of which enables support for different blockchains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/498/1*E-XJQLOyJsCE9zffa1xAVQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once applications (read: support for blockchains) are downloaded, the buttons on the hardware wallet need to be pressed simultaneously for each downloaded application to complete its synchronization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After synchronizing support for each blockchain, users can access public addresses. To receive funds, users connect the hardware wallet and verify the address through the hardware. To verify each address, the two buttons on the hardware wallet must be pressed simultaneously. The addressed for each blockchain needs to be confirmed one by one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/307/1*U-sVl_iBQTt80SSnwwVinA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transactions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make transactions with Ledger, the hardware wallet has to be connected to a computer with a cable which has installed the Ledger Live application. Once the hardware wallet is connected, users will be prompted to enter a pin code to unlock the device functionality. After that, users can access the Bitcoin application from the Live dashboard and select the &lt;em&gt;send&lt;/em&gt; Bitcoin option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After that, a menu is prompted which allows users to select the amount of BTC they want to send, where it should be sent, and the preferred network fee. Once the data has been inputted, the transaction can be sent by confirming all the data on the hardware device through the buttons on the device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summing up, to receive and send any coin the application of the specific coin has to be downloaded on the Ledger Live and then confirmed on the hardware device. At the time of transacting, the hardware device must be connected to a computer with Ledger Live and then the application and the wallet have to be unlocked. After that, transactions can be confirmed through the hardware device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitfi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitfi is a new technology where the hardware never stores private keys (it is the only cryptocurrency wallet that does not store any private keys). Bitfi aims to elevate security beyond cold storage (as there is no storage at all) while also creating a user friendly interface to enable ordinary people to use it quickly and easily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitfi is unlike any hardware wallet or any wallet. It’s a technology that lets users create a wallet that can be accessed through a user selected salt (a salt is just a password but one that you already know like your social security number) and passphrase. The Bitfi device is a private key generator which turns your salt and passphrase into the appropriate private key at the time of transaction and the private keys do not exist in the device at any other time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a way, Bitfi takes advantage of the brain wallet concept but in a very different way because:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;A single salt &amp;amp; phrase will generate private keys for an unlimited number of currencies so as in the above example with brain wallet, instead of having to create 18 different salts &amp;amp; phrases, Bitfi will secure all 18 assets with just a single salt &amp;amp; phrase.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is no downside of the single-use functionality that limits the usage to one transaction. Bitfi creates each transaction in an ultra secure environment and enables frequent payments without the need to store private keys on a physical device that can be lost, stolen, or seized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is no possibility for the private key to leak because it only comes into existence for a fraction of a second to sign the transaction. Otherwise, private keys do not exist on the device or any data whatsoever.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the device ID is entered, a notification is instantly delivered to the Bitfi device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After that, users are asked to enter their chosen salt and passphrase; both of these can be memorized (although you don’t have to and this is optional). The device will require that you reenter the salt and passphrase to ensure it was properly entered. A wallet is now created but no private keys will be stored within the device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set-up is complete.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transactions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Bitfi devices innately tracks the value of all cryptocurrencies and digital assets stored within it. The device generates wallets for all supported cryptocurrencies at once, there isn’t a need to generate wallets for each blockchain one by one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the Dashboard and the Bitfi device will provide access to public addresses for all supported cryptocurrencies. These can be used to receive coins and tokens. All assets including ERC-20 tokens, are automatically tracked by the Bitfi device. ERC-20 assets are added in mere seconds by simply entering the contract address of the token.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/171/1*xztaaTG4UF__IXMcEF7tbg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sending coins requires approval from the Bitfi device. From the Dahboard, users can access the wallets associated with various coins. Once a wallet is open, users can click the &lt;em&gt;send&lt;/em&gt; option to initiate a transfer. When a transfer is initiated, users are asked to provide the target address, amount to be sent, and the preferred network fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/196/1*quqwv_uVmDqnkXcXkLcQCQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the &lt;em&gt;send request&lt;/em&gt; button is clicked, the Bitfi device will instantly receive a pop-up asking user to authorize the transaction by entering their salt and passphrase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The transfer is complete.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=bb6652c925de" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/comparing-three-popular-wallets-the-differences-are-greater-than-you-might-think-bb6652c925de"&gt;Comparing three popular wallets. The differences are greater than you might think.&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Exclusive: EU to drop threat of Huawei ban but wants 5G risks monitored - sources -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/exclusive--eu-to-drop-threat-of-huawei-ban-but-wants-5g-risks-monitored---sources-11371674</link><description>The European Commission will next week urge EU countries to share more data to tackle cybersecurity risks related to 5G networks but will ignore U.S. calls to ban Huawei Technologies, four people familiar with the matter said on Friday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 04:06:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Google Pay to enter wealth management services with 'Gold Account' -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/google-pay-to-enter-wealth-management-services-with-gold-account-119032300083_1.html</link><description>Move marks the tech giant's entry into wealth management space in India</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 02:33:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: How to Solve Talent Shortage in Data Science Jobs -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/how-to-solve-talent-shortage-in-data-science-jobs-51a4e45ce9a7?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*z_8tiXSzygrOwlWXC0wxUw.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent years have brought an explosion of data science jobs, and the demand is on the rise. Data analysts, data miners, Big Data scientists, and more similar job titles populate online job boards now. This is a new domain, and very few people, if any, occupying these positions have an academic qualification in this exact field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most data scientists come from other jobs or entirely different career paths. Some of them were engineers; others were programmers, statisticians or mathematicians. Mostly any job which required a solid understanding of logic and statistics can act as a launching point for a career in data science. Here is an outlook on a few trends identified, proposed and analyzed by the likes of &lt;a href="https://www.pwc.com/us/en/library/data-science-and-analytics.html"&gt;PwC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2018/07/16/how-will-data-science-evolve-over-the-next-decade/#51b1503a254e"&gt;Forbes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://indatalabs.com/"&gt;InData Labs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Call for Specialists and Fierce Competition&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As most companies are shifting toward a data-driven approach, there is a higher demand for data scientists, either for in-house development or for software providers offering SaaS products. There is a definite scarcity of these specialists; they need to have a rare combination of skills and a multidisciplinary thinking which has not been encouraged by most corporate environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some companies are already ahead of the game and have attracted and trained top talent from around the world, newcomers to this industry will have a hard time sourcing the right people, and this will come at a very high cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate for these jobs is what Tim Brown of IDEO calls a T-shaped individual. This means a person who has a vast experience in a niche subject, but enough curiosity and personal skills to integrate that in a broader context. They are gurus in their area of know-how but are well-read and inquisitive so that they can work with others and create value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies recruiting for data science jobs should be prepared to wait until they fill these positions for longer than when they are filling more general roles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Entrepreneurial Mindset In a Corporate Environment&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reason why candidates for data science jobs are hard to find in a typical corporate environment is that this multidisciplinary approach is more characteristic to entrepreneurs. They need to connect the dots, come up with ideas which have not been tested before and innovate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior experience in number-dominated fields helps but is not enough. Also, the best results are achieved by those who have an inquisitive approach to problem-solving, instead of just using the beaten track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attracting or growing such talent will be a challenge for most organizations, as these people are more set to create their startups instead of spending time on common office jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As data-centered skills are in demand, the academic world is catching up and designing data science programs. When these get traction, it will be presumably easier to grow such specialists, but for the next years, the dominant strategy will be to convert specialists from other related fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Growing Into the Role&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it’s almost impossible to find the right candidate on the market, some companies will have to resort to recruiting from within the organization and help such hires to develop the necessary abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The initial requirements for education are quite high. All data science jobs require a B.Sc. in Engineering, Mathematics or related fields. Some positions may even require skills associated with Ph.D.-level studies. Good news is that these skills can be trained, and knowing the internal workflows and problems helps once a solid computational base is set.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when preparing your HR budgets for the next year, set aside a consistent amount for continuous education and training of your in-house data scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Migration from Academia&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The set of analytical skills required by data science jobs is usually found in people who have already completed academic degrees. Therefore, it is reasonable to expect to see a migration of the workforce from academia to the business world, also driven by higher pay rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only problem of these latecomers, compared to their peers from engineering or other applied fields, is that some of them miss the contact with real-world issues and business context specifically. However, as such hires have the framework in place, they will get used to the nature of data tasks set by their corporate employers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;More Job Titles&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world of job titles is confusing right now since many organizations tend to use titles as a way of employee gratification. It is not unusual to see employees in mid-level positions called VP just to give them an ego boost instead of a financial one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the world of data science, it gets more confusing due to the novelty of the job requirements. It is not uncommon to call a data scientist any of the following roles: those who perform SQL queries, data cleaners, machine learning roles (from architects to testers) and researchers. As you can imagine, each of these is, in fact, a separate job. However, until now these roles were not distinctive enough to get a title on their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As data science makes its leaps into the future, there will be less demarcation between data scientists per se and other roles, such as product managers. This already happens in companies like Quora, which are at the forefront of online innovation when it comes to data applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No talk about the future of data science jobs is complete without mentioning the impact on other jobs. As automation scale and pace increase, data scientists are like to put others out of their jobs. Although there will be no shortage of work in the future, there will be some imbalance between highly skilled positions and the low-end of the working spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=51a4e45ce9a7" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/how-to-solve-talent-shortage-in-data-science-jobs-51a4e45ce9a7"&gt;How to Solve Talent Shortage in Data Science Jobs&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 12:28:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cooperativa tecnología: El final que propone la IA para la sinfonía inconclusa de Schubert -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.cooperativa.cl/noticias/tecnologia/industria/telefonia-movil/el-final-que-propone-la-ia-para-la-sinfonia-inconclusa-de-schubert/2019-03-23/121202.html</link><description>En un evento realizado en México, la Orquesta Filarmónica de las Américas interpretó los dos últimos movimientos de la "Unfinished Symphony" de Schubert, logrados en base a la inteligencia artificial del Huawei Mate 20 Pro.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 15:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Planning for the uncertain future of work -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Y_uiVBTXwvA/</link><description>In a recently published, roughly 75-page report, British non-profit organization The Royal Society for the Encouragement of Arts (RSA) outlined several scenarios for how the UK labor market will be impacted by frontier technologies such as automation, AI, AVs and more. The analysis titled “The Four Futures of Work” was conducted in collaboration with design [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 17:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: WTF is Cuckoo Cycle PoW algorithm that attract projects like Cortex and Grin? -  Puntaje: 3000</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/wtf-is-cuckoo-cycle-pow-algorithm-that-attract-projects-like-cortex-and-grin-ad1ff96effa9?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WTF is Cuckoo Cycle PoW algorithm that attract projects like Grin and Cortex?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;In 2017, the cryptocurrency rage reached to the highest point when Bitcoin surged to USD19,783, many speculators and miners started to invest an enormous amount of money into mining hardware and chips hoping to get on the craze. Cryptocurrency mining was originally designed to be doable with general-purpose computers. Yet with the increase in competition to the limited resources, miners have been seeking an effective way to improve their chances.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application-specific integrated circuit chips&lt;/strong&gt;, known as ASIC, has taken over the mining market since. ASIC are chips that are designed with a singular purpose. For cryptocurrency mining, these chips are built into specifically designed motherboards and power supplies to efficiently &lt;em&gt;solve a specific algorithm&lt;/em&gt;. Each cryptocurrency has its own cryptographic hash algorithm and ASIC hardware are designed to excel at calculating that algorithm, in the case of Bitcoin, ASIC hardware is designed to calculate the SHA-256 hash algorithm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, in 2018, the bearish performance in the cryptocurrency market has put them in a difficult situation. Though with better performance comparing the general-purpose computer using GPU or CPU cards, there is a limited room of adjustment for the ASIC hardware. ASIC miners were seeking ways to deal with their machines and spaces they rent for running the mining machines. In contrast, GPU miners can easily adapt to new PoW algorithms and tokens due to better compatibility with different hash algorithms (in the cost of performance). Furthermore, the emerging of Cuckoo Cycle algorithm sheds light on the GPU mining to compete against the ASIC miners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Cuckoo Cycle PoW algorithm?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/412/1*y9-rz5yuvrYeQMhyFChocg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cuckoo cycle&lt;/strong&gt; is one of the most promising &lt;em&gt;ASIC-resistant&lt;/em&gt; PoW algorithm created by Dutch computer scientist, John Tromp. Cuckoo cycle was originally applied as a measure to prevent email spams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;The email sender has to perform a certain amount of work that consumes computational power to prove that he does have the need to send out the email to the recipient.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, with its unique design, it sees fit for GPU mining. It focuses more on memory use, meaning the solution time is bound to memory bandwidth rather than the raw processor or GPU speed. Unlike other PoW algorithms that requires maxing out the capacity of your hardware that drains a lot of power which produces heat (which is why most mining factories are located in colder locations/or locations with cheap electricity that can turn A/C on 24/7), a memory-bound algorithm like Cuckoo cycle require far less energy than most other GPU, CPU or ASIC-bound PoW algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most up-to-date implementations and findings can be found on his &lt;a href="https://github.com/tromp/cuckoo"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difference between the Cuckoo Cycle PoW algorithm and the SHA256 used by Bitcoin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The SHA256 used by Bitcoin is a simple and pure hash function. The computational process of the solution is easily migratable from the CPU to GPU, FPGA, and ASIC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/539/1*2uyKtECG_P2qZqq1-RYVbg.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The above picture is an 8-node, 4-sided Cuckoo Cycle bipartite graph&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cuckoo Cycle is a graph theory-based algorithm. It tries to find a fixed length L ring in the Cuckoo Cycle bipartite graph randomly generated by Siphash. As the scale of the graph increases, the L value increases and becomes more difficult to find a ring that fits the length of L. Solving the solution (i.e., the process of finding a loop) itself requires a relatively large amount of memory to store the sorting of data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cuckoo Cycle algorithm is &lt;em&gt;resisted&lt;/em&gt; to ASIC chips. The difficulty and cost to make Cuckoo Cycle compatible on ASIC are much higher than the SHA256 of Bitcoin. It is possible to reduce the anti-ASIC capability by deformation and become an ASIC-friendly algorithm, but it is also possible to further improve its ASIC resistance through deformation as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, &lt;strong&gt;CuckAToo algorithm&lt;/strong&gt; simplifies and discards the binary end of nodes in the bipartite graph which greatly reduce the difficulty of the solution. However, if all the nodes in the bipartite graph are grouped where all the nodes in the group have mutually dependent relationships, it is necessary to calculate the hash of all the nodes in the group. The difficulty of the solution and the requirements for data cache are then greatly increased. This transformation of Cuckoo Cycle is called &lt;strong&gt;CuckARoo algorithm&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects using the Cuckoo Cycle algorithm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the official Cuckoo Cycle &lt;a href="https://github.com/tromp/cuckoo"&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; page, a list of projects using this algorithm was announced including AE, Grin, and Cortex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*yK6azs_n3Zj6uD_JYOFHtg.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The list of projects using Cuckoo Cycle on GitHub&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aeternity.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, also known as &lt;strong&gt;æternity&lt;/strong&gt;, is a new blockchain technology, designed to deliver unmatched efficiency, transparent governance, and global scalability. &lt;a href="https://github.com/aeternity/aeternity/releases"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Minerva Mainnet upgrade&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;(2.0.0) was released a couple weeks ago. AE has a total of 254,396,431 AE and aims to boost 1,000 TPS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://grin-tech.org/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is currently live with its &lt;a href="https://github.com/mimblewimble/grin"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;mainnet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Grin uses the Mimblewimble protocol to improve scalability and privacy. It empowers anyone to transact or save modern money without the fear of external control or oppression. Grin is designed for the decades to come, not just tomorrow. Grin wants to be usable by everyone, regardless of borders, culture, skills or access. Grin does not have circulating limit, which means that there is no limit on the total amount, and 60 Grins are mined per minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cortexlabs.ai/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cortex&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is building something unique and original. Cortex aims to create a decentralized AI autonomous system that continues to expand the performance boundaries of smart contracts, allowing smart contracts to be actually smart with AI algorithms. In Cortex’s AI on Blockchain ecosystem, AI model developers, AI DApp developers, miners, and users can be linked together through public blockchain to create more AI DApps with real-world use cases. It also help stimulating more high-quality AI models to open source through the tokenomic model and incentive mechanism, which helps to democratize AI research which often led to concentrations of power and money. This is a new AI on Blockchain ecosystem that is independently governed by AI smart contracts. Cortex follows the four-year halving mechanism of Bitcoin. The total amount of CTXC mined through PoW is 150 million, and the first four years yields 75 million, which is halved every four years. Currently, the &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/cortex-testnet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TestNet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is live and the&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/digital-clash"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;first AI DApp&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grin and Cortex&amp;#39;s take on ASIC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Grin&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://grin-tech.org/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; uses CuckARoo (anti-ASIC) and CuckAToo (ASIC-friendly) algorithms in parallel where 90% of Grin is mined by ASIC-resistant CuckARoo and 10% of Grin is mined by ASIC-friendly CuckAToo. This ratio will be adjusted every six months to the point that will fully adopt ASIC-friendly CuckAToo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Cortex&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, &lt;a href="https://www.cortexlabs.ai/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cortex’s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; goal is to try to establish an environment where any AI equipment or conventional hardware already owned by everyone to be able to mine. Based on this goal, anti-ASIC is a firm belief in Cortex. The reason for this is that Cortex hopes to allow the mining machine investors in the Cortex ecosystem to have better general-purpose computing capabilities and lay the foundation for the future large-scale AI computing demand market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cortex has released a full version of the &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/cortex-testnet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TestNet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; which is already using a version of Cuckoo Cycle for consensus mechanism. The AI smart contract feature has also been deployed. The first fully available &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/digital-clash"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI DApp&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has been created on the TestNet. The development progress of the MainNet is working in progress according to the roadmap, which will be launched in Q2 of 2019. The launched of Cortex MainNet will bring a new wave of not just to AI developers and DApp developers but also to GPU miners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*oj_JHnbpqJzSdglXRNyRZg.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The first AI DApp on the Cortex TestNet&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cuckoo Cycle is the newly emerging Proof-of-Work algorithm adopt by many projects to establish a friendly mining environment. It generates random bipartite graphs from a provided message and tries to find whether a subgraph with required property exists or not. Different projects have their objectives using Cuckoo Cycle. The algorithm itself has a relatively high anti-ASIC capability and can be modified into other algorithms to adjust the anti-ASIC capability. For Grin, Cuckoo Cycle was used to &lt;em&gt;mitigate against&lt;/em&gt; the Bitcoin-style “hardware arms-race” by making it ASIC resistant. For Cortex, it is to &lt;em&gt;lower&lt;/em&gt; the mining requirements to lay the foundation for future scalability in AI computing demand market. Cukoo Cycle and GPU mining will lead us to a better mining environment where anyone can be a part of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=ad1ff96effa9" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/wtf-is-cuckoo-cycle-pow-algorithm-that-attract-projects-like-cortex-and-grin-ad1ff96effa9"&gt;WTF is Cuckoo Cycle PoW algorithm that attract projects like Cortex and Grin?&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 09:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cooperativa tecnología: Inteligencia Artificial finalizó sinfonía inconclusa de Schubert -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.cooperativa.cl/noticias/tecnologia/industria/telefonia-movil/inteligencia-artificial-finalizo-sinfonia-inconclusa-de-schubert/2019-03-23/112530.html</link><description>El teléfono Huawei Mate 20 Pro se basó en la original para generar el tercer y cuarto movimiento. La clave estuvo en su potente procesador Kirin 980 y su NPU Dual.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 01:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: The Crypto ‘Trichotomy’ -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/the-crypto-trichotomy</link><description>The crypto space has split into three different areas, and the term “crypto” no longer applies to all of them, argues Tim Enneking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 11:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: UPS Targets B2B Sales With New Blockchain E-Commerce Platform -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/ups-targets-business-sales-with-new-blockchain-e-commerce-platform</link><description>U.S.-based shipping giant UPS has announced a new blockchain integration aimed to bring business-to-business sales into the digital age.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 12:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Binance, HitBTC, etc., Market Maker Pitch: How To Get Rich Online -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/binance-hitbtc-etc-market-maker-pitch-how-to-get-rich-online-2988c1d328ac?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h3&gt;Cheap VPS&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://techvoices.club"&gt;http://techvoices.club&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;press ‘all’ after about 15s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Case in Point&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine this hourly graph without the steep drops from paying fees on the green (buy) lines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*WmxjLMNzSEUeuSlgJu_VCg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a follow-up to this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/making-markets-moving-crypto-free-and-open-source-binance-9bcea607e57b"&gt;https://hackernoon.com/making-markets-moving-crypto-free-and-open-source-binance-9bcea607e57b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/privateMarketMakerRepo"&gt;https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/privateMarketMakerRepo&lt;/a&gt; ** ask for access **&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TL;DR join us here &lt;a href="https://t.me/themarketmakerbot"&gt;https://t.me/themarketmakerbot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Elevator Pitch&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market making on Deribit and BitMex failed because it counted on the market to remain more or less stagnant on the 0.25$ step. We’re now looking at automating two market making strategies for smaller volume, higher spread pairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Market Maker Trader&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We buy just above the highest bid and sell just below the lowest ask. We repeat this process, using a fraction of account balance in base pairs, until we see the net profits as price fluctuations cancel each other out in the approaching infinity sense — while we soak up profits from the spread itself in the ‘relative orders’ strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversationally, and not coded yet, is the ‘staggered order’ strategy, where you pick a maximum and minimum price for that pair and then stagger orders up and down the order book to buy and sell along set intervals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resources: Would need servers close to different exchanges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scalability: More coins; more scale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pros: I’ve had 0.57 bitcoin volume on my deposit of $18 worth of coins on the ‘relative’ strategy in the last 24 hours, while sustaining about -0.5% growth. There are other exchanges (some with margin) where we can reproduce the bot, like bitfinex/ethfinex who have a market maker rebate paid monthly in their proprietary coin, or liquid who has a market maker rebate on pairs that were previously on qryptos&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add’l pros: on Binance I can effect a 20% or 40% income on fees via my referral link, on HitBTC the affiliate program is on pause but I may eventually be able to effect 75% — although the potential gains from HitBTC affiliate are less as there will eventually be a 0% or rebate on the maker fees&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cons: To prove profitable on Binance or HitBTC, you’d need to eliminate the fees or effect a market maker rebate. On Binance this involves volume as well as holding BNB — while still paying some fees, while on HitBTC that only involves building volume first — effecting 0% maker fees then 0.01% rebate. &lt;a href="https://hitbtc.com/fee-tier"&gt;https://hitbtc.com/fee-tier&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.binance.com/en/fee/schedule"&gt;https://www.binance.com/en/fee/schedule&lt;/a&gt; On HitBTC there’s also a market making program &lt;a href="https://hitbtc.com/mm"&gt;https://hitbtc.com/mm&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;To Prove for Viability&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Consistent over all types of markets, but identify when it does better&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run, price volatility helps the ‘staggered’ strategy more than it does the ‘relative’ strategy&lt;br&gt;Less volatility but still having volume, there will be gains from the ‘relative’ strategy&lt;br&gt;The potential loss is 1. Fees 2. Grabbing a coin that immediately dies, inclusive.&lt;br&gt;If you’re to eliminate fees or effect a fee rebate, this risk goes down&lt;br&gt;If you automate many pairs you lessen the negative effect of grabbing a coin that dies&lt;br&gt;Conversationally, a stop loss can be created to further lessen this risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Sunk costs of development&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;None — need to code the ‘staggered’ strategy, which I can do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Scalability given current market liquidity and volume&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;On exchanges like Binance or HitBTC, with many coin pairs that have significant volume, we can scale indefinitely&lt;br&gt;The bot currently checks the average volume per base asset, then the spread of a given pair, and enters only into those markets that meet the minimum and maximum volumes and target spread, as well as a minimum order quantity and maximum order quantity (to avoid sh#tcoins)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In base: market pair: volume in base, that looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;{ BTC: { XDNBTC: 69.3393775486, VETBTC: 42.606415325 },&lt;br&gt; TUSD: { NXTUSD: 67247.7248096, TNTUSD: 53891.073732 },&lt;br&gt; MUSD: { QTUMUSD: 2545776.043225 },&lt;br&gt; NUSD: { XDNUSD: 280614.7629689 },&lt;br&gt; DUSD: { MAIDUSD: 54019.8292817 },&lt;br&gt; ETH:&lt;br&gt; { ICXETH: 589.145211656,&lt;br&gt; NXTETH: 266.992269315,&lt;br&gt; REPETH: 616.456689351,&lt;br&gt; ONTETH: 5359.788369161,&lt;br&gt; NTKETH: 197.416308344,&lt;br&gt; KBCETH: 355.311810444,&lt;br&gt; ROXETH: 311.845628547 },&lt;br&gt; BUSD: { DGBUSD: 2445.14526651 },&lt;br&gt; GUSD: { BTGUSD: 141765.29622322 },&lt;br&gt; UUSD: { QNTUUSD: 29.4731369 },&lt;br&gt; PUSD: { ETPUSD: 68.5015549, ZAPUSD: 40.1461164 },&lt;br&gt; YUSD: { DAYUSD: 338.8757426, BERRYUSD: 248.9052084 },&lt;br&gt; QUSD: { STQUSD: 6039.7474451 },&lt;br&gt; IUSD: { WIKIUSD: 10575.2656811 },&lt;br&gt; FUSD: { ELFUSD: 14.04120135 },&lt;br&gt; URS:&lt;br&gt; { ETHEURS: 2486.24206583,&lt;br&gt; LTCEURS: 1485.789705,&lt;br&gt; XMREURS: 2807.0239136 },&lt;br&gt; ‘0USD’: { POA20USD: 20.1087685 },&lt;br&gt; EOS: { LSKEOS: 39.06901764 },&lt;br&gt; RWB: { BTCKRWB: 44.82036 } }&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Forward Tests&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This strategy was first coded about 48 hours ago on Binance. It lost about 0.5% in one day, and had 0.46 BTC in volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FqEyq1ZB&amp;amp;src=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FqEyq1ZB%2Fembed%3Fpub%3Dtrue%26ref%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fembed.ly%26w%3D607&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;schema=imgur" width="607" height="364" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/b998ee17f9822e2470a3fcd3a21577e1/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/b998ee17f9822e2470a3fcd3a21577e1/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second iteration was on HitBTC, and as of about 10–12 hours ago has 0.12 BTC in volume (across many smaller orders, instead of the test version on Binance risking everything on one pair).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FU6p4pX6&amp;amp;src=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FU6p4pX6%2Fembed%3Fpub%3Dtrue%26ref%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fembed.ly%26w%3D500&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;schema=imgur" width="500" height="339" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/2a92a3ba02b0430036a88d80ce856f22/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/2a92a3ba02b0430036a88d80ce856f22/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s lost about 0.23% in that time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FxEk6xe4&amp;amp;src=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FxEk6xe4%2Fembed%3Fpub%3Dtrue%26ref%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fembed.ly%26w%3D598&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;schema=imgur" width="598" height="335" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/fcaee3f63ecb646cb972d2c362465b0c/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/fcaee3f63ecb646cb972d2c362465b0c/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;p&gt;My calculations, based on losing 0.5% a day on average with entry level fees and based on HitBTC’s 0% maker fee after 1500BTC in 30-day volume, indicate that after a certain amount of time while trading a certain balance we can effect 0% fees, and therein effect profits:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FHFQjgl0&amp;amp;src=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2FHFQjgl0%2Fembed%3Fpub%3Dtrue%26ref%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fembed.ly%26w%3D616&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;schema=imgur" width="616" height="303" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/0db9bcb29e02b6038f6f53317921da66/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/0db9bcb29e02b6038f6f53317921da66/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not including the chance we can get market maker benefits or the 0.01% &lt;br&gt;rebate after 6000 BTC volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2F80ifssM&amp;amp;src=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2F80ifssM%2Fembed%3Fpub%3Dtrue%26ref%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fembed.ly%26w%3D500&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;schema=imgur" width="500" height="599" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/003fad58768ac02ee74d9c3b11481d5c/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/003fad58768ac02ee74d9c3b11481d5c/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2Fo5mpKYc&amp;amp;src=https%3A%2F%2Fimgur.com%2Fo5mpKYc%2Fembed%3Fpub%3Dtrue%26ref%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fembed.ly%26w%3D500&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;schema=imgur" width="500" height="639" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/730d56d181ba690652f2fc2fc7f5afe6/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/730d56d181ba690652f2fc2fc7f5afe6/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;With enough volume anything is possible. Come join us! &lt;a href="https://t.me/themarketmakerbot"&gt;https://t.me/themarketmakerbot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=2988c1d328ac" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/binance-hitbtc-etc-market-maker-pitch-how-to-get-rich-online-2988c1d328ac"&gt;Binance, HitBTC, etc., Market Maker Pitch: How To Get Rich Online&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 16:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: India: Police Arrest Four More Suspects in Alleged $14 Million Crypto Scam -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/india-police-arrest-four-more-suspects-in-alleged-14-million-crypto-scam</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hYzNkN2Q5NjU0YzcxNzU5ZjQyOWQ0NmE2MjdiOGIwMy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A cryptocurrency scam that amassed nearly $17 million has led to the arrest of four more suspects by law enforcement in Mumbai&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: 4 Signals That Explain How Businesses Are Adopting Blockchain -  Puntaje: 4800</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/4-signals-that-explain-how-businesses-are-adopting-blockchain-7204ba901140?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*_8NOZVqpSrg2mxgAKvzvvw.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;a href="https://provide.services/state-of-enterprise-blockchain-study-report/"&gt;State of the Enterprise Blockchain Study&lt;/a&gt; contains some key signals to how business is adopting blockchain technology. These signals identify its progress, but also highlight the best inroads to working with enterprises and the work the industry needs to complete to build on the progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. More best practices are needed.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*8zm9u5p5dtXbK-ZILxQvGA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;While 75% of respondents agreed that blockchain will be mainstream technology by 2025, enterprises—especially large ones—are still waiting for patterns of success before opening their wallets. 62% cite a lack of tooling and internal skills as roadblocks to adoption. 50% need further proof in the form of use cases or pre-built solutions to develop their blockchain business case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, blockchain is still too hard to learn for busy IT shops running at scale, and too poorly understood to justify projects. To change that, tooling to simplify interactions with blockchain solutions needs to become more prevalent and more turn-key solutions with publicly proven benefits need to emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Full disclosure:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; I work for Provide Technologies, whose mission is to make blockchain developers more productive through &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://provide.services"&gt;&lt;em&gt;platform development&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and turn-key solutions like &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://providepayments.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;providepayments.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Early adopters are most likely small, privately owned organizations.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*2QQsYGBVn_o2E9ji0o_NSA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the nearly $9M spent last year on blockchain projects by respondents, 82% came from organizations with less than 99 employees. 70% of that investment poured in from privately owned companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a typical adoption pattern for new technologies. Smaller companies often possess a stronger appetite for risk—seeking competitive differentiators more aggressively to win customers or establish new markets. Larger companies wait until concrete patterns emerge that save time, money or attract new customers. Then with deeper pockets and larger resource pools, large enterprises catch up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This pattern is likely to exist for a couple years before the balance normalizes. For the next five years, small company blockchain budgets will continue to outpace the larger enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Blockchain starts with IT.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*ys9MgfyUIua-Y_e3hstGag.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, blockchain is a technology, so it makes sense that IT directs the majority of its adoption today. If the decision is clearly cut from either business or technology teams, it is 40% more likely that IT initiates the project. In fact, it appears that IT is central to blockchain projects getting started. 75% of the time, technology teams are either initiating or partnering with the business as the driving force behind blockchain adoption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Business teams still participate in over half of the decisions to use blockchain, but the gap in participation underscores that business executives struggle to identify (and justify) business use cases for blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or maybe they do envision what their markets look like after decentralization, and they are resisting the change. That is a dangerous view, though. Remember, it only took Netflix three years to drive Blockbuster to bankruptcy by embracing Web 2.0. Decentralization is at the core of the &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@matteozago/why-the-web-3-0-matters-and-you-should-know-about-it-a5851d63c949"&gt;Web 3.0 evolution&lt;/a&gt; underway today, and—&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/how-blockchain-is-eating-the-world-82ca87d26429"&gt;as I outlined in a previous post&lt;/a&gt;—even Netflix isn’t safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regardless, decentralization is still a very technical discussion, and technology companies and partners would better serve future projects by providing technology teams with the tools to be their blockchain champions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. It’s a polychain world.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*jvB38RH-1Do-JzBVRDp3TA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not surprisingly, Ethereum leads the market for enterprise adoption. 62% base their blockchain projects on &lt;a href="https://www.ethereum.org/"&gt;Ethereum&lt;/a&gt;, the protocol designed for developers — allowing them to put business logic on chain using smart contracts. A respectable 42% use the &lt;a href="https://bitcoin.org/"&gt;Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt; network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the really impressive number is 78% of the respondents reported supporting projects for two or more chains. Certainly, many of these projects involve accepting cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it is logical that while technologists work out best practices, and software providers craft turn-key solutions, many chains will root themselves in niches and prosper. Similar to how companies already rely on several relational databases to power facets of their business, we should expect to see chains to follow a similar pattern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;About the State of the Enterprise Blockchain Study&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study sampled the current state of blockchain adoption for 82 organizations ranging in size from startups to juggernauts. The median size company employs 250 people, while the mean employs closer to 30,000. The study started began in December 2018 and concludes with &lt;a href="https://provide.services/state-of-enterprise-blockchain-study-report/"&gt;this report&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://provide.services/"&gt;Provide Technologies&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.emory.edu/home/index.html"&gt;Emory University&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.aprio.com/"&gt;Aprio&lt;/a&gt; sponsored the State of the Enterprise Blockchain Study. Special thanks to &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/benn-konsynski-2a4b001/"&gt;Dr. Benn Konsynski&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jagruti-solanki-11825810/"&gt;Jagruti Solanki&lt;/a&gt; for their help in completing this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*-7QXxfs-JcWjiw_gAMwomg.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Source: &lt;a href="https://provide.services/state-of-enterprise-blockchain-study-report/"&gt;State of the Enterprise Blockchain Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=7204ba901140" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/4-signals-that-explain-how-businesses-are-adopting-blockchain-7204ba901140"&gt;4 Signals That Explain How Businesses Are Adopting Blockchain&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 06:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>