<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 11:23:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cointelegraph: Ex-NATO Secretary General Bullish on Blockchain as He Partners With Swiss Startup -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ex-nato-secretary-general-bullish-on-blockchain-as-he-partners-with-swiss-startup</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yZmRmMzdlYzA0MTVmMTQyYzkzZjY2MzViYTdhOGE5Ni5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiss blockchain startup will get expertise sharing from three-time Danish prime minister Anders Fogh Rasmussen&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Ex-NATO Chief, Danish PM Now Advises Blockchain Firm Concordium -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/ex-nato-chief-danish-pm-now-advises-blockchain-firm-concordium</link><description>A former prime minister of Denmark and secretary-general of NATO has joined blockchain identity startup Concordium as a strategic advisor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 09:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Australia unveils national blockchain strategy -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33568/australia-unveils-national-blockchain-strategy?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Australian government has launched a national blockchain plan which it hopes will bolster its fi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 10:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Lightning Labs Releases Alpha Version of Lightning Offramp Solution Lightning Loop -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/lightning-labs-releases-alpha-version-of-lightning-offramp-solution-lightning-loop</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lNmQ2NzIzNDY3ZmRlYTRmN2Q4OGRjZDBlNmRhN2MzYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The initial release of Lightning Network offramp Lightning Loop has been announced by blockchain development company Lightning Labs&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Sirin Labs, MyEtherWallet Team Up for Finney Phone Integration -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/sirin-labs-myetherwallet-team-up-for-finney-phone-integration</link><description>Sirin Labs, developer of the Finney blockchain phone, has teamed up with MyEtherWallet for an integration aimed to benefit both companies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: WSJ Claim of $9 Mln Laundered Via Shapeshift Based on Flawed Investigation, Analysts Say -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/wsj-claim-of-9-mln-laundered-via-shapeshift-based-on-flawed-investigation-analysts-say</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85ODYxNmU2Yzk4MDI1MDkxNzBiYTM0Zjc3NTQ3ZmUyNi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysts have accused the Wall Street Journal of using flawed investigative methods and grossly overestimating the extent of alleged laundering via crypto exchange ShapeShift&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Crypto Market Maker B2C2 Hires Wall Street FX Vet to Lead US Expansion -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/crypto-market-maker-b2c2-hires-wall-street-fx-vet-to-lead-us-expansion</link><description>London-based crypto liquidity provider B2C2 has hired Wall Street veteran Rob Catalanello to lead its expansion in the U.S.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 11:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Cryptocurrency Price Correlations in Bitcoin, Dollar Flipped in 2018, Binance Finds -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cryptocurrency-price-correlations-in-bitcoin-dollar-flipped-in-2018-binance-finds</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hZDliOGUyNGZhNTZjM2EyYTFhMjQ5YWY4YWVjZjUxNC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latest research piece from Binance highlights behavioral trends in price among cryptocurrencies&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Payment Service Square is Hiring Crypto Engineers, Offers Salaries in Bitcoin -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/payment-service-square-is-hiring-crypto-engineers-offers-salaries-in-bitcoin</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy84ZjljODg4YWY5OWUyYzkzZWM5YWU4NjI5MzFhNmFjZS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Payment platform Square is looking for cryptocurrency engineers and is offering to pay them in Bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: IPC partners Omniex on extranet-based cryptocurrency trading ecosystem -  Puntaje: 1900</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33558/ipc-partners-omniex-on-extranet-based-cryptocurrency-trading-ecosystem?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Dealing room communications outfit IPC has teamed up with digital asset trading platform Omniex to e...</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC business: Russian hackers targeting European governments ahead of May election, cybersecurity firm says -  Puntaje: 375.0</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/21/russian-hackers-target-european-governments-ahead-of-election-fireeye.html</link><description>The findings are likely to fuel worries over the possibility that Russia may influence upcoming EU elections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: [SI-LAB] LockerGoga is the most active ransomware that focuses on targeting companies -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82684/malware/lockergoga-ransomware-spreads.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;LockerGoga is the most active ransomware, experts warns it focuses on targeting companies and bypass AV signature-based detection. LockerGoga&amp;#160;ransomware&amp;#160;is a crypto-malware&amp;#160;that loads the malicious file on the system from an infected email attachment. This threat is very critical these days, and it is&amp;#160;the most active ransomware that focuses on targeting companies.&amp;#160;Altran&amp;#160;and&amp;#160;Norsk Hydro&amp;#160;are two companies severely [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82684/malware/lockergoga-ransomware-spreads.html"&gt;[SI-LAB] LockerGoga is the most active ransomware that focuses on targeting companies&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 07:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Nigerian fintech startup OneFi acquires payment company Amplify -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/d9X2QLoDKhk/</link><description>Lagos based online lending startup OneFi is buying Nigerian payment solutions company Amplify for an undisclosed amount. OneFi will take over Amplify’s IP, team, and client network of over 1000 merchants to which Amplify provides payment processing services, OneFi CEO Chijioke Dozie told TechCrunch. The move comes as fintech has become one of Africa’s most [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 07:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: 41% of banks missed PSD2 deadline says survey -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33569/41-of-banks-missed-psd2-deadline-says-survey?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Close to half of banks (41%) failed to meet a recent deadline for the Payment Services Directive (PS...</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 11:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Facebook Posts Job Vacancy for Senior Lawyer With Blockchain, Payments Experience -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/facebook-seeks-legal-counsel-as-hints-of-blockchain-payments-continue</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8wNGU3NzQxNDRiODJhOWI2YWU0NTE0MjNhMjA1ZTc5Yi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major legal post focusing on blockchain has opened at Facebook in the latest sign of associated payment plans&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Four corporate email oversights that put your organization at risk -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/four-corporate-email-oversights-that-put-your-organization-at-risk/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_662220520-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_662220520-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_662220520-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;(Author: Morey Haber, CTO, BeyondTrust)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of onboarding, new hires typically sign an employee handbook which includes policies and guidelines for acceptable information technology usage. Within the details, are often policy restrictions regarding unacceptable usage for email. Typically, these policies state that email should only be used for official company business correspondence, and not for personal communications. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you travel frequently for work, or are responsible for purchasing merchandise or services for your employer, is it acceptable to use your work email address, or should you use your personal email to complete the transaction?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Morey Haber, CTO, BeyondTrust)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This question, and the aftermath of your departure from an organization, can create a complicated situation and security risk that most employers are completely ignoring. And, unfortunately, they have no way to manage or mitigate the potential risk. Consider these real-life scenarios that organizations are facing today:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using corporate email accounts as the login for travel services&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An employee creates an account on an airline’s website using the corporate email address. This address is used for authentication into the service and to book flights or other travel arrangements. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Potential security implications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After their employment is finished, any notifications or future bookings for flights are tied to the suspended business email account. If your organization auto-forwards the email to a peer or a manager, then an identity theft threat vector has now been created. A co-worker now receiving the former employee’s emails can simply select “Forgot password” and own the former employee’s account. This is especially true if the account is not further protected by security questions or additional two-factor authentication. If verification is tied back to the same email address, then it is game over once they have a confirmation link. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recommendation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most security-conscious way to handle this scenario is for an organization to enforce the use of an approved corporate travel service for booking flights, hotels, cars, etc. in lieu of allowing employees to book travel on their own and using a corporate email account. If the business permits bookings outside of a corporate service, allow and recommend individuals to use their personal email accounts for booking travel—even if they pay with a corporate credit card. After all, it is their account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email address formats&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most organizations have an email address schema. Typical formats include first initial last name or first name dot last name. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Potential security implications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens when an employee leaves the organization and a new employee starts with the same name or initial combination? The new employee potentially receives all email of the former employee even if it not slated for them. Depending on the new employee’s role, the email may not be remotely appropriate (such as when PII and financials are involved) for them to receive. Organizations that continue to grow will have a higher statistical likelihood of overlap for names and initials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recommendation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizations should never reuse email addresses from former employees for new personnel. Consider adding numbers like “01” to the end of new email addresses to avoid this problem in the future. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using corporate email accounts for payment gateways&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some organizations allow for the purchase of merchandise and services through common payment platforms, like PayPal or Apple Pay. These are necessary for some employees (such as marketing team members) to perform their job functions.  However, none of these platforms should be set up with a user’s corporate email address. If they need to use a business email address, create a group or alias for these services. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Potential security implications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just as with the air travel example in the first scenario, a personal account used for services can be leveraged against the individual if they leave and have no access to change their email address. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recommendation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For these types of situations, it is recommended to use a dedicated account name for authentication, as opposed to an email address. This option allows the account owner to change the email address, but does present additional risk if the account is shared. Former employees using shared accounts for payment services underscore the ongoing risk of inadequate privileged access controls and the threats of shared accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using corporate accounts for personal email&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some employees use personal email for group-based personal correspondence, such as for their children’s school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Potential security implications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once an employee departs the organization, the receiver of forwarded email is now potentially exposed to highly personal information, and potentially in violation of some local regulations. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recommendation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corporate email addresses should always remain strictly delegated to business usage—and never for personal communications. The results can present some interesting legal ramifications, especially if removal of the address from a group is not trivial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, the boundaries of work and personal spheres continue to blend and blur—providing benefits (work flexibility, higher productivity, etc.) for both employers and employees—but not without cyber risks. Completely strict policies of corporate email usage will only introduce more risk as employee turnover occurs and our dependence on electronic communication continues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizations have embraced policies like Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) for mobile device support and should consider allowing personal emails addresses for exactly the same reasons. Acceptable email usage policies need to clearly state when personal usage is acceptable, should be implemented, and when it creates unnecessary risk due to employee termination. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/four-corporate-email-oversights-that-put-your-organization-at-risk/"&gt;Four corporate email oversights that put your organization at risk&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 13:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cooperativa tecnología: Google celebra a Bach con su primer doodle basado en inteligencia artificial -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.cooperativa.cl/noticias/tecnologia/internet/google/google-celebra-a-bach-con-su-primer-doodle-basado-en-inteligencia/2019-03-21/021639.html</link><description>La experiencia interactiva anima a los usuarios a componer una melodía y utiliza el aprendizaje automático para armonizarla con el estilo del célebre compositor alemán.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 05:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Finaxar Wins the Visa Everywhere Initiative with its Financing Solution -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29644/fintech/finaxar-visa-everywhere-initiative/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Visa announced Finaxar as the winner of the Visa Everywhere Initiative (VEI) 2019 during the Singapore finals. Finaxar is perhaps best known for partnering with Lazada to offer financing for&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29644/fintech/finaxar-visa-everywhere-initiative/"&gt;Finaxar Wins the Visa Everywhere Initiative with its Financing Solution&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 09:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Hear it from the Experts: The Future of Fintech and Inclusivity -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://finovate.com/hear-it-from-the-experts-the-future-of-fintech-and-inclusivity/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As technology advances, are we having enough conversations about how we can ensure the benefits will remain inclusive of all? The experts weigh in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/hear-it-from-the-experts-the-future-of-fintech-and-inclusivity/"&gt;Hear it from the Experts: The Future of Fintech and Inclusivity&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Vietnam’s Deputy Prime Minister Says It Will Be Piloting P2P Lending Soon -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29629/vietnam/vietnam-p2p-lending/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Deputy Prime Minister Vuong Dinh Hue announced during a ministerial meeting recently that the Vietnamese government will soon issue a decision to allow a pilot implementation of peer-to-peer (P2P) lending&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29629/vietnam/vietnam-p2p-lending/"&gt;Vietnam&amp;#8217;s Deputy Prime Minister Says It Will Be Piloting P2P Lending Soon&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 09:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky News technology: Bach to the future: AI turns Google Doodle into clever melody maker -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://news.sky.com/story/bach-to-the-future-ai-turns-google-doodle-into-clever-melody-maker-11671694</link><description>Google has celebrated legendary composer Johann Sebastian Bach by creating the first-ever Doodle to be powered by artificial intelligence (AI).</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: MX and Personetics team up to bring AI-driven insights to FIs -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77757/mx-and-personetics-team-up-to-bring-ai-driven-insights-to-fis?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>MX, one of the fastest-growing fintech providers, partnering with more than 1,800 financial institut...</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 12:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Travelstop Targets Fintech SMEs with Business Travel Management Platform -  Puntaje: 1800</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29596/travel/travelstop-targets-fintech-smes-with-business-travel-management-platform/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Co-founded by former Expedia employees, Singapore-based Travelstop is a modern, artificial intelligence (AI) powered SaaS platform that simplifies business travel, automates expense reporting for businesses in Asia, and offers insights&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29596/travel/travelstop-targets-fintech-smes-with-business-travel-management-platform/"&gt;Travelstop Targets Fintech SMEs with Business Travel Management Platform&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 07:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: Why the Pentagon wants more AI, drones, attack submarines and nuclear weapons -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/why-the-pentagon-wants-more-ai-drones-attack-submarines-and-nuclear-weapons</link><description>Nuclear weapons, Research and Development, space war, attack submarines, drones and AI are all massive areas of priority for Pentagon weapons developers as they seek to accelerate its growing “pivot” to major-power warfare, seeks to address deficits and - perhaps of greatest significance - stay ahead of Russia and China when it comes to weapons areas of great concern to the US military services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 12:28:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Sirin Labs Partners With MyEtherWallet to Enhance Outreach of Blockchain Smartphone -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sirin-labs-partners-with-myetherwallet-to-enhance-outreach-of-blockchain-smartphone</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83ZjAwMmM3OWY0ZWFlNWExMDY3ZjAxYjU4YjEyMzBjYi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sirin Labs is aiming to increase the profile of its blockchain smartphone via an integration with MyEtherWallet&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Mt Gox Trustee Approves Creditor Claims Worth Billions -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/mt-gox-is-taking-a-step-towards-paying-out-creditors</link><description>The trustee of collapsed crypto exchange Mt. Gox has approved creditors' claims amounting to billions of dollars, but there's a catch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 10:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Tandem launches Autosavings account -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33566/tandem-launches-autosavings-account?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>UK challenger bank Tandem has launched an interest-paying savings account that uses machine learning...</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Redditors Call Out Reported Scam on Blockchain-Based Prediction Platform Augur -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/redditors-call-out-reported-scam-on-blockchain-based-prediction-platform-augur</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82NjlhZWY2ZDgzYWEwMjRiNWNkZWU0YTQ3ZDJmZTE2ZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one scammer is reportedly gaming other users on the blockchain-powered event betting platform Augur by creating deliberately invalid markets&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 08:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Facebook Seeks Counsel to Forge Blockchain Partnerships for New Products -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/facebook-seeks-counsel-to-forge-blockchain-partnerships-for-new-products</link><description>Facebook is looking to hire a lead commercial counsel for blockchain to negotiate "partnerships needed to launch new products."</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 02:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Broadridge integrates Swift gpi -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77758/broadridge-integrates-swift-gpi?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Broadridge Financial Solutions, Inc. (NYSE:BR), a global Fintech leader and part of the S&amp;P 500® Ind...</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 12:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Bill Pay Service Doxo Adds Apple Pay Compatibility -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/payment-methods/2019/doxo-apple-pay/</link><description>Mobile and web payment service doxo announced on Thursday (May 21) that it is adding Apple Pay compatibility, according to a release by the company. The bill pay market is worth $3.9 trillion, the company said, and comprises 55 percent of annual household spending. “With doxo, consumers already have the ability to pay all their […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 12:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Google Pay Is Coming To eBay -  Puntaje: 1100</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/payments-innovation/2019/google-pay-ebay-digital-mobile-payments/</link><description>Very soon, eBay shoppers will be able to choose Google Pay as their payment method when checking out. The move comes as the latest expansion of its newly redesigned payments experience. In early 2018, eBay announced its plans to intermediate payments through a multi-year implementation that may last through mid-2020. PayPal remains a payment option […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Xiaomi Mi 9 in the UAE: An affordable flagship is here! -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/gadgets/xiaomi-mi-9-affordable-flagship/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/RTX6O8G1-min-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/RTX6O8G1-min-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/RTX6O8G1-min-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Xiaomi, the world's fourth-largest smartphone vendor, launched its Mi 9 phone in Dubai on Wednesday focusing on the flagship's specs and competitive price - and rightly so!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first look, the Mi 9's AI triple rear camera, which includes a primary 48-megapixel camera, along with a 6.39-inch screen, 6GB RAM + 128GB storage, and the world's first 20W wireless charging battery that safely charges to 100 percent in just 90 minutes, seems impressive. However, what really catches the eye is its affordable price point of AED 1,849, which is considerably lower than other flagships that have similar specs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although Xiaomi is not particularly well-known in the UAE market, the launch of an affordable smartphone with top-of-the-line offerings could not have come at a better time. The UAE smartphone market, which is one of the most highly penetrated markets globally, posted a decline of 2.4 percent in the fourth-quarter of 2018 echoing the first-ever global dip in overall smartphone sales. Xiaomi, however, along with its competitor Huawei, bucked that trend last year. Xiaomi announced a better-than-expected net profit of $276 million in the fourth-quarter of 2018 with more than 120 million shipments in a "difficult" year for smartphones globally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better than Apple, Samsung, and Huawei?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mi 9, when compared to other flagship phones introduced by the Top 4 smartphone companies in the world, holds its own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who insist on holding only a good-looking phone, the Mi 9 comes with an all-curved design certified by the Gaudi Academia of Knowledge. The smartphone has a noticeable full HD+ resolution, at 2340 x 1080 pixels, and can also host HDR playback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Inspired by the works of Antoni Gaudi, Mi 9 beautifully combines the reflection of light, seamless curves, and the use of natural elements to create a masterpiece of art,” said Carlos Canals Roura, President of The Gaudi Academia of Knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mi 9 sports a 6.39-inch AMOLED display and comes with an in-screen fingerprint sensor that unlocks the phone 25 percent faster than the previous generation. Even though this is just a matter of milliseconds, you'll notice the difference. The protective layer of Corning’s Gorilla Glass 6 minimizes scratches and protects against that occasional phone drop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who are more functionality-oriented, the Mi 9 is powered by the best-in-industry Snapdragon 855 chipset and comes with 6GB RAM as well as 128 GB worth of storage. It features a fast-charging solution for both wired and wireless charging. The 3300 mAh battery lasts a whole day and can charge to 100 percent within 60 minutes when wired, and 90 minutes wirelessly, which is much faster than its competition. German institution TUV Rheinland has certified the safe and fast charging batteries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mi 9 also has plenty to offer for those of us who use our phones primarily to take photos, videos and use social media. The Mi 9's AI triple camera comprises of the main 48-megapixel camera, 16-megapixel ultra-wide-angle camera, and a 12-megapixel telephoto camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main rear camera utilizes the latest 48-megapixel Sony IMX586 1/2” sensor which can shoot high-resolution, 48-megapixel images. The camera also takes clear and bright photos in low-light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The secondary rear 16-megapixel camera has a Sony IMX481-powered sensor that provides a wide 117-degree field of view, which provides a decent panoramic shot at the click of a button instead of having to move your phone from left to right or visa versa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third rear 12MP camera uses a Samsung S5K3M5 telephoto sensor which provides a clear 2x optical zoom, so you don't have to go closer to the subject you are photographing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The selfie camera on the front is a 20-megapixel camera with an f/2.0 aperture, which is touted to take clearer photos than all its flagship competitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The objective DxOMark website, which compares the photo- and video-quality of various smartphone cameras, has given the Mi 9 the highest score in terms of video and the second-highest in terms of photos captured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this and more, at AED 1,849 seems like there has to be a catch, but there isn't any. The reason that the price is this affordable is that Xiaomi has promised its users that it will not earn more than a 5 percent profit margin on any of its hardware products, which include smartphones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi also launched the Redmi Note 7 in the UAE on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/gadgets/xiaomi-mi-9-affordable-flagship/"&gt;Xiaomi Mi 9 in the UAE: An affordable flagship is here!&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Etihad Airways will install new tech at Abu Dhabi International Airport -  Puntaje: 3200</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/travel/etihad-airways-abu-dhabi-international-airport/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_289000634-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_289000634-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_289000634-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, and Elenium, a provider of automation technology solutions, will together demonstrate how a newly developed voice-activated self-service kiosk, bag drop and boarding gate facility will revolutionise the travel experience by taking facial recognition technology to new heights. The demonstration will take place at Passenger Terminal EXPO (PTE) in London between 26 – 28 March.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using cloud technology, artificial intelligence (AI), computer vision and natural human interfacing, Etihad Airways and Elenium will demonstrate how they will change the way consumers travel by showcasing the airport experience of the future.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jorg Oppermann, VP HUB and Midfield Operations, Etihad Airways said: “With biometric installations increasing across airports globally, Etihad is recognising the growing demand to streamline not just the passenger verification process but to also decrease passenger queues and to increase operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A key area of cooperation involves the use of technologies from Elenium, Amazon Web Services (AWS), the cloud computing subsidiary of Amazon Inc, and Etihad Airways. Together at PTE, the three entities will demonstrate a test concept for a seamless travel experience across the entire customer journey from booking to arrival at the final destination. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new check-in experience &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Passengers check-in to their flight and register their biometric data on their mobile device before arriving at the airport, reducing queues at the airport.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Using AI, new baggage-drop terminals scan and memorise each suitcase placed on the belt and assign it to the guest reservation, removing the need for tagged luggage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Using biometrics, passengers are identified and offered a personalised duty-free shopping experience through a voice interactive display, catered to the individual’s interests and needs, and also utilising floor space efficiently. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Customer Service Kiosks are available throughout the terminal to assist with airport information, provide ancillary opportunities, and because the kiosks are portable, disruption management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Passengers will board their flight by walking through boarding channels which will automatically validate them without the need for a printed boarding pass - a faster, safer system. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike Papamichael, VP Technology and Innovation, Etihad Airways said: “The technological vision and strategy is to make the guest journey a frictionless and digitally enabled experience across all channels and touch points at the airport. Etihad’s relationship with Elenium builds on this vision and along with our micro services strategy, allows us to co-create and develop innovative self-service and biometric solutions for greater flexibility and a seamless guest experience.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etihad Airways will also white label the Elenium Voyager App which features booking management, passenger check-in, passport validation, timatic auto check, facial biometric enrolment, payment wallet, itinerary management (hotel, transfer, car etc.) and companion functions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aaron Hornlimann, Elenium Automation’s Chief Executive Officer said: “Together with Etihad, we have imagined how artificial intelligence and cloud computing can be used to reinvent the passenger experience by using voice recognition and biometrics. Our vision is for passengers to simply walk through the airport unencumbered by the legacy of kiosk touch screens and the need to scan a boarding pass.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Manchester City Football Club Premier League Trophy will also be on display at the Etihad and Elenium stand on the first day of the Passenger Terminal Expo. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etihad Airways will install the new self-service transfer kiosks in phases at the new Midfield Terminal in Abu Dhabi. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/travel/etihad-airways-abu-dhabi-international-airport/"&gt;Etihad Airways will install new tech at Abu Dhabi International Airport&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 08:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>