<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:34:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>finextra: Regulated Blockchain - Oxymoron Or Killer App? -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16916/regulated-blockchain---oxymoron-or-killer-app?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>There are many business relationships where trust is one-sided. In the contract between two parties...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Tron Supports Gambling DApps Restrictions in Japanese Market to Comply With Regulations -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tron-supports-gamblings-dapps-restrictions-in-japanese-market-to-comply-with-regulations</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hMzcwODdjNzlhYTg0YTFlZjE5ZGE4MGEzNTFhODFjYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockchain-based DApp platform Tron wants to comply with Japanese laws by restricting the development of gambling apps in the local market&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:34:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: ConsenSys Picks Latest Blockchain Startups for Accelerator Program -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/consensys-picks-latest-10-blockchain-startups-for-accelerator-program</link><description>ConsenSys Ventures has selected 10 blockchain startups for the second cohort of its accelerator program Tachyon, launching today.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Research: Ethereum-Based Prediction Market Augur Currently Faces a Design Flaw Attack -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/research-ethereum-based-prediction-market-augur-currently-faces-a-design-flaw-attack</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8zYjgyYWJhNjNhMzEyY2Q4OWFjMGIwM2I5ZjhmYWQ3YS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A design flaw attack is reportedly ongoing on Ethereum-based prediction market Augur, according to research&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 13:47:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Muttniks: An open source dapp to show you how we built Astro Ledger -  Puntaje: 2400</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/muttniks-an-open-source-dapp-to-show-you-how-we-built-astro-ledger-8a063b788d0b?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*0INXYqbKz8RCX0pLwGtlPQ.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;A sneak peek into the &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks"&gt;Muttniks&lt;/a&gt; kennel.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Launching a dapp may not be as hard as launching a rocket… but it’s no moonwalk, either. A dapp, portmanteau of “decentralized app,” is any app that runs on decentralized infrastructure, like on Ethereum. For your coding pleasure, our team is happy to present Muttniks, a friendly Ethereum space doggo “kernel” (or kennel) that you can build from the comfort of your spacecraft. Muttniks is an open source sample dapp, built to guide you through our exciting journey with Astro Ledger. Like the real stars and planets featured on &lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org"&gt;astroledger.org&lt;/a&gt;, you can securely adopt, name, and trade Ethereum space doggos with Muttniks (and then donate your testnet ETH to build more &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laika"&gt;Laika&lt;/a&gt; monuments). The following is a step-by-step technical exploration of the inner workings of Astro Ledger, which you can recreate on your local machine with Muttniks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Muttniks was the “pet” project of Astro Ledger CWM (Chief Wow Muttniks) &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka"&gt;Tony&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks Tony!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/385/1*FhP6UIAHAAjcceXIdkCjjQ.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;This star’s Henry Draper catalog number is HD137052. &lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org/#/card?externalId=137052&amp;amp;category=1"&gt;It has been named ‘Tlon&lt;/a&gt;’.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Keeping Track of Stars &amp;amp; Muttniks&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In order to assign names to actual stars, we needed a way to uniquely identify them. For this we used the Henry Draper Catalog of the brightest stars in the sky, with meta-information provided by the &lt;a href="http://www.astronexus.com/hyg"&gt;HYG database&lt;/a&gt; from The Astronomy Nexus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our specially selected Muttniks have no such prior catalog so we pseudo-randomly assigned each Muttnik a number, 1–6. The meta-information about each Muttnik (name and image) is loaded into the database in this &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks/blob/develop/modules/flyway/src/main/resources/db/migration/V3__pets_1.sql"&gt;Flyway migrations file&lt;/a&gt;. Our Astro Ledger creative content (spearheaded by Chief Chocolate Dehydrator &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/laazeecat"&gt;Aleeza&lt;/a&gt;) and image links are similarly loaded into the database, with SQL code created by offline Python scripts that load data from HYG and other sources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a Muttnik is added to a database, we use a &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks/blob/develop/sol/migrations/3_muttniks_1.js"&gt;Truffle migration script&lt;/a&gt; to add the same Muttnik to the contract, putting it up for adoption. For Astro Ledger stars, those same offline Python scripts create corresponding Truffle migration scripts to create stars and put them up for space-grant-supporting-auctions at the price of about a dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Contract &amp;amp; Events: Creating and Adopting&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Muttniks are stored in a &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks/blob/3f981a7191f7b313aaea77e2156416d2c2e19446/sol/contracts/Adoption.sol#L12"&gt;“pets” mapping&lt;/a&gt; where each pet has an address variable for the adopter, initialized to address(0), and a boolean variable exists to distinguish this pet from one that hasn’t been created yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The function createAdoptee is used by the &lt;em&gt;Muttnik Kernel&lt;/em&gt; owners to create each Muttnik in the contract. This is typically done in batch with a &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks/blob/develop/sol/migrations/3_muttniks_1.js"&gt;Truffle migration script&lt;/a&gt;, but could be called by any function. Adoption happens via the adopt function, which checks to see that the Muttnik hasn’t already been adopted before assigning the Muttnik’s address to the adopter. Adoption events are emitted so the browser can inform the astronaut/cosmonaut of the adoption when the blockchain confirms it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Contract &amp;amp; Events: Naming Muttniks&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious solution to handling Muttnik (and star) names was to store the name as a variable in the contract. To find the name, folks could call a view function (for zero gas) that would return the name. However, storing data in an Ethereum contract is never a cheap operation. Because Astro Ledger’s goal is to allow anyone to be able to assign meaningful names to stars, we implemented the assignName function using &lt;em&gt;events&lt;/em&gt; instead. Names are forever stored on the blockchain as 32 bytes of data on a log of the event, but because they aren’t accessible to the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), the gas cost to assign a name is almost negligible. This philosophically-motivated decision allowed us the exhilarating discovery that much of the existing software for Ethereum does not fully support event-logs, but we went to the edges of the universe to achieve a solution for pulling up the names quickly, as described later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/909/1*E-hICbgh-y3hecBDtfH9fQ.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The owner of &lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org/#/card?externalId=162004&amp;amp;category=1"&gt;HD162004&lt;/a&gt; is well aware that changing a star’s name is not to be taken lightly…&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Web Stack&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Chief Rubber Taster &lt;a href="http://jonathan.lansey.net/"&gt;Jonathan&lt;/a&gt; worked on the contract and the star database, Tony began building the Astro Ledger web stack using Play! for a web framework (&lt;a href="https://engineering.linkedin.com/play/play-framework-async-io-without-thread-pool-and-callback-hell"&gt;ol’ reliable&lt;/a&gt;), and Postgres for the database (ol’ &lt;a href="http://renesd.blogspot.com/2017/02/is-postgresql-good-enough.html"&gt;good enough for everything&lt;/a&gt;). At first, Tony chose &lt;a href="https://www.playframework.com/documentation/2.7.x/ScalaTemplates"&gt;Twirl&lt;/a&gt; to generate HTML pages of available stars. He quickly learned that the majority of the anticipated Astro Ledger user base had settled on a browser plugin called MetaMask to talk to Ethereum blockchains, and so began sneaking in some JavaScript (including a popular library called &lt;a href="https://github.com/ethereum/wiki/wiki/JavaScript-API"&gt;web3js&lt;/a&gt;) into the webpages to support this. The code to generate web pages soon became a funny mix of Scala, HTML, and ES5, where all of the blockchain interactions were executed using web3js. This worked, and was fast enough in our test environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though it’s probably still fair to call the main Ethereum network itself a “test environment,” deploying our app to it in our first production alpha revealed one that was far slower than even Tony’s 2014 Macbook Air. This was particularly true for the for-loops we used in our contract to search for a user’s star cards, which were executed individually in the user’s web browser whenever they went to our page (note that, to guard against this performance hit, the &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks/blob/develop/sol/contracts/Adoption.sol"&gt;Muttniks Solidity code&lt;/a&gt; uses no for-loops). To prevent expensive, redundant contract calls, we decided to move some of these queries to the Scala side of things, where they’d execute once on our Heroku instance every few minutes, and then be accessible to a user’s web browser without it having to call any contract code itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/385/1*mR7duXRp6mDtQKyvHuSckA.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org/#/card?externalId=188260&amp;amp;category=1"&gt;Jellybean&lt;/a&gt; isn’t for sale, but it’s hot enough to melt your heart.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was great for querying a user’s star cards, but things became interesting when we needed to query the names that they assigned to stars. As mentioned earlier, rather than put these names in contract storage as we did with auctions and card ownership, we chose to keep a record of star names using Ethereum events: this was intended as a &lt;a href="https://media.consensys.net/technical-introduction-to-events-and-logs-in-ethereum-a074d65dd61e"&gt;less expensive form of storage&lt;/a&gt;. So why not cache &lt;em&gt;these&lt;/em&gt; on our server? As we soon discovered, &lt;a href="https://web3j.io/"&gt;web3j&lt;/a&gt; (a library similar to web3js that we used for querying the blockchain in Scala) &lt;a href="https://web3j.readthedocs.io/en/latest/filters.html#filters-and-events"&gt;did not support filters&lt;/a&gt; on Infura, the free client we used for accessing the main Ethereum network. Web3js &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; support querying events in the user’s browser, but this had even worse performance effects on the browser than querying ownership, because it would poll the blockchain every second or so to get event information (web3js 1.0 &lt;a href="https://github.com/ethereum/web3.js/issues/326"&gt;has since addressed this&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get a better handle on things, we decided to go closer to the source. In earlier investigations, Tony had coded up some Clojure code to talk directly to Infura’s RPC endpoints. With it running on our server, we could essentially do the same thing as web3js would in someone’s browser, but in one place (for $7/month) and at a longer poll interval. So, we decided to turn it into a full blown service. Coupled with Redis, this gave us our own centralized names cache, which, as with auctions and card ownership, could be accessed in someone’s browser much more quickly than if it were to query the blockchain directly itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Single-Page&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, Chief Rubber Taster Jonathan was tasting the rubber over in Tel Aviv when he met the team developing &lt;a href="https://www.portis.io/"&gt;Portis&lt;/a&gt;, a browser based smart-contract enabled wallet. Portis would allow folks to use Ethereum on a vanilla web browser (i.e. without MetaMask installed), including iOS or Android. However, &lt;a href="https://gitter.im/portis-project/Lobby?at=5b4b4f799a612333aa63b400"&gt;since the Portis library only stored user credentials in browser memory&lt;/a&gt;, our initial approach of rendering web pages server-side (where clicking a link would open a brand new page) would oblige users to log in over and over again whenever they navigated anywhere on our site. The solution was to migrate to a &lt;a href="https://tinnedfruit.com/articles/create-your-own-dysfunctional-single-page-app.html"&gt;single page application&lt;/a&gt; that could be downloaded all at once in a user’s web browser, to provide full functionality without a user ever having to refresh the page or log in again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*p30-vrUbedjzuNOPeGnMNA.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Easily accessing astroledger.org with Portis, so we can add &lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org/#/card?externalId=139997&amp;amp;category=1"&gt;Libre&lt;/a&gt; to our star collection.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To accomplish this, we settled on &lt;a href="https://reactjs.org/"&gt;React&lt;/a&gt;, since it afforded us the ability to easily use another popular library, &lt;a href="https://github.com/trufflesuite/drizzle-react"&gt;Drizzle-React&lt;/a&gt; to interoperate with web3js in a singly-paged way. However, The Drizzle library itself relied on web3js 1.0, which at the time &lt;a href="https://github.com/MetaMask/metamask-extension/issues/3642#issue-307084613"&gt;was not fully compatible with MetaMask&lt;/a&gt;. We eventually abandoned Drizzle, but continued on with React.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Muttniks!&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Muttniks is a pared down version of the Astro Ledger app, available here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks"&gt;https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get started with Muttniks, head over to the &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks#cheat-sheet"&gt;cheat sheet&lt;/a&gt;! The overall structure can be gleaned from the &lt;a href="https://github.com/tlazenka/muttniks/blob/develop/docker-compose.yml"&gt;docker compose file&lt;/a&gt;, and by drilling down into each service’s individual list of dependencies (note that some dependencies aren’t relevant to Muttniks, but were used by Astro Ledger). &lt;a href="https://docs.docker.com/compose/overview/"&gt;Docker compose&lt;/a&gt; is a convenient tool that lets you package up all these fun little services so you can easily launch them together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Docker Compose Services&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;app&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main Scala app that sits atop Postgres. When the app is started, it runs the database migrations if needed with &lt;a href="https://flywaydb.org/"&gt;Flyway&lt;/a&gt;, and then &lt;a href="http://slick.lightbend.com/doc/2.1.0/code-generation.html"&gt;Slick generates the case classes&lt;/a&gt; from the resulting schema. A periodic task is scheduled with &lt;a href="https://doc.akka.io/docs/akka/2.5/scheduler.html"&gt;Akka&lt;/a&gt; to query the blockchain with web3j and update the Postgres database.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;db/redis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Postgres/Redis databases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;jobs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Clojure service that sits atop Redis. When started, it schedules a task with &lt;a href="http://clojurequartz.info/"&gt;Quartzite&lt;/a&gt; to periodically query the local Ethereum blockchain, and caches the results in Redis using &lt;a href="https://github.com/ptaoussanis/carmine"&gt;Carmine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;sbt/lein&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Centos images that map sbt/ivy2/m2 directories to your local machine to speed up dependency downloads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;truffle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Truffle service for compiling the Ethereum contract and running the tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ganache&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://truffleframework.com/ganache"&gt;A Ganache service used here for a local development blockchain.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;react&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The React version of the website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;web3j&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A web3j image that includes the &lt;a href="https://web3j.readthedocs.io/en/latest/command_line.html"&gt;command line tools&lt;/a&gt; for generating code from the Truffle JSON artifacts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;firefox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A service with a Firefox browser plus MetaMask that you can access using VNC, you don’t want to install MetaMask in your own browser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Wrap-Up&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In case you are struggling for a reason why Muttniks needs to be on any blockchain… you are not alone in the universe. However, let’s suspend disbelief and say that the gray area of “ownership over the naming privileges of non-existing Soviet dogs long gone to the happy hunting ground in the sky” needs to be codified in some way…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*uNWFyYIK18AQX09NpzzkBQ.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;This vegetating llama could be vegetating on blockchain… Photo by &lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/cheryl_strahl/"&gt;Cheryl Strahl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You can put literally anything countable on blockchain!&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/385/1*rU01CQEyDIhuo1qljc_2dQ.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org/#/card?externalId=16620&amp;amp;category=1"&gt;HD16620&lt;/a&gt; is just one of &lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org/#/onSale"&gt;many awesome stars&lt;/a&gt; needing a name…&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are really happy with how the framework runs and would love to hear about how Muttniks has helped you to put vegetating llamas on blockchain, or maybe adopt every single Amur Leopard on blockchain, or perhaps slam slowly slaloming snails… yes, on blockchain!!! If you are having any difficulty with your implementations, just radio for help. The &lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org/#/about#team"&gt;Astro Ledger team&lt;/a&gt; would be happy to work with you — shoot an email to &lt;a href="mailto:groundcontrol@astroledger.org"&gt;groundcontrol@astroledger.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if you just can’t get enough Muttniks, don’t forget to beam over to &lt;a href="https://www.astroledger.org"&gt;astroledger.org&lt;/a&gt; and try naming some blockchain stars!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=8a063b788d0b" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/muttniks-an-open-source-dapp-to-show-you-how-we-built-astro-ledger-8a063b788d0b"&gt;Muttniks: An open source dapp to show you how we built Astro Ledger&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Balancing Openness &amp; Safety in DeFi: Mitigating Front Running on Bancor -  Puntaje: 7800</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/balancing-openness-safety-in-defi-mitigating-front-running-on-bancor-c2b42513a033?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*08jLK9s-mqOPvpExuIhDsQ.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open financial networks on the Ethereum blockchain must deal with the risk of exposing users to an array of abusive practices. While decentralized finance or “DeFi” instruments offer huge advantages over legacy financial systems, namely by eliminating rent-seeking intermediaries and bringing new levels of transparency to token markets, network designers should seek to strike a balance between openness and user safety. After all, if DeFi solutions become rife with abuse and are only safe for the most advanced users, they will undermine the very openness that DeFi projects seek to promote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One such attempt to exploit the design of DeFi architectures is the abusive practice known as &lt;strong&gt;front running&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;which occurs when malicious actors steal money from users by stepping in front of pending transactions. The term front running originated in the stock market, when trades were executed on paper and carried by hand between trading desks. A broker would receive an order from a client to buy a certain stock, but place a buy order in front of the trade for themselves, benefiting from the eventual price rise and effectively stealing money from the client.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On certain Ethereum-based networks, a front runner can monitor for incoming transactions that will increase the price of an asset and step in front of a transaction by paying a slightly higher gas fee, resulting in miners selecting their transaction first. The original pending transaction and the user who submitted it are manipulated by the front runner who profits from the price increase and then dumps the asset, while the user receives less of the asset than expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the Bancor Protocol launched in 2017, it introduced a new level of transparency into token conversions. Historically, crypto token conversions have been processed inside the vaults of exchanges or via off-chain order matching — between buyers and sellers — which often leads to opaque pricing and unexpected costs (e.g., “slippage”) for users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Bancor Protocol, conversions occur fully on-chain — from pricing through settlement — via &lt;a href="https://blog.bancor.network/smart-tokens-101-63edc2cc5a89"&gt;automated market maker smart contracts&lt;/a&gt;. Since users convert &lt;a href="https://blog.bancor.network/why-bnt-is-crucial-to-the-bancor-network-e102c964bcbf"&gt;directly against smart contracts&lt;/a&gt;, without order books or counterparties, users are able to pre-calculate the amount of tokens they’ll receive with greater accuracy, while every movement of tokens in the network is publicly recorded and auditable on the blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, this level of visibility and predictability can be a double-edged sword as it can also be used by malicious actors to front run conversions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bancor mitigates front running by building hard-coded values into transactions at the protocol level and setting a maximum gas price which dynamically adjusts for each transaction on the network. This ensures that transactions submitted to the network are executed in the correct and valid order, neutralizing the threat of front running.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To determine maximum gas price, Bancor developed a heuristic which calculates the optimal gas price within the average time it takes to execute a transaction on the Ethereum blockchain (between 45s and 1m and 15s). The heuristic is designed to avoid anomalies such as Ethereum network congestion and spam which could lead to inflated gas prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are certainly trade-offs to this approach. While some DeFi protocols are able to keep Ethereum gas prices lower because they do not implement a max gas price, they expose users to front running abuse, which increases as a network’s volume grows and returns become more attractive for sophisticated front-running traders or bots. While these protocols tout their ability to maintain lower gas prices, ultimately, users may end up incurring even higher costs if their conversions are front run by malicious actors. Moreover, the conversion volume from front running may lead product operators to delay front running protection, so as to maintain network volume, despite it being partially the result of manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the long term, de-prioritizing user safety will create environments which are not suitable for everyday users, undermining the very openness of open finance. DeFi simply won’t succeed if users have to master gas strategies to avoid abuse. As DeFi projects look towards new innovations that target everyday human users, basic protections against manipulation will be key to driving healthy interest and long-term growth. Network operators should seek to introduce elements that make manipulative behavior unprofitable or prevent it altogether, while imposing the least collective costs on users. As with decentralization, products and services can strive for how to best achieve the benefits of openness, rather than making it the aim in and of itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;About The Bancor Protocol&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bancor.network/"&gt;Bancor&lt;/a&gt; is an on-chain liquidity protocol revolutionizing the way people create and share value by ensuring constant convertibility between tokens. Conversions via Bancor are executed against on-chain liquidity pools using automated market makers to price and process transactions without order books or counterparties, enabling faster, cheaper and more predictable conversions across 9700+ ERC20 and EOS token pairs, including non-custodial conversions between blockchains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;How to get involved with Bancor&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://support.bancor.network/hc/en-us/articles/360002098551-Apply-to-join-the-Bancor-Network"&gt;Add your token&lt;/a&gt; to the Bancor Network.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Checkout &lt;a href="https://github.com/bancorprotocol/contracts"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;, jump in and contribute code.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build a dApp with the &lt;a href="https://support.bancor.network/hc/en-us/sections/360001492551-Developer-Tools"&gt;Bancor APIs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support us on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Bancor"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://about.bancor.network/careers/"&gt;Join our team&lt;/a&gt;. We have new positions posting all the time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=c2b42513a033" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/balancing-openness-safety-in-defi-mitigating-front-running-on-bancor-c2b42513a033"&gt;Balancing Openness &amp;amp; Safety in DeFi: Mitigating Front Running on Bancor&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 07:36:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Markets Continue Rising While Bitcoin’s Dominance Continues to Drop -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-markets-continue-rising-while-bitcoins-dominance-continues-to-drop</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8zNDI0ZmExZjhjOWJhZTIwMjk4YTBmOTA0ZTFhZTYxNy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto markets continued to rise today, with Bitcoin seeing stable price growth but a slight decline in its market share&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:10:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coincheck Launches Bitcoin OTC Trading Desk for Large-Scale Institutional Clients -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coincheck-launches-bitcoin-otc-trading-desk-for-large-scale-institutional-clients</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lMmY3MzkxZTI1N2MyMmE0ODgyODc0MzQ0YjlkNzcyMy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese cryptocurrency exchange Coincheck has launched a Bitcoin over-the-counter trading desk for large-scale institutional investors&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 08:39:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>We Live Security: Cryptocurrency exchange loses millions in heist -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/eset/blog/~3/7JyHcyPBkRE/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Bithumb believes that, unlike in the past, this theft was the work of rogue insiders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.welivesecurity.com/2019/04/01/cryptocurrency-exchange-millions-heist/"&gt;Cryptocurrency exchange loses millions in heist&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="/" rel="nofollow"&gt;WeLiveSecurity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/eset/blog/~4/7JyHcyPBkRE" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 14:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: US SEC Seeks Crypto Specialist Attorney Advisor to Develop Plan for Crypto Securities -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-sec-seeks-crypto-specialist-attorney-advisor-to-develop-plan-for-crypto-securities</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9kY2IwZTZkNWVkNThmMTI5ZWQyZjNhZGY5Mjg3MTVlYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States Securities and Exchange Commission is looking to hire a crypto specialist attorney advisor for its Division of Trading and Markets&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:11:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Finovate Alumni News -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-969/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Around the web Salt Edge unveils new version of API with a consent management system and UX enhancements. MOXY bank selects NYMBUS&amp;#8216; SmartCore platform. InComm and WH Smith launch in-store and online hubs for game cards in the U.K. STOblock interviews Bitbond Founder and CEO Radoslav Albrecht. India&amp;#8217;s Federal Bank turns to Ripple to power cross-border remittances. &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-969/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-969/"&gt;Finovate Alumni News&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 14:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: Blockchain Front Page: Is a 51% attack a real issue? -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/04/01/blockchain-front-page-is-a-51-attack-a-real-issue/</link><description>Last week our theme was &amp;#8220;Can a Cryptocurrency replace the US Dollar to Become the World’s Reserve Currency?.&amp;#8220; Our theme for this week is &amp;#8220;Is a 51% attack a real issue?&amp;#8221; In 2018, cryptocurrency hackers earned $20M with 51% attacks, The report by Group-IB, showed that in 5 incidents last year, hackers walked away with $19.5 million worth [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 05:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: India's Federal Bank to use Ripple for cross-border remittances -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77858/indias-federal-bank-to-use-ripple-for-cross-border-remittances?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>This is to inform Federal Bank has entered into a partnership with Ripple Inc, a blockchain supporte...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 14:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Indian Crypto Exchange Coindelta Shutters Services, Citing Adverse Regulatory Conditions -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/indian-crypto-exchange-coindelta-shutters-services-citing-adverse-regulatory-conditions</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85MjhhNDc1MTJhNTNiNWQ2MmJiNWFjYjAyNDFhYjkyMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian cryptocurrency exchange Coindelta is terminating its services in light of the adverse operating climate for crypto businesses in the country&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 10:42:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Coincheck Launches OTC Crypto Trading for Institutions -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/coincheck-launches-otc-crypto-trading-for-institutions</link><description>Japanese cryptocurrency exchange Coincheck has launched an over-the-counter bitcoin trading service aimed at clients with deep pockets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Techniques used by Hackers to steal Cryptocurrecny -  Puntaje: 9000</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/techniques-used-by-hackers-to-steal-cryptocurrecny-e172ba5d79fb?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;p&gt;From phishing to crypto jacking to key-logger attacks, there are a lot of ways, hackers can steal your stash of cryptocurrency. In early July 2018, Bleeping Computers identified a suspicious activity to defraud 2.3 Million Bitcoin wallets. All these wallets were under the threat of being hacked. The malware used was “clipboard hijackers.” It operated in the clipboard and could replace the copied wallet data with one of the hackers while transferring Bitcoin to other wallets. Kaspersky Lab had predicted such type of hacking attacks in November 2017, and it didn’t take long to become a reality. &lt;br&gt;Till date, this is one of the most popular types of attack to steal user’s crypto and information. About 20 percent of the total cryptocurrency hacking attempts are made on individual’s wallets and accounts. Kaspersky Lab’s report published in Cointelegraph stated that criminals had stolen $9 million through social media engineering and other hacking techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*vSGbOrQq0ruy69eMmoYkNA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are chances that some undetectable programs are running on your smartphone or Laptop right now, copying your every single seed, password or any button you hit on. When these programs send back or change the copied clipboard data, it becomes too easy for the attacker to gain full access to your wallets. Hackers use the vulnerability we didn’t notice. Here’s how they do it and how we can protect our wallet:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;SLACK BOTS&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many slack bots which are being used by hackers. &lt;br&gt;Since mid-2017, there have been many cases of stolen cryptocurrency through this technique. The bot sends a notification to the user’s device about issues with their wallet. The ultimate goal is to force the user to click the notification and type private key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/582/1*-T82KP78F486Am_ExoGIAA.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image source: Steemit @sassal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIPS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Report Slack-bots immediately;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ignore bots’ activity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;ADD-ONS FOR CRYPTO TRADING&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;You get extensions to do more comfortable work with wallets. But these extensions are vulnerable to hacking attacks as they are developed on JavaScript. Might be an extension is using your computing resources for mining purposes. To avoid it: &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Use incognito mode. &lt;br&gt;Use separate browser for cryptocurrency related work &lt;br&gt;Install Network protection&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;SOCIAL ENGINEERING AND PHISHING&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cybercriminals also ramp up their focus on social engineering to steal cryptocurrency from newbie users. Fraudulent websites and paid ads are still on the rise even after the ban. Hackers mimic the authorization pages of exchanges and dupe users to enter the private key. To avoid it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enter the exchange address directly to the URL bar &lt;br&gt;Never trust ads offering free cryptocurrencies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;CRYPTOCURRENCY MINING BOTNETS&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Botnets’ are networks malware-infected systems which can be controlled remotely. Generally, botnets are used to distribute malware or to perform DDoS attacks. But for quite a few time crypto-criminals are using it to mine cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;SMS AUTHENTICATION&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the users have mobile authentication as it is handy and they always have the smartphone. But using the SS7 protocol hackers can intercept an SMS with a password confirmation. Here’s the vulnerability is in the cellular network. To avoid it: &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stop using SMS verification &lt;br&gt;Use software base 2FA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bad news is there is no decrease in the activity of crypto hacking. As per JAN 2019, there are more than 11000 dark web platforms selling more than 34000 offers. Here anyone can get malicious software for an average price of $240.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/726/1*6h6DXl85i9FtJLUFWXGYSA.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Report Source: CARBON BLACK&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big question is: How do these softwares get on our computer? On June 27 a program called All-Radio 4.27 was installed unknowingly on many devices. The situation got more complicated when people were not able to uninstall it. It had given a whole suitcase of unpleasant surprises. It was found that the program had hidden miner and was monitoring the clipboard. This program was installed on the systems which have cracked games or OS versions. It’s foolish to become a scapegoat of such hacking attacks. So, in conclusion, I’ll like to remind you of advice from Bryan Wallace:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Encryption, anti-virus software, and multi-factor identification will only keep your assets safe to a point; they key is preventive measures and simple common sense.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=e172ba5d79fb" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/techniques-used-by-hackers-to-steal-cryptocurrecny-e172ba5d79fb"&gt;Techniques used by Hackers to steal Cryptocurrecny&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 07:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Naked Security: Microsoft slaps down 99 APT35/Charming Kitten domains -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2019/04/01/microsoft-slaps-down-99-apt35-charming-kitten-domains/</link><description>Court order in hand, Microsoft seized control of the hacker group's (which it calls Phosphorous) phishing sites.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 11:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Threatpost: ThreatList: Game of Thrones, a Top Malware Conduit for Cybercriminals -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://threatpost.com/game-of-thrones-malware-piracy/143318/</link><description>As Game of Thrones' eighth season gets ready to kick off, a new report says the popular TV show accounted for 17 percent of all infected pirated content in the last year.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: New Linux/DDosMan threat emerged from an evolution of the older Elknot -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83157/malware/new-linux-ddosman-threat-emerged-from-an-evolution-of-the-older-elknot.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The popular expert unixfreaxjp analyzed a new China ELF DDoS&amp;#8217;er malware tracked as &amp;#8220;Linux/DDoSMan&amp;#8221; that evolves from the Elknot malware to deliver new ELF bot. Non-Technical-Premise “This report is meant for incident response or Linux forensics purpose, TO HELP admin &amp;#38; IR folks”, with this the very beginning sentence starts the new analysis of one [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83157/malware/new-linux-ddosman-threat-emerged-from-an-evolution-of-the-older-elknot.html"&gt;New Linux/DDosMan threat emerged from an evolution of the older Elknot&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 10:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Threat actors in the ME are becoming more destructive in 2019 -  Puntaje: 8800</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/it-2/threat-actors-in-the-me-are-becoming-more-destructive-in-2019/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1007525926-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1007525926-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1007525926-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;National State Actors from around the world including Iran continues to be a major cybercrime threat to businesses and government institutions across the Middle East according to the annual global Threat Report published by CrowdStrike®, the leader in cloud-delivered endpoint protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CrowdStrike’s report reviewed incidents of both eCrime and state-sponsored cyberattacks across the world and found that Russian, China, Iran and North Korea continue to maintain a professional and experienced cybercrime capability which presents a major threat to countries whose political agenda conflicts with the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking ahead of next month’s GISEC, the largest cybersecurity exhibition and conference in the Middle East, Africa and Asia, Dubai-based CrowdStrike Head, Rawad Sarieddine, said: "Many nation states including Iran sustained a moderate operations tempo throughout 2018. Saudi Arabia continued to be the primary regional target for this actor, however, the use of Bahrain-themed spear- phishing underscores tensions between Iran and Bahrain. Governments and businesses need to be aware of the threat they present and be prepared to deal with that threat."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report indicates that entities in the UAE and Saudi government, defence and NGO sectors will continue to be the targets of these operations of potentially unfriendly government is seeking geopolitical prominence, both in the region and internationally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our report has found that Iran along with other threat actors continues to be a destructive threat — not only within the Middle East but also to companies based in Western countries that may do business or maintain infrastructure in the region,” said Sarieddine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At GISEC, CrowdStrike will present a Secret Briefing titled: Combatting today’s advanced attacker: Key trends, predictions and the need for speed, to provide delegates with insights and real-world examples of how cybercriminals combine advanced, targeted attack techniques with ransomware to cause massive financial loss and how CrowdStrike’s Threat Hunting team are able to spot and deal with threats quickly before significant impact to the corporate network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“During our Secret Briefing, we will help delegates understand how threat hunting can be used to identify and stop advanced attacks in our environment, and how to defend organisations against advanced attacks,” said the session’s presenter Roland Daccache, Security Engineer at CrowdStrike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CrowdStrike Falcon platform remains the only next-generation endpoint protection solution that unifies next-generation antivirus (AV), IT Hygiene, endpoint detection and response (EDR), threat intelligence, and managed hunting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About CrowdStrike®&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CrowdStrike is the leader in cloud-delivered endpoint protection. Leveraging artificial intelligence (AI), the CrowdStrike Falcon® platform offers instant visibility and protection across the enterprise and prevents attacks on endpoints on or off the network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/it-2/threat-actors-in-the-me-are-becoming-more-destructive-in-2019/"&gt;Threat actors in the ME are becoming more destructive in 2019&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 06:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Biometric payments at the tip of your fingers -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16918/biometric-payments-at-the-tip-of-your-fingers?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The word biometrics is derived from two Greek words – bio meaning “life” and metrics meaning “to mea...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Clearing House bids to win over smaller institutions to real-time payments network -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33615/clearing-house-bids-to-win-over-smaller-institutions-to-real-time-payments-network?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Clearing House is bidding to win over community banks and credit unions to its real-time payment...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 11:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Exclusive: Renault alerts prosecutors over Oman dealer payments under Ghosn -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/exclusive--renault-alerts-prosecutors-over-oman-dealer-payments-under-ghosn-11401668</link><description>Renault has alerted French prosecutors after uncovering suspect payments to a Renault-Nissan business partner in Oman under former Chief Executive Carlos Ghosn, two sources told Reuters on Monday.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 22:31:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Jio has FANG, technology that will edge in every aspect of digital economy -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/jio-on-path-to-connect-every-possible-tech-use-case-through-acquisitions-119033100597_1.html</link><description>Unlike peers, the telco is on the path to connect every possible tech use case through acquisitions</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 21:50:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Truevo taps Temenos for fintech-targeted payments line -  Puntaje: 1100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77867/truevo-taps-temenos-for-fintech-targeted-payments-line?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Malta-based card acquirer and payment solutions provider, Truevo Payments, today announced that it h...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: Tencent’s Payment &amp; FinTech Business, an Important Revenue Growth Driver -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://gomedici.com/tencent-payment-fintech-business-important-revenue-growth-driver/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/tencent-payment-fintech-business-important-revenue-growth-driver.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;Tencent recently announced its FY 18 results and the total revenue for the company at USD 45.46 billion grew by 24.5% on a YoY basis and net profit to the shareholders at USD 11.44 billion increased by 4.22% on a YoY basis. Tencent divides its total revenue into three segments: Value-Added Services (comprises of social networks &amp;amp;amp; online games) Online Advertising Others The Others segment primarily consists of Payment &amp;amp;amp; FinTech services, Cloud services, and other services. For this article, we will focus on Payment &amp;amp;amp; FinTech services. The Payment &amp;amp;amp; FinTech services of Tencent comprise the following: Weixin/WeChat Pay: An integrated feature in Weixin/WeChat (instant messaging and social entertainment mobile app), Weixin/WeChat Pay is a mobile payment solution. QQ Wallet: QQ Wallet is integrated into QQ instant messaging platform for PC and mobile. QQ Wallet is a mobile payment product that incorporates multiple payment methods such as bank card...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 17:21:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Pakistan Introducing Regulations, Licensing Scheme for Crypto Firms -  Puntaje: 2500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/pakistan-introducing-regulations-licensing-scheme-for-crypto-firms</link><description>The government of Pakistan is putting in place regulations that will see digital currency firms licensed to combat illicit uses of the technology.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:05:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: World Bank Sees DLT Potential For Cross-Border Transactions -  Puntaje: 5500</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/payment-methods/2019/world-bank-swift-ripple-dlt-cross-border/</link><description>The jockeying for cross border-payments continues, and SWIFT and Ripple continue to dominate the headlines. At heart of the matter, of course, is the place (or choice) of using distributed ledger technology (DLT) to underpin the transactions — especially B2B transactions. As noted, SWIFT has rolled out its gpi (short for global payments initiative). Ripple […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 17:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: The 3 V’s of Big Data Analytics -  Puntaje: 4300</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/the-3-vs-of-big-data-analytics-1afd59692adb?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want to know how big data could be a crucial part of your business? Keep reading to see how big data analytics services has helped the tech industry become successful in 2019.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/847/1*be2sR_HIKjY36cWuWRcu-Q.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Big Data?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big data is the rapid extension of unstructured, semi-structured, and structured data generated from &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/everything-you-need-to-know-to-start-your-iot-project-ef036c9f6e6e"&gt;internet connected devices&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The insights that are delivered from big data analytics services will help marketers like &lt;a href="https://alex-reviews.com/"&gt;Ecom Cash Crusher Review&lt;/a&gt; target campaigns more strategically, help healthcare professionals notice epidemics, and help environmentalists understand future sustainability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3v’s of Big Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big data analytics can be a difficult concept to grasp onto, especially with the vast varieties and amounts of data today. To make sense of the concept, experts broken it down into 3 simple segments. These three segments are the three big V’s of data: variety, velocity, and volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Velocity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Initially, the acceleration of big data has to lead to more opportunities. There’s a lot of data at hand, and once we have access to this data, you can use it to discover new realities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly, the rate of data growth is passing our ability to decipher it. A study conducted by Digital Universe by IDC reveals that data around the world doubles in size every two years. What’s more important is that 3% of the data is organized, with only 0.5% is ready for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big data isn’t just big; it’s growing fast. On example of this the daily Facebook statistics. Based on Social Skinny’s insight, 293,000 statuses are updated, 136,000 photos uploaded, and 500,000 comments posted on Facebook every minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metadata technology and Big data technology paired with machine learning and AI will have to be used to their highest potential to give a snapshot of future frontiers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Variety&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data is fast, data is big, but data is extremely diverse. A few decades ago, data would’ve been in a structured database in a simple text file. There was not a lot of options on how to use the data besides finding a trend and simple classification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, big data has changed the data landscape. While there’s still a place for text data, there are other forms of data presentation that are more convenient. For instance, video, audio, geospatial, images, and many others come into play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each data form has its own type of uniqueness in terms of how it’s classified and stored on a cloud. What makes the format unique is how we can analyze them to create valuable solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world has a lot of data behind it, possibly at an incomprehensible amount. With over &lt;a href="https://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/291358/90-of-todays-data-created-in-two-years.html"&gt;90% of today’s data&lt;/a&gt; being generated in the past 2 years, that estimates to 2.5 quintillion data bytes daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s think about volume from a social media standpoint, since social media has a huge impact on data. Since 2016, there are over 2 trillion posts and 250 billion photos uploaded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has a wealth of personal data and its 2.2 billion users share data every second of the data. This would be impossible if it weren’t for the development of big data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;With big data analytics services, businesses will find it easier to present information, make predictions, and create innovative solutions. When using it, make sure that the data is accurate so that it runs properly. Thus, big data analytics is a necessary skill that will become more demanded in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=1afd59692adb" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/the-3-vs-of-big-data-analytics-1afd59692adb"&gt;The 3 V’s of Big Data Analytics&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Salt Edge updates API -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77864/salt-edge-updates-api?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Salt Edge announced the release of a new version of its unified Open Banking Account Information API...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Seizing the open banking opportunity -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/videoarticle/2025/seizing-the-open-banking-opportunity?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Eli Rosner, Chief Product and Technology Officer, Finastra, speaks at Money20/20 ASIA in Singapore a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 10:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: PSD2 and consumer credit: how will open banking impact the market for unsecured loans? -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16919/psd2-and-consumer-credit-how-will-open-banking-impact-the-market-for-unsecured-loans?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>15 months after open banking launched in the UK, consumer understanding of what it means remains low...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:20:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: ICO Invites Applicants to GDPR Sandbox -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/ico-invites-applicants-to-gdpr-1/</link><description>Beta phase will see 10 organizations given help with  data protection compliance</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Kyyba Innovations launches Detroit Fintech Challenge -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77866/kyyba-innovations-launches-detroit-fintech-challenge?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Kyyba Innovations, in partnership with TechTown Detroit, launches the second series of "Detroit Fint...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 17:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Lenders without border walls -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/lenders-without-border-walls</link><description>Some fintechs have figured out how to provide international students and immigrants with credit cards and loans. Machine learning makes the underwriting possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 01:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: EBAday 2019 zones in on fintech -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33614/ebaday-2019-zones-in-on-fintech?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Finextra and the Euro Banking Association are inviting startups from across Europe to apply for one...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: NatWest trials money management app -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33611/natwest-trials-money-management-app?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>UK bank NatWest is trialling a standalone personal finance app that uses AI, data analytics and Open...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian technology: Google employees call for removal of rightwing thinktank leader from AI council -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/01/google-kay-coles-james-removal-employees-letter</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Staffers criticized the appointment of Heritage Foundation president Kay Coles James in a letter published on Monday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of Google employees have called for the removal of a rightwing thinktank leader from the company’s new artificial intelligence council, citing her anti-LGBT and anti-immigrant record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;Related: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/28/big-tech-ai-ethics-boards-prejudice"&gt;'Bias deep inside the code': the problem with AI 'ethics' in Silicon Valley&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/01/google-kay-coles-james-removal-employees-letter"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: By 2023, 50% of gov’t IT workers will occupy roles that don’t exist today -  Puntaje: 3600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/2023-new-jobs-government-it/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_669170671-1-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_669170671-1-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_669170671-1-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Gartner, Inc. predicts that by 2023, 50% of the roles that government CIOs will oversee do not exist in government IT today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recent Gartner CIO survey shows that the transition to digital government is gaining momentum. It found that 53 percent of digital initiatives in government organizations have moved from the design stage to early stages of delivering digitally driven outcomes. This is up from 40% last year. Additionally, 39% of governments expect cloud services to be a technology area where they will spend the greatest amount of new or additional funding in 2019. “These findings demonstrate that leadership has become more comfortable with cloud delivery models and has moved away from concerns regarding security and data ownership,” said Cathleen Blanton, research vice president at Gartner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The move to digital business means that the IT organization needs to adapt to new skills requirements,” Ms. Blanton said. “In many governments, roles of chief data officers and cloud architects are already present. However, it is worth noting that 38% of government respondents did not introduce any new roles in 2018 due to insufficient resources, skills and cultural issues.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To adapt to new skill requirements, CIOs need to initiate a transformation process that results in new or changed roles. For example, as cloud services become more prevalent, the number of data center management roles will decline. Furthermore, the emergence of digital product management is changing how governments think about their services, and this will lead to the emergence of digital teams internally to design and deliver products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the future, government IT will also accomplish more diversified tasks than today. Public sector agencies will rely on government IT services to address inclusion, citizen experience and digital ethics. Those fields require new types of skillsets, such as researchers, designers and social scientists. “Government CIOs must employ experts to model and explain how citizens and businesses will need to respond to regulations and policies, and what impact that will have on society, the economy and government revenues,” Ms. Blanton said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, government IT will need to assign new roles to support their digital transformation and introduce emerging technologies in diverse businesses and mission areas. As artificial intelligence (AI) and Internet of things (IoT) technologies advance, machine trainers, conversational specialists and automation experts will slowly but certainly replace experts in legacy technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything-as-a-Service on the Rise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gartner predicts that by 2023, over 80% of new technology solutions adopted by governments will be delivered and supported using an anything-as-a-service (XaaS) model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XaaS summarizes several categories of IT, including those delivered in the cloud as a subscription-based service. It also encompasses managed desktop, help desk and network services, voice over IP and unified communications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Adoption of XaaS models is increasing across all industries globally – primarily driven by cloud services - and government is no exception,” said Alia Mendonsa, senior director analyst at Gartner. “The model offers an alternative to legacy infrastructure modernization and investment. It’s a promising way to scale digital government, because it can provide small local offerings as well as nation-wide services.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the XaaS model also creates new challenges for government CIOs. In the early stages of adoption, business units may turn less to the IT department to deliver solutions, as they are now able to acquire XaaS solutions without the involvement or the resources of IT. This is a dangerous endeavor as departments often lack the knowledge to negotiate complex contracts and individual departments may be independently acquiring duplicative capabilities already offered centrally. Furthermore, as-a-service contracting is still immature and often offers weak service levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For this reason, CIOs must educate business units about the risks associated with this type of contracting and need to take an active role in negotiating these contracts wherever possible,” Ms. Mendonsa said. “Without the support and experience of their IT organization, an XaaS solution can create significant risks to the organization and the citizens it serves.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/2023-new-jobs-government-it/"&gt;By 2023, 50% of gov&amp;#8217;t IT workers will occupy roles that don’t exist today&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 08:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Manchester to be test bed for finger vein payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33618/manchester-to-be-test-bed-for-finger-vein-payments?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Manchester has been chosen as the global launch city for finger vein payments system, Fingopay.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Global Demand Grows For Instant Payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/today-in-data/2019/faster-payments-real-time-p2p/</link><description>Woody Allen once supposedly said 80 percent of success is just showing up. Beyond that, in business and in life, showing up on time counts for a lot, too. So it is with payments, where speed counts. The movement toward faster payments and peer to peer (P2P) is, well, quickening. As the Faster Payments Tracker shows, the clamor […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Curve showcases AR payment pilot -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/curve-showcases-ar-payment-pilot/</link><description>Comes with a showcase of the tech in a cool video.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:04:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Police Freeze Accounts, Seize Luxury Cars in Probe of ICO Promoter Vanbex -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/police-freeze-bank-accounts-seize-luxury-cars-in-probe-of-22-million-ico-promoter-vanbex</link><description>Canadian police have frozen assets of the founders of Vanbex, as part of a fraud probe into the firm's $22 million ICO.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 04:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Coconut joins RBS bail out queue -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33612/coconut-joins-rbs-bail-out-queue?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Current account and bookkeeping app Coconut is the latest fintech startup to apply for a slice of th...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 10:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: United Arab Emirates to Host Blockchain Aviation Conference in Abu Dhabi -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/united-arab-emirates-to-host-blockchain-aviation-conference-in-abu-dhabi</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yNzY4MjgzNDFkYWNmZjg2YmFjZTNmOWQ4NjJmNjE5My5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abu Dhabi is gearing up to host a blockchain conference dedicated to the aviation industry this week&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 13:53:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker News: Thousands of Unprotected Kibana Instances Exposing Elasticsearch Databases -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~3/2w0P4pvV0r8/kibana-data-security.html</link><description>In today’s world, data plays a crucial role in the success of any organization, but if left unprotected, it could be a cybercriminal’s dream come true.

Poorly protected MongoDB, CouchDB, and Elasticsearch databases recently got a lot more attention from cybersecurity firms and media lately.

More than half of the known cases of massive data breaches over the past year originated from unsecured&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~4/2w0P4pvV0r8" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 08:22:58 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Decentralized Platform Launches New Features as Demand for Crypto Lending Increases -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/decentralized-platform-launches-new-features-as-demand-for-crypto-lending-increases</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80OTk0ZDMzNTFjZDA0NTQ5ZTRmMGM2M2I4ODY5YTg0Zi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decentralized crypto lending platform has expanded the range of stablecoins that can be used for collateral as demand for loans rises #SPONSORED&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 11:25:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: 10 Fintechs Stand a Chance to Present Their Solutions to Singapore’s Investment Industry -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29819/roboadvisor/accelerator-imas-singapore-investment-fintech-wealth-management/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A Singapore industry group representing the city&amp;#8217;s asset management firms, IMAS, has launched an accelerator programme which could position 10 Fintechs to present their solutions in front of leading VC&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29819/roboadvisor/accelerator-imas-singapore-investment-fintech-wealth-management/"&gt;10 Fintechs Stand a Chance to Present Their Solutions to Singapore&amp;#8217;s Investment Industry&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 05:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: The SEC Wants to Hire a ‘Crypto Securities’ Advisor -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/the-us-sec-is-hiring-a-crypto-specialist-legal-advisor</link><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is looking for an attorney advisor to help develop a plan for digital and crypto securities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 10:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bitcoin Cash, Litecoin Futures Volumes Top $150 Million at Kraken Exchange -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bitcoin-cash-litecoin-futures-volumes-top-150-million-at-kraken-exchange</link><description>Kraken's Crypto Facilities has seen trading volumes in litecoin and bitcoin cash futures surge five-fold in recent weeks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 09:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Speak Out: Discussing the Top Cryptocurrencies -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/speak-out-discussing-the-top-cryptocurrencies</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81OWQ4OWNjOTExOGRiN2Y1MTliNWE4YWVhM2Y1ZGU2OC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the next major cryptocurrency and why? Reply&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Morgan Stanley focuses on data quality to strengthen AI -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/morgan-stanleys-new-data-strategy-for-higher-quality-ai</link><description>The bank is one of many to realize that artificial intelligence is only as good as the data fed into it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Pakistan Plans New Digital Currency Regulations Following FAFTA’s Urging -  Puntaje: 2100</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pakistan-plans-new-digital-currency-regulations-following-faftas-urging</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9iYTk1YmJkM2Q0M2Q4OTkyY2MwNTRhMzIwY2RhODVjOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;After almost a year of cryptocurrency being formally illegal, Pakistan plans to implement a new licensing scheme for electronic money institutions&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 09:21:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: Capital One Treasury Head: AI and ML Driving Customer Experience Improvements -  Puntaje: 4200</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/04/capital-one-treasury-head-ai-and-ml-driving-customer-experience-improvements/</link><description>Phil Beck, Head of Treasury Management at Capital One, is almost a year into his job at the McLean, Virginia-based bank, where his focus has been getting commercial banking up to speed with the digital economy. This entails transforming legacy platforms, products and capabilities into industry-leading technologies and approaches using a mix of artificial intelligence, [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>