<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:47:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Fortune: Wells Fargo and Mastercard CEOs Still Skeptical About Blockchain’s Impact -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://fortune.com/2019/03/28/wells-fargo-mastercard-blockchain/</link><description>They're just not sure its value is as great as supporters say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Wall Street Blockchain Alliance adds Donna Redel to advisory board -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77835/wall-street-blockchain-alliance-adds-donna-redel-to-advisory-board?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Wall Street Blockchain Alliance (WSBA), an industry leading non-profit trade association with a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: OKEx Founder Reveals OK Group’s Partnership With US Trust Firm, Plan to Launch Stablecoin -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/okex-founder-reveals-ok-groups-partnership-with-us-trust-firm-plan-to-launch-stablecoin</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hNjQ0MTFlNjUwNzk5MGMzMTE3OGM4YWRiNjU5NWIyZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;OKEx, OKCoin founder Star Xu announced OK Group partnership with blockchain-focused trust company, allowing the firm to launch its own compliant stablecoin&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC finance: Wells Fargo, Mastercard CEOs say blockchain has yet to live up to the hype -  Puntaje: 500.0</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/28/wells-fargo-mastercard-ceos-say-blockchain-has-yet-to-live-up-to-the-hype.html</link><description>The top executives at Wells Fargo and Mastercard, which are experimenting with blockchain, say the technology has yet to pay off.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: BofA, Wells Fargo sour on blockchain -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/bofa-wells-fargo-sour-on-blockchain</link><description>They haven't thrown in the towel yet, but comments by top executives at the two big banks suggested that their interest in finding financial services uses for distributed ledgers is wearing very thin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: AlphaPoint Appeals to Institutions With Security Token Tech Upgrade -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/alphapoint-appeals-to-institutions-with-security-token-tech-upgrade</link><description>Blockchain services firm AlphaPoint has upgraded its tech solution for security token offerings in bid to attract institutional clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Digix is launching DigixDao Platform, Joining Ranks of Pioneering Decentralised Autonomous Organisations in Singapore -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/28/digix-is-launching-digixdao-platform-joining-ranks-of-pioneering-decentralised-autonomous-organisations-in-singapore/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/28/digix-is-launching-digixdao-platform-joining-ranks-of-pioneering-decentralised-autonomous-organisations-in-singapore/"&gt;Digix is launching DigixDao Platform, Joining Ranks of Pioneering Decentralised Autonomous Organisations in Singapore&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/lAU5IAkA_400x400-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/lAU5IAkA_400x400-150x150.jpg 150w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/lAU5IAkA_400x400-300x300.jpg 300w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/lAU5IAkA_400x400.jpg 372w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" data-attachment-id="32336" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/28/digix-is-launching-digixdao-platform-joining-ranks-of-pioneering-decentralised-autonomous-organisations-in-singapore/lau5iaka_400x400/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/lAU5IAkA_400x400.jpg" data-orig-size="372,372" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="lAU5IAkA_400x400" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/lAU5IAkA_400x400-300x300.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/lAU5IAkA_400x400.jpg" /&gt;Digix, creator of the world’s first asset-backed digital gold token, will launch its DigixDAO platform, joining the ranks of some of the first Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAO) in the world. From March 30, anyone who owns Digix&amp;#8217;s DGD tokens can contribute and vote on proposals to grow and improve the Digix platform. Digix, a platform [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/28/digix-is-launching-digixdao-platform-joining-ranks-of-pioneering-decentralised-autonomous-organisations-in-singapore/"&gt;Digix is launching DigixDao Platform, Joining Ranks of Pioneering Decentralised Autonomous Organisations in Singapore&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Ledger, Legacy Trust to Offer Institutional Custody of ERC-20 Tokens -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/ledger-legacy-trust-to-offer-institutional-custody-of-erc-20-tokens</link><description>Hardware wallet maker Ledger and Hong Kong-licensed Legacy Trust now provide custody for crypto assets including ethereum-based tokens.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Marco Polo blockchain network used for commercial transactions -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33602/marco-polo-blockchain-network-used-for-commercial-transactions?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Marco Polo blockchain trade finance network has successfully navigated unchartered territory, fa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: First transactions carried out on blockchain-based Marco Polo network -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/first-transactions-carried-out-on-blockchain-based-marco-polo-network/</link><description>Delivery triggers irrevocable payment from buyer’s bank.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Goldilocks and the Three Blockchains -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/goldilocks-and-the-three-blockchains-7fa911de81c2?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h4&gt;A Fairytale Search for the Sweet spot of Centralised/Decentralised&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*3p_xQfIDW6uDO-wHCKJAVA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was an enterprise named Goldilocks. She visited a house in the woods in search of the perfect blockchain porridge- one that was both fast, affordable and scaleable, &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; decentralised enough to ensure an uncorruptible, trustless, immutable record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And while she already loved Bitcoin porridge, she dreamed of a blockchain that was rich enough for all the applications she could dream of…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First, she tasted the Ethereal blockchain porridge:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Mmmmmm… this blockchain is so delicious with decentralisation” she said. “If only it was faster. And who exactly are the development team? I want some customized support and special Goldilocks features.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next, she tasted the Hyperledgereal blockchain porridge:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Oh goody”, said Goldilocks. “These people cooked my blockchain especially for me! They make updates whenever I want and it’s so fast. But hang on, who’s blockchain is it anyway? This doesn’t seem very decentralised at all- so why exactly am I using a blockchain again?”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So, poor Goldilocks was left hungry. Although there were plenty of options on the menu, no single blockchain porridge could satisfy her.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“I feel caught between a block &amp;amp; a hard place”, she said. “Is it so much to ask- to have my Proof-Of-Stake &amp;amp; Sweeten it too?”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poor puns aside, &lt;em&gt;where is the ‘Goldilocks’ of centralised/decentralised?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, here are three projects that strive to take the best aspects of both extremes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/113/1*SVOBiU5qkY5hlf6Ol1SAgQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://somee.social"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SoMee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Short-form social media hub on the blockchain. &lt;em&gt;“Social Media Redefined”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br&gt;This project combines the rapid development of a centralised company with the uncensorable nature of posting to a blockchain. The project is partnered with Steemit, which offers a complementary platform for long-form content. SoMee offers users ownership over their data, rewards them for engagement, and acts as a hub for multiple social media platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/135/1*_j6_bzy_C32duwSfzY5LLg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://unification.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;A blockchain of blockchains. &lt;em&gt;“Ethereum for Enterprise”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br&gt;This project offers enterprises/governments the reliable speed and cost of running a permissioned network (a ‘WRKChain’), while demonstrating these have not been tampered with by committing the header of each block to a public ‘MainChain’. Use cases being built out range from Insurance Providers to Electronic Healthcare Records, Smart City Management to Governmental Stablecoins.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/130/1*G-rcBwuG2Hn4SEC1OYbi-Q.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ceek.com"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ceek VR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Virtual Reality music, sports, learning and arts, powered by the blockchain. &lt;em&gt;“Your Ultimate Front Row Experience”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br&gt;While the central company films and provides experiences in dedicated VR studios, the distributed network of connected powerful computers (MasterNodes) relay near-instant streams to all audiences to ensure high quality content delivery. This architecture ensures reliable delivery of resource intensive content that is secure, protected, censorship resistant and throttle-proof.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d love to introduce Goldilocks to each of these projects to help her with her dilemma. While I know these three well as I have some involvement with each of them, there are certainly more out there that attempt to bridge the best of both worlds- the centralised and the decentralised. May the two be married, and live happily ever after…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which other projects do you know that are walking this tightrope?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=7fa911de81c2" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/goldilocks-and-the-three-blockchains-7fa911de81c2"&gt;Goldilocks and the Three Blockchains&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 15:23:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Combining Blockchain and File Storage Might Just Decentralize the Internet -  Puntaje: 25200</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/combining-blockchain-and-file-storage-might-just-decentralize-the-internet-d94c2701a8fa?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*bxevWuHYOJQRKaNW" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eric Wang is a co-founder at the Archon Cloud, a blockchain-based file storage system, where he leads research and other efforts.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: This article describes the emergence and potential impact of file storage systems based on blockchain technology. Blockchain-based File Storage (BFS) is a promising alternative to both centralized storage and non-incentivized P2P file systems. If BFS can overcome the many usability and technological challenges it faces, it can potentially become the de facto storage infrastructure, catalyzing a decentralized internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is recent focus on decentralized systems because they promise new classes of applications free from intermediaries, create new economies of scale and offer unprecedented user control of data. Smart contract functionality offers users the ability to create applications that grant these advantages. With this tool in hand, people increasingly romanticized a new internet known as the decentralized internet (or web3), where apps will be even more powerful and spectacular than they are now. Decentralized applications would be developed over an infrastructure of economically secured blockchain systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It soon became apparent that, as “decentralized operating systems”, blockchains cannot themselves handle applications more resource-hungry than Cryptokitties without improving many things. These events created a public frenzy to innovate and improve on decentralized infrastructure, so that useful decentralized applications could be produced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, the blockchain by itself is a very poor storage apparatus. One of the important realizations was that one cannot store files economically on-chain [1]. Indeed, a ledger shared by thousands of users, where each piece of data is replicated amongst each user is not practically capable of hosting data beyond the megabyte scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Therefore, many important developments within decentralized systems should and do happen outside the blockchain — certain layer 2 solutions, private P2P networking solutions, storing files etc. The actual blockchain and other separate components sum up to form the decentralized internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/822/0*YseaRvSyVl-g7Otv" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The web3 stack&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although decentralized systems are potentially revolutionary, not many people will join the decentralized internet if the technology sucks, which means that the decentralized tech stack can’t be that much worse (barring the interesting property of decentralization) than existing solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, no part of the stack is complete, with the DNS, storage and computing layer development being especially early. A typical mantra is “we will build a DApp using a blockchain to take advantage of blockchain immutability etc., and even if we have to store our files in some centralized location it’s OK” [2].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I argue that though it’s possible to build an “application” on top of blockchain that receives solid adoption, these applications aren’t “decentralized applications” without their data being loaded and exchanged in a trustless, decentralized manner. In other words, these are interesting applications on other merits, but not necessarily because they’re truly decentralized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This brings me to my core thesis:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blockchain-based File Storage -&amp;gt; Decentralized Data -&amp;gt; Decentralized Internet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;BFS will be the candidate to serve as a backbone to web3. I will reinforce my claim that BFS catalyzes a decentralized internet through &lt;em&gt;decentralizing data&lt;/em&gt;. Because without truly decentralized data, there aren’t true Dapps, and without true Dapps there is no decentralized internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A secure, fair, economically-driven BFS has many potential benefits over other storage solutions, both in general and for web3 infrastructure. I will also analyze substantial technological and business barriers towards achieving mass spread popularity for BFS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Centralized Cloud Storage begins to dominate the market (1990s-present)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the 1990s, files were stored in and served from local servers and people would simply request data directly from other distinct computers. Although people were able to fully control and serve files on their own, setting up these servers well required extensive experience in networking, cybersecurity, as well as, time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This initially didn’t seem to be much of a problem, as the entire Internet was only about 1.5TB by 1997 and the combined value of the Internet was not nearly as large as it is today. A popular belief at the time can be summarized well by a well known computer scientist: “There may be a few thousand petabytes of information all told; and the production of tape and disk will reach that level by the year 2000” [3].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paradigm changed over the following years, as computer-to-computer interactions generated far more data than humans themselves could and much of this data was very useful for consumers as well as enterprises who found new ways to generate results from data such as in artificial intelligence, ultra high definition video and financial modeling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The demand from users to store, handle and analyze this data became increasingly important and difficult to handle on their own. As of 2018, there is now ~32 total ZB (that’s 32,000,000,000 TB) of data generated annually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s where Amazon comes in. As Amazon began establish itself as &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; major player in the e-Commerce business, they realized that they had developed a huge set of in-house APIs and infrastructure to handle a huge amounts of data for their business. Soon, Amazon teams built an entire internal collection of software to help their various divisions save months of time from not needing to worry about infrastructure [4]. In 2006, Amazon S3 and EC2 were unveiled, heralding the age of the centralized cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cloud gave users easy access to Amazon’s powerful collection of tools and began to dominate the storage needs of many businesses due to its simplicity and power. Amazon (followed by Microsoft, Google and “private” clouds like Facebook) gained increased control of the data on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individual users lost sovereignty and the ability to control their own data. With ~1 point of failure, various large data holders became victim of increased data breaches, data loss and high profile server downtimes cost businesses billions of dollars in lost revenue, as well as lost human knowledge and liberty. This, coupled with an increased understanding that large centralized cloud holders might be able to violate personal and business privacy, sparked an &lt;em&gt;ideological and practical&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;movement&lt;/em&gt; against data centralization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a component of the decentralized internet, then, Amazon S3 is as an enticing choice at first glance due to its simplicity and power. Numerous DApps currently use such services to bootstrap their products, promising decentralized data in the future, or they may argue that one can have a decentralized application without decentralized data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, I argue that data centralization is a fundamentally crippling problem that renders applications or infrastructure hosted on the centralized cloud (~1 point of failure) to be not decentralized. The internet is simply a bunch of computers transferring files to each other. Centralized storage enables centralized data, which enables a centralized internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/500/0*81zqBrvWIastkeOB" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In corollary, good decentralized storage ensures the legacy of the decentralized web. Even if many other components of the web3 stack are attacked, data can always eventually be retrieved/communicated later in a trustless manner. Even the public chains themselves are not that decentralized without decentralized storage, since it is very likely that the majority of blockchain full nodes are hosted on very few centralized cloud storage solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralized storage enables decentralized data&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;A challenger emerges: Peer-To-Peer file storage (2001-present)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peer-To-Peer file storage emerged as an alternative to centralized clouds without the ideological and practical dangers of centralization. Five years before Amazon S3, BitTorrent already paved the way by allowing files to be shared amongst peers efficiently. Peer-to-peer applications eventually accounted for ~50% of internet traffic in 2009. Although BitTorrent allowed people to share files with one another, it was not suited to store and discover these files in the same way as Amazon S3 or Dropbox would allow you to; it does not function well as a file &lt;em&gt;storage &lt;/em&gt;solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IPFS builds on the milestones of BitTorrent to develop a real peer-to-peer, decentralized file storage system. In IPFS, all files are united within one swarm, where there is a common language in a united file system, and all peers are shared within the entire system which allows people to discover and transfer files to each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organizations such as the Internet Archive and many DApps began to experiment and use IPFS to store their files to advertise more of their stack as decentralized. For many initial experimental use cases, IPFS was more than sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because IPFS unites peers in one system (where peers can discover each other through what’s called a distributed hash table (DHT)), there is a common language of communication through the IPFS protocol and there is no central point of failure, IPFS is a truly decentralized candidate for the storage backbone of a new decentralized internet. Surely enough, many well known DApps such as OpenBazaar and Augur use IPFS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There, unfortunately, are fundamental problems that prevent IPFS from expanding significantly beyond the realms of community projects and open source enthusiasts. Here are the most pressing ones:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Files in IPFS are distributed to more nodes the more they are accessed, but because there is no major incentive for nodes to hold files beyond philanthropy, less accessed files will disappear over time. This already makes many commercial applications such as long term archives of videos and old blockchains infeasible.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Although the DHT backbone makes it very efficient for peers to discover each other and find files in IPFS, DHTs are insecure for file discovery. This means that malicious attackers can, for example, prevent you from finding a particular file with relatively little effort.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many projects have patched the first issue by wrapping files in IPFS nodes hosted by centralized Amazon S3 computers. This means that there are some Amazon S3 nodes that you will host yourself over time to guarantee the existence of your file on IPFS (as long as Amazon itself works as intended). However, there once again is the problem of centralization, defeating the purpose of using IPFS in the first place. To make decentralized data good, what we need is a way to take inspiration from such systems but add an incentive layer as well as stronger security guarantees to make a decentralized data feasible at the same scale as centralized data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain-based File Storage holds promise (2020+)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public blockchains use cryptographic incentives and punishments to steer untrusted user behavior towards a desired consensus. Therefore, an ideal BFS with a strong cryptographic incentive system underpinned by other parts of a decentralized tech stack, such as a secure alternative to DHTs, seems to solve both problems that prevent IPFS from being the de-facto decentralized internet infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;For a decentralized internet, an ideal file storage solution is equal to if not better than a centralized one, but also decentralized.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a good scenario, each storage provider in the network has large amounts of storage space to provide and their storage and bandwidth can be efficiently cryptographically guaranteed. BFS enabled innovations and completely new uses of technologies such as erasure coding, proofs of storage and proofs of space. There are many innovative players coming into the scene and dozens of projects with various approaches to innovate both on the technology and product fronts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The collection of individuals and participating professional storage providers adhering to the rules of a blockchain can eclipse the reach and power of any centralized company&lt;/em&gt;, even a behemoth like Amazon. Beyond just data exchange without intermediaries, blockchain-based solutions introduce many advantages:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Allows you to control your own data and is censorship resistant&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;With cryptographic incentives, nodes will be economically punished if they do not store and serve data. Corporations and even governments will find it hard pressed to take down files when they have such high fault tolerances. Because of decentralization, there is no middleman (like Google/AWS) who manages the data on your behalf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Are very resistant to crippling black swan events and file downtime&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By storing shards of the file, either through traditional slicing or erasure codes, there are many hosts who hold a file. If there are enough nodes then natural disasters, human/computer error, and coordinated attacks should be very difficult to affect the system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Have potential performance benefits over centralized systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because many nodes store smaller parts of the file, downloading a file can be parallelized. Like in BitTorrent, where parallelized downloads can be many times faster than normal downloads from a centralized cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. Are likely very cheap and creates new economies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Storage and data are considered by many to be a commodity, and large amounts of hard disk space is empty. Storage providers can monetize their hard drive assets for useful purposes. Because the cost to store files is very little beyond the initial purchase cost of the hard drive itself, there is very little overhead costs to host files — storage providers are essentially generating pure profit. Existing solutions have demonstrated the wild cost savings to the user: Sia costs approx. &amp;lt;$2/TB/month compared to S3, which costs $23/TB/month with its standard offering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a decentralized internet, an ideal file storage solution is equal to if not better than a centralized one, but is also decentralized. BFS stands to have performance users expect from centralized entities, and the decentralization people adored from IPFS. The main problems that centralized solutions had all stemmed from the fact that they’re centralized. In other words, &lt;em&gt;an ideal BFS is an ideal file storage solution&lt;/em&gt;; it should move the substantial mass of people who care about decentralization away from centralized solutions towards using decentralized data since there is relatively little sacrifice to be made in the migration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain-based File Storage has a lot of problems yet to solve&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous sections have built an argument regarding the potential benefits that BFS might have over IPFS and centralized solutions. In reality, the two most popular production-level storage projects combined literally store thousands of times fewer petabytes of data in 2018 than large cloud providers did in 2016, and the total stored capacity in cloud storage is expected to grow significantly over the coming years. After discussing with many individuals within blockchain as well as traditional enterprises and businesses, I reached the conclusion that there is much to do before a decentralized internet can put centralized solutions out of business. Amazon S3 and others have features and optimizations, as well as usability that currently cannot be matched by blockchain-based solutions or IPFS. We will examine both &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;usability&lt;/em&gt; issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/347/0*nz2mJcHWJR0XEYWR" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Blockchain-based File Storage systems are still in their youth&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon S3 currently has significant advantages in both upload/download performance as well as having a much wider feature set.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per upload, decentralized solutions might always have some inefficiencies compared to centralized solutions. Generally, uploads are handled through decentralized marketplaces marketplaces, where storage providers and storage “buyers” need to be matched in some manner. This provider/buyer matching and communication process, as well as the slower speed of individual nodes compared to enterprise-level centralized computers, is the upload bottleneck. To upload files to a particular person, one often needs long initialization time (upload latency) the first time he/she uploads a file to that person (in the form of some sort of storage contract verified posted on-chain); alternatively, one might first post and allow a file upload transaction (where buyers and sellers are matched) to be included in a verified block per file, which can take a few seconds to minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some solutions such as parallelized uploading, where different shards or pieces of files can be uploaded to different nodes at once to maximize connection bandwidth, long term buyer-provider contracts, batched off-chain buyer/seller matching and storage negotiations that can be reclaimed later on-chain (layer 2 solutions) and faster consensus/more efficient block propagation are underway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockchain scalability is also an issue preventing blockchain systems from increasing its capacity. A back of the envelope calculation shows that if each Tx specifies a 50MB file to be stored and there are 25 storage transactions per block, which is generated every 30 seconds, then the total system can store ~1.3Exabytes of data annually, which pales in comparison to what large cloud providers are currently storing. In addition, there are many other bottlenecks like slow Proofs of Storage that would prevent the system from achieving the calculated maximum capacity. Layer 2 and other scalability solutions can help with the problem, but cryptographic proofs need to also be more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Downloads speeds also suffer similar problems as uploads, where download speed and latency issues are caused by buyer/provider matching and communication, as well as the speed of individual nodes are called into question. Downloaders can pre-pay for downloads (Sia, Storj), or pay for them on demand, per-download (Filecoin). The per-download method utilizes buyer-seller matching and payments each time, which can take longer than centralized solutions even if the process was done off-chain. Solutions to these problems are similar to solutions for uploads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, there is the wealth of features that blockchain-based solutions do not have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, currently in all solutions I’ve seen, every downloader must be a registered user within the blockchain and generally has to own tokens, whereas in the centralized cloud, everybody can browse content on their browser or app without any knowledge that they are using the cloud (this is also a usability issue, of course). Current solutions give users the ability to encrypt a file client side but since transactions are public, onlookers can see that pseudonymous addresses are sending hashes of particular files to each other. This can be very tricky for certain companies like genomics companies who might not want others to know whom they are sending data to and any public info about the data (not even the hash).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, it is incredibly difficult to design efficient proofs that storage providers have the files they’re supposed to store (Proofs of Storage), or that they are uploading files as they should (Proofs of Upload). In addition, professional services that enterprises have come to expect like guaranteed. Service-Level Agreements (SLAs) and file permissioning (who can view which file) are difficult to implement. Most features are at a very early stage of development (we are ~20% of the way there before feature sets are comparable to centralized).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Usability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Usability in the context of BFS and blockchains themselves are a larger barrier of entry than any other issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of integration into blockchains and additional payment choices are big problems. BFS are generally siloed away from the DApp user’s public chain of choice. For example, Filecoin, 0Chain, Sia have their own blockchains. A DApp user does not want to navigate the complex rules of a completely new chain and learn about staking and behaviors etc. to upload a file. Cross-Chain integration and cross-chain payments can be used to make this much easier. For example, a NEO Dapp user (who probably has some NEO and gas tokens) on the NEO blockchain can pay Gas tokens to upload a file through an easy to plugin upload API, which works fine whether the BFS is native to NEO itself or simply has some oracle or cross-chain integration to NEO. Ideally, all of the dynamics of token payments are made to be as intuitive as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, the generally bad user experience when trying to use a file comes into play. For example, whether you’re an uploader or a downloader, in Filecoin and Sia you must currently download an entire blockchain, which takes hours. Then, you generally have to have an account on an exchange and be able to understand cryptocurrencies and wallets to just view a file. This is in stark contrast to Amazon S3, where you can manage all your uploads through a web interface, and all downloads are so abstracted away from the end user that they don’t even realize where the file is coming from on their browser until Amazon crashes and takes down massive parts of facebook and other parts of the internet with them. Clearly, solutions allowing for more abstraction of user experience away from cryptocurrencies and blockchain are needed to make the user experience comparable to a centralized cloud. One solution is to put the complexities of crypto and payments all on the uploader’s side, so that the downloader can use a simple JS module on their browser view decentralized data without installation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, the lack of tools to migrate data from centralized cloud solutions encumbers the switching process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The virtuous cycle of Blockchain-based File Storage and the decentralized internet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decentralized internet promises types of data exchange without intermediaries. This enables new uses of web applications that improve on existing applications, or completely new applications that were never before possible. As Olaf Carlson-Wee of Polychain Capital said, “I think we’re going to be comparing, or port rather, web 2 things on to this web 3 or decentralize user-owned web, but that overtime, we’ll find those web 3 native applications, those are the things I really care about even though right now they do sound somewhat sci-fi and I think it’s very unclear what they look like” [5]. Having a tool to store and share these pieces of data, whether it’s archived blockchains, front end data, metadata or large multimedia files is crucial to this type of data exchange and to the very idea of decentralization. Though BFS systems are works in progress, let us lavish on them the attention they deserve and build on them to make them the products they can be. Blockchain-based file storage is no longer just a buzzword, but represents a large piece of a solution to a problem many in society desperately wants solved, IF it is also fairly convenient to do so. This convenience comes in the form of a future decentralized solution as powerful and easy to use as centralized ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/762/0*yXRjDOMXffTWYOv5" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Blockchain-based File Storage catalyzes adoption of the decentralized internet&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralized data makes the decentralized internet&lt;/strong&gt;. As mentioned previously, the internet is simply a connection of computers that store and transfer data to each other through some sort of communication protocol. Decentralized data is then the trustless, decentralized way of storing and sharing the data. As of this writing, there are 32 million blockchain wallets; these are millions of users already taking advantage of decentralized communication protocols (gossip protocol, Tor etc.) and trustless ways to verify data (blockchains themselves). However, there are barely any truly working+adopted+decentralized apps. A powerful storage layer is the missing component.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether the decentralized internet will completely replace the centralized internet depends on whether adoption of BFS can cause an exodus from centralized services (figure above, B), and the results remain to be seen. Since increased participation in decentralized storage is in essence increased participation in a new decentralized internet, in the process of trying to solve this problem, &lt;strong&gt;we may have inadvertently created a storage system that is simply better than existing solutions&lt;/strong&gt; for society’s evolving needs, resulting in a &lt;em&gt;virtuous cycle&lt;/em&gt; (figure above, A) that allows even more people to join the decentralized internet. Nonetheless, there are many problems that remain to be solved before the virtuous cycle can occur, which is what projects like the Archon Cloud is focused on. I hope this article serves as a solid introduction to Blockchain-based File Storage and its importance. Stay tuned for future articles that will describe specific BFS solutions people like us are working on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to Sam Suh from Archon for helping me with my writing style and editing the document and Andrew Lee of Web3Journal for reviewing my work.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am a co-founder at a Blockchain-based File Storage company.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sources:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[1] &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@didil/off-chain-data-storage-ethereum-ipfs-570e030432cf"&gt;https://medium.com/@didil/off-chain-data-storage-ethereum-ipfs-570e030432cf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[2] &lt;a href="https://blog.wavesplatform.com/web3-0-the-road-ahead-for-waves-9bd8a51f63ce"&gt;https://blog.wavesplatform.com/web3-0-the-road-ahead-for-waves-9bd8a51f63ce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[3] &lt;a href="https://courses.cs.washington.edu/courses/cse590s/03au/lesk.pdf"&gt;https://courses.cs.washington.edu/courses/cse590s/03au/lesk.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[4] &lt;a href="https://techcrunch.com/2016/07/02/andy-jassys-brief-history-of-the-genesis-of-aws/"&gt;https://techcrunch.com/2016/07/02/andy-jassys-brief-history-of-the-genesis-of-aws/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[5] &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9SYVX2wcMVM"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9SYVX2wcMVM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=d94c2701a8fa" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/combining-blockchain-and-file-storage-might-just-decentralize-the-internet-d94c2701a8fa"&gt;Combining Blockchain and File Storage Might Just Decentralize the Internet&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:11:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japanese Court Acquits Man Accused of Cryptojacking -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japanese-court-acquits-man-accused-of-cryptojacking</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85ZGNhY2EyYWYzY2YwMjcyNTRhZjE5YWI4MWExMGVjYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Japanese court has ruled to acquit a man who was illicitly mining crypto after embedding Coinhive on his website&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Speak Out: Discussing Your Experience in Crypto -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/speak-out-discussing-your-experience-in-crypto</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xYWYwZTUzNWNmZWMxYjU0MWNhNDhmYzY2MjE4MzkwYy5wbmc=.png"&gt;&lt;p&gt;How adventurous is your crypto experience? Got an interesting story to share? You are welcome here.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Kraken Ramps Up Security With Enforced 2FA and Dedicated Lab -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/kraken-ramps-up-security-with-enforced-2fa-and-dedicated-lab</link><description>Crypto exchange Kraken is embarking on a security drive, introducing compulsory two-factor authentication and a dedicated security lab.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 06:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Binance CEO CZ: Fake Volume Reports Are Useful for Crypto Industry to Move Forward -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-ceo-cz-fake-volume-reports-are-useful-for-crypto-industry-to-move-forward</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8wY2I2YjQ5NmY4OGI2YmI1ZDkzZjY1ZWVhMGZlNjEwYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binance CEO CZ says that recent reports on fake trading volumes are useful for transparency in the crypto industry&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Crypto Startup TokenPay Buys Equity Stake in Heidi Klum Lingerie Maker -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/crypto-startup-tokenpay-buys-equity-stake-in-heidi-klum-lingerie-maker</link><description>TokenPay is turning ICO proceeds into equity investments, this time with a stake in lingerie company Naked Brand Group.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Crypto 2.0, accessibility, and Apple’s future strategy -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/AkDtnuFFvCo/</link><description>From Extra Crunch Jon Evans has a comprehensive look at the most compelling futures for “Crypto 2.0.” With the trading frenzy out of the way (at least for the time being), engineers and product designers can now get back to the real world of improving these systems. Digital accessibility expert Beth Franssen has a piece [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Swiss Watchdog Rules Crypto Miner’s ICO ‘Seriously Violated’ Laws -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/swiss-watchdog-rules-crypto-miners-ico-seriously-violated-laws</link><description>Switzerland's finance regulator has found that crypto mining firm Envion's $90 million ICO took deposits from investors unlawfully.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Bitcoin Bear Market Diaries Volume 12 Marty Bent -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/bitcoin-bear-market-diaries-volume-12-marty-bent-20a4df0e224d?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/619/1*1D9IoUZRVcYTHtTkgkkwog.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@piratebeachbum"&gt;Bitcoin Bear Market Diaries&lt;/a&gt; are a series of interviews featuring various important voices and perspectives in the Bitcoin ecosystem. Each interviewee was carefully selected and asked the same group of questions. The main goal was to provide the world with a collection of commentary and opinions on the state of the current Bitcoin and crypto market. Some of the names you will recognize while others don’t wish for the limelight but have great insight and experience we all can learn from.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;These interviews are raw and unfiltered with no agenda other than giving each individual their opportunity to speak their mind. If you like what you see, please share with your friends. If something offends you, you should probably X out and find another crypto fluff piece that gives you warm fuzzies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MartyBent"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marty Bent&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a long time Bitcoiner and is best known for his daily Bitcoin newsletter and podcast &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TFTC21"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tales from the Crypt&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; that recently featured Twitter and Square Cofounder and CEO &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/jack"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jack Dorsey&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Marty is an extremely knowledgable and articulate person that everyone should be paying attention to.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/400/1*dhfvb6QtrA-XDoT2EE4rmA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MartyBent"&gt;Marty Bent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Country&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;United States&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do people know you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoiners probably best know me from my daily newsletter about Bitcoin, Marty’s Ƀent, and my podcast, Tales from the Crypt, which includes an interview series with people interested in Bitcoin hosted by myself and a weekly topical news show called Rabbit Hole Recap that I co-host with Matt Odell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long have you been into Bitcoin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too long&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best Bitcoin experience?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s a hard one. To get cheesy, the best Bitcoin experience has been the journey it’s taken me on for many years now. Forcing me to question my beliefs about many things, pushing me into subjects I never thought I would explore, and introducing me to some of the smartest, most passionate people I have ever met in my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One particular experience of mine that still gives me goosebumps when I think about it was an “oh shit, this is crazy” moment I had while traveling. I budgeted very poorly and quickly ran through my allotted funds like a high time preference freak. Luckily, I acted preemptively, created a wallet, moved some BTC to it before leaving for my trip, and wrote the seed phrase down on the tiniest piece of paper. Stranded in a foreign land with no funds and in a pinch, I downloaded an Electrum wallet on a friend’s computer, used the seed from the tiny tear of paper to recover my wallet, and moved some funds to an account associated with a debit card I had for this specific emergency. I felt an incredible sense of security and power in that moment. Using 12 words to conjure money via software that is free and open to anyone in the world. That was MY money and only I could conjure it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worst Bitcoin experience?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following David Seaman in the early days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you think is Bitcoin’s biggest threat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A solar flare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your thoughts on the various Bitcoin forks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Very uninteresting up to this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are you optimistic about in this space?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m very optimistic about UX improvements in multisig wallets/schemes in the very near future. This has been a very unappreciated and under-adopted feature that a user(s) has when using Bitcoin and I believe the lack of adoption as been a UX problem up to this point. Vast improvements are on the way that will give Bitcoin users more certainty and peace of mind when holding bitcoin. Ultimately, this will make the “$5 wrench attack” less likely as potential attackers would be dissuaded from targeting users engaged in multisignature schemes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, Schnorr signatures, as they will help provide material gains in efficiency, scalability and fungibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biggest regret during the last bull market?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting caught up in the euphoria. It’s something you tell yourself you’re not going to do when we’re in the depths of the bear market (as we are now), but it’s hard not to get sucked into all the hype.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What have you learned during the current bear market?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot more people earnestly dedicated to helping Bitcoin succeed than I would have imagined. I was expecting many more people to be washed away with the price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the biggest fail you have seen during the bear market?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People clinging to ideas + projects that the market has rejected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you think helped trigger the current bear market?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immaturity of the infrastructure, i.e., glitching of exchanges and mempool backup, compounded by overt scams and euphoria that wasn’t representative of the underlying fundamentals. Smart money saw this and took gains. Newer, overextended retail money experienced some volatility for the first time, panicked, and dumped. Likely locking in losses and precipitating the bear market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What kind of damage do you think latest price drop has done to buyer sentiment?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It depends what someone bought. With that being said, there certainly hasn’t been enough damage to stop another retail-led rally. A string of green candles will cause people to develop amnesia real quick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you feel about the current state and future of lightning network?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cautiously optimistic. A lot further along than I thought it would ever be at this point. Though, most of the journey is still ahead of us though. There’s still a lot of things to test, implement, and battle harden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your thoughts on HODLing Bitcoin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think it’s the logical thing to do if you believe Bitcoin has a chance at achieving its goal of providing the world with a distributed, peer-to-peer cash system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are you thoughts on alt-coins?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are inevitable and provide cover and research for Bitcoin, but also lure in unsuspecting greater fools with siren calls of a “better Bitcoin”. They are a double edged sword.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you hold any? If not, why?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I do hold some privacy-focused alts, but they don’t make up a material percentage of my holdings and I am not as worried about Bitcoin’s fungibility issues as I was when I acquired them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What kind of impact do you think the radical drop in alt-coins will have on their future?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most, the same impact that has historically affected alts that experience a radical drop, zombie-fication that allows a new crop to enter and churn the “top” alts that follow in Bitcoin’s wake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thoughts on the notion of bitcoinization?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think it’s happening. Slowly but surely. The number of people who are deciding to trade their work or fiat for BTC only seems to be increasing, precipitating bitcoinization at a slow pace, but a pace nonetheless. And even with that being said, the pace of bitcoinization is different depending on where you find yourself on this rock we call Earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Bitcoin startups are you excited about?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Startups with a security focus, particularly around multisig custody. And gaming startups utilizing unique monetization paths enabled by BTC/LN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What “crypto influencers” do you think get it wrong and why?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who take themselves too seriously and refuse to adapt their views in spite of overwhelming evidence that contradicts their position. Some people need more humility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What “crypto influencer” do you think get it right and why?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hate the phrase “crypto influencer”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s it going to take for this bear market to turn around?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green candles and forced adoption via survival + wealth preservation mode being enabled for some people in certain parts of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How bullish are you on Bitcoin despite this recent pullback.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More bullish than I’ve ever been.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any tips you want to give to people new to Bitcoin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make sure you understand the gravity that comes with a world in which Bitcoin succeeds. It is a disruptive force that could potentially be met by an opposing, coordinated force in the future. Be prepared for that reality. I believe wholeheartedly that Bitcoin will be a net positive for the world, but it will obsolete a lot of entrenched power in the process of accruing a massive amount of value, and that entrenched power may not be all too pleased about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best tips for storing Bitcoin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Practice. Diversify your holdings among multiple storage methods. Aim to develop a web of trust you can set up multisig schemes with to help protect yourself and your bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name some of your favorite information sources and/or podcasts in the space.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twitter is my #1 source of information. I’ve been curating a list for years that provides me with a wealth of knowledge and links in a continuous stream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any last words of wisdom?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t be afraid to join the fray.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@piratebeachbum"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stay tuned for the next Bear Market Bitcoin Diaries. You can find more volumes and articles here!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=20a4df0e224d" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/bitcoin-bear-market-diaries-volume-12-marty-bent-20a4df0e224d"&gt;Bitcoin Bear Market Diaries Volume 12 Marty Bent&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:46:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Compliance officers wary of switch to 'Wild West' crypto sector -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/technology/compliance-officers-wary-of-switch-to--wild-west--crypto-sector-11388324</link><description>NEW YORK: After almost three decades in senior compliance roles at large financial firms including Bank of New York Mellon's Pershing and Goldman Sachs Group, Jeff Horowitz made an unconventional career move.

In July he became chief compliance officer at cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, taking a ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:14:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Android Trojan “Gustuff” capable of targeting more than 100 global banking apps, cryptocurrency and marketplace applications -  Puntaje: 2500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83005/malware/android-trojan-gustuff.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Security experts at Group-IB have detected the activity of Gustuff a mobile Android Trojan, which includes potential targets of customers in leading international banks, users of cryptocurrency services, popular ecommerce websites and marketplaces. Gustuff has previously never been reported. Gustuff is a new generation of malware complete with fully automated features designed to steal both fiat [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83005/malware/android-trojan-gustuff.html"&gt;Android Trojan “Gustuff” capable of targeting more than 100 global banking apps, cryptocurrency and marketplace applications&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: Microsoft Hails “Significant” Disruption of Iranian APT Group -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/microsoft-significant-disruption-1/</link><description>Redmond's Digital Crimes Unit seizes 99 phishing sites</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : Tidying Expert Marie Kondo: Cybersecurity Guru? -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/tidying-expert-marie-kondo-cybersecurity-guru/d/d-id/1334271?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>The "KonMari" method of decluttering can be a huge step toward greater security, according to a growing number of executives.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:20:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Exiger appoints Julie Peck COO -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77836/exiger-appoints-julie-peck-coo?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Exiger, the leader in the provision of technology-enabled regulatory, financial crime, risk, and com...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian technology: Huawei poses national security risks, says UK watchdog -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/28/huawei-chinese-firm-poses-national-security-risks-says-uk-watchdog</link><description>&lt;p&gt;NCSC report casts doubt over Chinese firm’s future involvement in telecoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government-led watchdog set up to vet Huawei products has given a damning report on the cybersecurity risks posed by the Chinese company’s involvement in the British telecommunications industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/huawei-cyber-security-evaluation-centre-oversight-board-annual-report-2019"&gt;annual report&lt;/a&gt; published by the Huawei oversight board, which is chaired by the head of GCHQ’s National Cyber Security Centre, said it has found further “significant technical issues in Huawei’s engineering processes leading to new risks in the UK telecommunications networks”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/28/huawei-chinese-firm-poses-national-security-risks-says-uk-watchdog"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Analysts Claim CoinBene Transactions, Recent Activity ‘Consistent’ With Exchange Hack -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/analysts-claim-coinbene-transactions-recent-activity-consistent-with-exchange-hack</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82N2VjMTU2ZWQ2ZmFhMzc4NTA3ODJmYjJkNGIzZjVlMS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elementus analysts have identified $105 million leaving crypto exchange Coinbene’s wallets, arguing that patterns are “consistent with how exchange hacks commonly play out”&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Lazarus APT continues to target cryptocurrency businesses with Mac malware -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82985/apt/lazarus-targets-mac.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;North Korea-linked Lazarus group made the headlines again, it has been leveraging PowerShell to target both Windows and macOS machines. The North Korea-linked Lazarus APT group made has been leveraging PowerShell to target both Windows and macOS machines in a new wave of attacks. The discovery was made by experts at Kaspersky Lab, the campaign [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82985/apt/lazarus-targets-mac.html"&gt;Lazarus APT continues to target cryptocurrency businesses with Mac malware&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 08:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Remitly taps Visa to let users send cross-border payments to debit cards -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33608/remitly-taps-visa-to-let-users-send-cross-border-payments-to-debit-cards?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>US mobile money transfer outfit Remitly has teamed up with Visa to let Americans send funds to debit...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: PayIt, a payments platform designed for public services, raises $100M+ from Insight Partners -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/KtLVVDLstmw/</link><description>Government services, for many, epitomize the worst of bureaucracy: they are, at their low point, large, lumbering organizations working under strained budgets, staffed by lifer employees who don&amp;#8217;t get much say in improving things, and lots of paperwork. But as ageing public information infrastructure grinds to a halt and public services start making the switch [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Finovate Alumni News -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-967/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Around the web Motive Partners closes investment in Finantix announced in December. Since launching in the region last year, Plaid expands coverage in Canada, adding support for Desjardins, National Bank of Canada, President&amp;#8217;s Choice, and Simplii. NDGIT’s API platform enables UBS to deliver PSD2 APIs for TPPs. Ledger partners with Hong Kong-licensed Legacy Trust to introduce institutional-grade custody &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-967/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-967/"&gt;Finovate Alumni News&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Capabilities to be built on- Blockchain Payment Platform -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16899/capabilities-to-be-built-on--blockchain-payment-platform?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Across the globe, banks are adopting to new technology for secured Banking in payments area. As Corp...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Why I quit my Medium membership -  Puntaje: 2400</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/why-i-quit-my-medium-membership-909909657ba?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h4&gt;Medium does not pay writers from less developed nations but has no qualms about taking our money&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*fOWATLwJE0QRsr4bwr4fYw.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fiction&lt;/strong&gt;: This maps shows countries where Medium pays writers (via Stripe), and includes India.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a Medium member based in India. This morning, I realized the credit card linked to my Medium account is due to expire. So I go to the settings page in my Medium account to check if I can update my card details. I find the button saying ‘Use a new card’ but also notice another button that says ‘View billing history.’ Out of curiosity, I click on it, and am presented with a long list of $5 monthly payments starting from March 24, 2017. Two years, or 25 months to be precise. Which add up to $125 (₹8,645) in membership fees, as of today. That makes me pause, and take stock of what I’m getting for my $125.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/795/1*xOQaB1fO5CrU-653SpIh_g.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Discriminating by where you live&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium has a partnership program that pays writers on the platform. This program only pays writers located in 23 countries, which are mostly wealthier nations. Writers living in the less developed parts of the world don’t get paid because Medium’s payment partner, Stripe, does not offer its services there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, Medium avoids paying writers purely based on where they live. That’s just not right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A year ago, I wrote a post offering suggestions on how to find a workaround to pay writers outside Medium’s charmed circle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/indian-thoughts/is-medium-trying-to-make-the-rich-richer-f47d10217b50"&gt;Is Medium trying to make the rich richer?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium claimed to be working at resolving the issue. But a year has gone by since that previous post of mine, and there’s absolutely no progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;The deafening silence of double standards&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having two standards for writers on Medium who pay the same membership fees is blatantly unfair. What’s particularly damning is Medium’s deafening silence about the issue of these unpaid writers. I went through the Medium’s own &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@MediumStaff"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;. There’s not even a mention or discussion about unpaid writers. It’s like we don’t exist. This would imply Medium is aware of the issue, but hoping it will go away if they keep ignoring it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assuming Medium is really unable to pay writers from these blacklisted countries, then why not reward them in some other way?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a suggestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Writers from blacklisted countries should have their ‘claps’ evaluated in the same way as their luckier non-blacklisted counterparts in the US. When or if that value equals $5, it should be used to pay their monthly membership fee for the next month. Anything above $5 can be credited to their account, and paid when Stripe sorts out its payment issues. It may not be much, but it’s at least a good gesture on Medium’s part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now if I could come up with that thought without even pausing my typing, I’m sure the boffins at Medium should be able to do better. If not, fire them and hire someone with brains, and make sure they have a heart too!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve always believed in the natural goodness of people. I feel if people have a choice, they usually do the right thing. So when Medium said they were trying to sort out the issue, I gave them the benefit of doubt, and continued paying my membership fees for two whole years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;The good, the bad, and the Medium&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;My relationship with Medium began in 2015. I came upon the site purely by chance, and straightaway fell for its unique blend of clean design and ease of writing and publishing. I liked the platform so much that I posted a whole bunch of articles over the next year, and wasn’t too bothered if anyone read it or not. At that point of time, Medium hadn’t as yet introduced membership fees or put up the paywall. So money didn’t come into the picture. In fact, there wasn’t really anything in it for me except the joy of writing whatever I wished, like this &lt;a href="https://medium.com/publishous/we-found-the-ipod-thief-3000-km-away-9933d53aba72"&gt;story of a stolen iPod&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three years later, my stats on Medium say I have written 323 stories. Since Medium labels my responses/comments on stories as individual stories, my guess is the real number of my published stories would be closer to 200.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s still a fair bit of writing and shows my involvement with the platform. Like any business, I know Medium needs an income to survive. I also realize that Medium is trying to do something that hasn’t done before, so there are bound to be mistakes. So I have not been worried about their changes of direction. Like when they initially allowed advertising on the platform to generate revenue, but later reversed their decision and moved away from advertising towards a paywall. Most of all, I find it commendable how they have worked out a system to pay writers from the monthly fees of Medium members. The ‘clap’ system isn’t perfect but I’ll give Medium points for trying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What I don’t appreciate about Medium is the above-mentioned discrimination. Why do they do it? Did things change once Medium started making money from its membership fees? As the song goes, ‘Money changes everything.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Incompetent Partner&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium has tied up with a payment platform called Stripe to pay its writers. When you try to join the Medium Partner Program (through which Medium pays writers), you will be directed to Stripe, which claims to be available in 32 countries. Of these, 23 are developed countries. Users in those nations can use Stripe for their financial transactions without any restriction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India appears in a second list and is even there on the Stripe’s map of countries that it’s active in (see title image). This seems to imply that users can get a Stripe account ‘invite’ on request. That is deceptive as I’ve requested Stripe for an invite several times over the last year. Forget invite, I have yet to even receive an acknowledgment of my many requests from Stripe. If you ask me, Stripes&amp;#39; ‘invite’ is pure eyewash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*t__qo-k54W8TWMUuJIW0Jg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;India has countless freelancers in diverse fields who take on jobs from companies based outside India, including the US and Europe. They get paid using the many financial platforms that are available. I have &lt;a href="https://medium.com/indian-thoughts/is-medium-trying-to-make-the-rich-richer-f47d10217b50"&gt;covered this subject in detail&lt;/a&gt; in my previous post written more than a year ago. Since then, many more options have sprung up to transfer funds to India. This includes Google Pay, which incidentally Stripe uses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of my neighbours, an elderly lady, has a daughter who lives in London. Twice a week, the daughter has fresh groceries delivered to her mother in India, while paying for it from London. If an individual can do this, why is it so hard for Medium to make regular payments overseas? More to the point, if Stripe can’t arrange payments to India, they must be extremely incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is what makes me skeptical about Medium’s choice of a partner. Is Medium unaware of how incompetent Stripe is? Or is Medium deliberately sticking with Stripe to have an excuse to avoid paying writers in India and elsewhere?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Fool me twice, shame on me&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enough is enough. Doing the math today, made me pause. Two years is a long time to resolve an issue, and $125 isn’t peanuts for someone living in India. There’s a difference between giving Medium the benefit of doubt and being gullible, and I suspect I’m in the second category.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wrote &lt;a href="https://medium.com/indian-thoughts/is-medium-trying-to-make-the-rich-richer-f47d10217b50"&gt;my previous post&lt;/a&gt; on this issue a year ago, at which point I had already paid Medium membership fees for a whole year. Since then, I have paid up a second year of membership fees, and I’m still swallowing Medium’s line of ‘working on it.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the old saying goes, ‘Fool me once, shame on you; Fool me twice, shame on me.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My patience has run out, and it’s time to consider my options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Option 1: Get a proxy&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;I do have a simple workaround to get paid. Just ask someone based in US or any of those other 23 countries to collect Medium writer payments on my behalf, by registering their bank account number on my Medium account. In fact, my brother who lives in UK volunteered to do this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m lucky I have a trustworthy resource who is willing to do this for me. But what about the other writers who do not have access to such resources? Not to mention the fact that my brother will have an additional headache while filing his tax returns. So I thanked my brother, and said no.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium needs to pay all writers, and I’m not giving them an easy way out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Option 2: Get a Stripe business account&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I first found that Medium wasn’t paying writers outside the US, I wrote to Your Friends@Medium. They suggested I use a Stripe business account.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/744/1*YygKaZWUE-CSTl76OeNhiQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, there’s a catch. It’s horrendously expensive. I checked this out when I wrote my &lt;a href="https://medium.com/indian-thoughts/is-medium-trying-to-make-the-rich-richer-f47d10217b50"&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt; a year ago, and I’m sure the figures will still be similar or probably higher. Here, let me quote from my earlier post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;You basically need to start a US company, which comes at an incorporation cost of US$500, a running cost of $25 per month, a yearly fee of $100 for an agent, plus other sundry costs like $349 for legal advice, and $250 for tax preparation.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a ripoff. Let’s move on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Option 3: Cancel my Medium membership&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Option 1 &amp;amp; 2 are not working for me. So canceling my membership seems to be the only way forward for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;What do I lose by canceling my membership?&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;How will canceling my Medium membership affect me? Medium has clearly stated that if a writer wants to get paid, he or she has to become a Medium member. That argument is irrelevant, as Medium is anyway not paying me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How will I be affected as a reader on Medium? To be frank, I have no idea. Like I said, I began writing on Medium before the paywall came up, and was a member after the wall rose. So I don’t know what life beyond Medium’s paywall feels like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From what I vaguely recall, non-paying members are restricted to three articles a month. I’m sure there are loopholes to get around this restriction, but why take the trouble to do that? Far easier to look elsewhere for good content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What else? There’s a possibility Medium could kick me out for publishing this post filled with unpatriotic thoughts about the mother platform. It’s a good idea to always be prepared for the unexpected. Hang on for a moment, while I back up all my posts on Medium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Advertising blues&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;At one point, advertising was the preferred source of income for any enterprise on the net. But the world turned against ads once they started popping up all over the place, driving readers crazy, influencing editorial, and incentivizing companies like Facebook to steal our private data, and change the course of history. That led to the rise of ad blockers and the like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium seems to be riding this anti-advertising wave when it decided to remove all advertising from its platform. Personally, I think it’s a good thing, though it does cut off a valuable source of revenue for Medium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My point is Medium’s paywall was inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Paywalls are the future&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook is still making &lt;a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2019/01/30/facebook-confirms-plans-merge-messenger-whatsapp-instagram-messages/2727200002/"&gt;billions from ads&lt;/a&gt;, which means advertising is adapting to survive in a changing world. But Facebook’s change of focus towards merging and encrypting its three messaging platforms (WhatsApp, Instagram and Facebook Messenger) seems to indicate Facebook knows change is inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google has shown how our data can be used responsibly. I have been using Google products for many years, and they have enriched my life in many ways, without misusing my data, fingers crossed. The search engine Duck Duck Go has also shown how advertising based on ‘search keywords,’ is a viable business, though not as wildly profitable as data sharing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However the fact is people are becoming reluctant to trust ads, and more open to the idea of paywalls. Publications like NYT have been successfully doing it for a while now, and many more have joined or will be joining soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So yes, paywalls are trending, and sooner or later, I’m going to have to subscribe to a paywalled publication if I want good reading content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Medium is like a second car&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a reading cum paid-writing platform, Medium gets my vote and my money. But if I’m an unpaid writer, then ‘writing’ goes out of the equation, and Medium is in a different ballgame. Medium will have to compete for my $5 with other publications, purely based on the quality of its ‘reading content.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I agree Medium has great original content, but it can’t be my first choice. To use a metaphor, Medium is more like a second car than your everyday workhorse, and I speak as a writer on Medium, who loves the platform. (Point to note: lots of people manage with just one car.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take the just launched Apple News app. From what I hear, it’s managed to include some of the world’s top publications and will cost $10/month in the US. It may take a while to reach India. My guess is it may launch for as little as $2/month* in India. Why would any reader pay $5 for Medium’s content when they can get Apple’s far richer content at around the same price?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Here’s how I arrived at that $2/month pricing estimate for Apple News. India is an extremely price-sensitive and complex market. A look at the music industry is quite revealing. Apple Music in India costs costs just $1.75/month (₹120) as against $10/month in the US. Even at this price, Apple Music is barely competitive. Spotify’s Premium version costs ₹129/month, while the basic Spotify is free. JioSaavn has a free version for users of the Jio cellular network, while JioSaavn Pro version costs ₹99/month, which is the same as Gaana and Wynk. Then there’s Amazon Music. I subscribed to this at ₹1000 or $15/year (₹129 or $2 /month) because it’s part of the Amazon Prime package deal, which also includes the usual free delivery for Amazon Prime shopping, movie/ video streaming on Amazon Prime Video, books on Kindle, and more. I must add that Apple has learned this lesson the hard way, with its exorbitantly priced iPhone having a minuscule 1% of India’s cellphone market. As for ‘news’ itself, it’s highly subsidized in India. My 16-page hard copy of India’s leading English daily newspaper, ‘The Times of India,’ costs me ₹120 ($1.75)/month.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Time to take a stand&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;To sum up, I don’t lose much by canceling my Medium membership. I can still write and publish (and not get paid) as usual on Medium. Reading will be a pain with the three articles a month restriction. I’ve heard there are loopholes to get around that, like visiting via Medium’s Twitter page. Even so, the constant nags to sign up for a Medium membership will be a major irritant. I’m seriously tempted to just pay up by the $5 and stay inside the paywall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No pain, no gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium needs fee-paying writers like me, more than we need Medium. So if more fee-paying writers stop paying (hint, hint!), Medium is more likely to get their act together and do the right thing. As they say, money talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not holding my breath. On April 24, 2019, my next payment to Medium will be due, and it will bounce as I don’t plan to update the expired credit card linked to my Medium account. And Club Medium is going to lose a member.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After all, if I don’t stand up for myself, who will?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=909909657ba" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/why-i-quit-my-medium-membership-909909657ba"&gt;Why I quit my Medium membership&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Checks and cash on the way out: Fintech in -  Puntaje: 8800</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/checks-and-cash-on-the-way-out-fintech-in/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_606090050_optimized-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_606090050_optimized-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_606090050_optimized-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Words By: Business Insider (abridged version) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital-only banks are redefining retail banking, open banking is pushing fintechs and legacy players to tap into customer data for more personalized services, and online transactions are swelling from widespread digitization. And these trends will continue at breakneck pace as more financial institutions up their digital capabilities and digital-only upstarts gain a greater foothold in the marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Insider Intelligence Head of Content Shelagh Dolan (SD) recently spoke with Daniel Van Dyke (DVD), Director of Research, Financial Services, at Business Insider Intelligence, where he leads Business Insider Intelligence’s Payments, Fintech, and E-Commerce coverage areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHELAGH DOLAN (SD): WHAT ARE SOME OF THE EMERGING MARKETS YOU'RE WATCHING FOR FINANCIAL SERVICES INNOVATION?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DVD: Recently, I’ve been most interested in Brazil, China, Kenya, and India. And not coincidentally, these were featured in a recent report of ours which highlighted key global regions for payments. Each region is interesting for different reasons; Brazil has a robust and growing card market, China is the global leader in mobile wallets, Kenya is the birthplace of mobile money, and India is experiencing a rapid government-prompted pivot from cash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SD: WHAT ARE SOME OF THE MOST MATURE MARKETS FOR FINANCIAL SERVICES?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DVD: On the developed side of things, other than the obvious (US), I’d highlight Australia, Sweden, and the UK. Australia is a market where government initiatives and regulations are driving payments change, Sweden is a great example of a post-cash society, and the UK is leading the way with contactless card adoption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SD: WHAT ARE SOME NEW FAST-GROWING PAYMENT TYPES TO WATCH?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DVD: IoT payments are about to have a moment. And by “IoT payments” I mean retail, person-to-person, or bill payments through connected televisions, connected cars, wearables, and smart speakers. In total in the US, we project volume through those categories to more than triple from $20 billion in 2018 to $62 billion by 2023, on the back of rising consumer usage of those devices as well as growing consumer familiarity with voice commerce.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SD: ARE THERE ANY PAYMENT TYPES WE’LL SOON BE SEEING A LOT LESS OF?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DVD: Checks, although New York landlords seem to have missed the memo. And cash, although regulation and holdouts (looking at you, bodega operators) will make it a slower death. We also predict slower forms of ACH (Automated Clearing House) to drop off as faster payments take their place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SD: WHAT'S THE MOST INTERESTING DIGITAL FEATURE YOU'VE COME ACROSS?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DVD: On the banking side of things, I’d point to account aggregation, which is the ability to view multiple accounts, credit cards, and other financial accounts in one portal. It’s been around for a long time, but it’s catching on now thanks to strong customer demand, increasingly powerful budgeting use cases, and international open banking regulations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SD: WHAT ARE SOME OF THE MOST POPULAR DIGITAL FEATURES WITH CONSUMERS? WHAT ARE THE MUST-HAVES?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DVD: People love security features. Of the 30-odd features I mentioned, the three that came out on top in our survey are the ability to turn a card on or off temporarily, the ability to tell your bank that you’re travelling in mobile banking, and the ability to file a card transaction dispute. 2018 was a massive year for data breaches, and that could be part of what’s behind the high demand for safety-related capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/checks-and-cash-on-the-way-out-fintech-in/"&gt;Checks and cash on the way out: Fintech in&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 06:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: Can a computer tell you when you're going to die? -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/can-a-computer-tell-you-when-youre-going-to-die</link><description>Everyone is faced with the prospect of death, though not knowing when the time will come can be unsettling for many. Now, researchers have uncovered a disturbing benefit of artificial intelligence – the ability to more accurately predict a person's demise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: New York Fed launches fintech advisory group -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33600/new-york-fed-launches-fintech-advisory-group?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Federal Reserve Bank of New York has set up a fintech advisory group, bringing together expertis...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC business: Artificial intelligence used in kitchen bin -  Puntaje: 500.0</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-47708059</link><description>Can technology help to cut the vast amounts of food that never gets eaten?</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: ING takes academic approach to AI -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33607/ing-takes-academic-approach-to-ai?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Dutch bank ING is teaming up with the Delft University of Technology (TU Delft) to build an artifici...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro News: Future wars will be waged with robots. But so might future peace  ǀ View -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/euronews/en/home/~3/bYp9M5JkfXo/future-wars-will-be-waged-with-robots-but-so-might-future-peace-view</link><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) usually makes headlines for all the wrong reasons. [...] At the United Nations we have been exploring completely different scenarios for AI: its potential to be used for the noble purposes of peace and security.&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/euronews/en/home/~4/bYp9M5JkfXo" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:57:59 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian technology: Can we stop robots outsmarting humanity? -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/28/can-we-stop-robots-outsmarting-humanity-artificial-intelligence-singularity</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The spectre of superintelligent machines doing us harm is not just science fiction, technologists say – so how can we ensure AI remains ‘friendly’ to its makers? By Mara Hvistendahl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&lt;em&gt;t began three and a half billion years ago in a pool of muck, when a molecule made a copy of itself and so became the ultimate ancestor of all earthly life. It began four million years ago, when brain volumes began climbing rapidly in the hominid line.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fifty thousand years ago with the rise of Homo sapiens sapiens.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/28/can-we-stop-robots-outsmarting-humanity-artificial-intelligence-singularity"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 06:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Exclusive: UAE is the Silicon Valley for education -  Puntaje: 6000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/exclusive-uae-is-the-silicon-valley-for-education/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_531229720-min-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_531229720-min-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_531229720-min-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Radical changes are being welcomed as the world breathes in innovation. With the rampant growth of technology comes the need to prepare the students of today for job opportunities of tomorrow. The UAE education sector is keeping pace - smartboards are replacing blackboards, tablets are replacing textbooks, and everything from the content of education to methods of delivery, timings, and assessments are being reimagined. The potential for businesses catering to the sector is immense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Kiran Tangri, the President and Co-founder of Kalebr Americas Corporation, shared her thoughts exclusively with AMEinfo on hidden opportunities in the education sector, the growth of online education, the impact of technology on education, "future-proofing" the education and the importance of women empowerment!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Education is the foundation upon which a country is built, and it is only through the power of quality education that we can help the next generation of leaders reach their full potential," said Kiran Tangri.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key trends and hidden opportunities in the GCC education sector&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiran Tangri: A key trend in the education sector for the UAE and the GCC will be the use of AI to provide customized learning practices, to help save educators’ time in the classroom and to introduce more skilled educators in the classrooms. AI will be the equalizer that will be able to make a good teacher push their boundaries and become great. AI models trained on the characteristics, actions and teaching practices of the best teachers will assist in equalizing the quality, efficacy and personalized focus that the learners need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A move away from traditional, subject-specific lessons through reworking the concept of the timetable is also a trend that we have noticed in the leading schools that we've worked with. The hidden opportunity here is to effectively utilize time and help teachers as well as learners to adopt innovation and well-being in schools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, companies are embracing shorter work days and there is evidence to suggest that employee productivity increases as a result of this concept. It's encouraging to know that this model can thrive in the education sector and help improve teaching and learning: a win-win situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Competitive strategies in the face of a growing online education industry&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiran Tangri: I don’t consider the online education industry a threat. I believe the traditional education industry players can benefit from the endless opportunities that are currently available online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest challenge in education is for educators to produce content in a social-media friendly format that speaks to the digital natives.  We also need to consider equitable access to this content, to equip educators with the tools they need and to hone students’ skills. Content has been the driving force in the traditional education industry model and will continue to be the key differentiator in the online industry model. The latter industry, however,  is at the forefront of solving content delivery challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Online delivery models provide a major opportunity to promote effective teaching practices, create powerful content and facilitate masterclasses, nano degrees, and how-to tutorials. Any established or traditional education industry player who welcomes the best-practices of the online education industry will be sustainable and competitive: a force to reckon with. What's more, the physical premises may be transformed into dynamic collaborative learning spaces for teamwork and skill-certification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technological advancements revolutionizing the education experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiran Tangri: In the teaching and learning spaces, technology has contributed to making learning more exciting and accessible. It has also allowed educators to create differentiated learning pathways and enabled thought-leaders to share global evidence-based practices through social media.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technology has also worked wonders in terms of experiential learning or hands-on learning. STEAMathalon is a specific example of how a mindful approach to technology is revolutionizing the education experience. STEAMathalon provides a framework for promoting innovation and well-being through real-world challenges in a competitive, exciting play-based innovation league. It is an initiative borne out of pilot programmes that were implemented in Canada and Finland to promote an inclusive environment similar to future workplace settings, whereby learners tackle real-world challenges and deal with a tangible setup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These challenges span across fintech, space, sustainability, wearable fashion and health-care to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teams collaborate to design and prototype their ideas whilst using AI to power their final product, IoT to receive real-time performance data and AR/VR for enhanced real-time end-user product experience. The ideas could take on various forms: a satellite model, a smart car model, a connected plant habitat, a drone with sensors, autonomous ships model or even well-being clothing. The possibilities are endless. This is the future of education which is being made possible due to technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investment in the UAE education industry&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiran Tangri: The education sector in UAE is similar to the tech sector in San Francisco: it's constantly evolving. In many ways, it is like the Silicon Valley for education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is possible thanks to the investor-friendly policies from the government, the ease of operating businesses, accessible regulatory bodies and decision makers, and finally, close proximity to high-growth markets. What also helps is a large number of private schools in the region that are willing and able to try innovative solutions, implement the best practices and embody the true spirit of the nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simply put, the UAE is definitely a prime location if you are in the education sector.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Future-proof" education&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiran Tangri: It is imperative. We must acknowledge that in the future, it will become incredibly challenging to know everything or stay in-step with all the changes around us. We must ask ourselves: how quickly can we learn, how well can we work in groups and how well can we manage learning fatigue?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to nurture and grow human capital for sustainable growth in the future, we must invest in honing future trade-specific skills in AI, IoT, Blockchain, VR, quantum computing or prevalent technology of the time. We must also improve 21st century skills such as collaboration, critical thinking, creativity and. communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we must also focus on self-care and well-being. This will help us immensely. We'll be able to contribute directly to the knowledge-based economies by excelling in group-based projects and effectively collaborating with each other. We'll also be equipped with a fast learning curve and be able to avoid work-related fatigue or burnout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The future is uncertain, unseen.  That doesn't mean we can't prepare for it. We must future-proof our young learners and prepare the next generation workforce for whatever lies ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Women in leadership&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiran Tangri: It is crucial. We are increasingly seeing female leaders inspire people around the world. They are now leading in positions that were previously reserved for men. New Zealand’s Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern, Vogue's iconic editor-in-chief Anna Wintour, General Motors’ CEO Mary T. Barra, filmmaker Patty Jenkins, and Indian entrepreneur Nita Ambani are remarkable female leaders representing diverse sectors across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is vital for young women to have a female role model as much as it is imperative for young males to be accustomed to women in a position of power. It fosters equality, respect, and a level playing field. Through Kalebr Americas Corporation, we ensure our content, products, and organizational practices reflect these principles and values, always.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[caption id="attachment_1381775" align="aligncenter" width="683"] Kiran Tangri, Co-Founder and President of Kalebr Americas[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/exclusive-uae-is-the-silicon-valley-for-education/"&gt;Exclusive: UAE is the Silicon Valley for education&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: How Localized Payments Give Lime A Leg Up In Rental Scooter Race -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/payments-innovation/2019/rental-scooter-localized-options/</link><description>After an influx of investors turned the rental scooter market into a multibillion-dollar industry, startups in the space are clamoring for capital and customer loyalty. Players like Bird, Juice Bike and Spin are all revamping their approaches to user design and comfort in a world where loyalty can be hard to win. Rental scooter services […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Top Cap and Delta Cap: New Metrics for Spotting Bitcoin Price Trend Reversals -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/top-cap-and-delta-cap-new-metrics-for-spotting-bitcoin-price-trend-reversals</link><description>Cryptocurrency researchers Willy Woo and David Puell released several new valuation metrics for bitcoin's price in February. Here's an overview.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 02:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: ASUS fixes supply chain of Live Update tool hit in Operation ShadowHammer -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82997/hacking/asus-operation-shadowhammer.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;ASUS released security patches to fix the issues in the Live Update utility that were exploited by threat actors in Operation ShadowHammer. ASUS announced to have released a fix for the Live Update utility that was exploited by threat actors behind the Operation ShadowHammer to deliver malware to hundreds of users.  The Operation ShadowHammer took [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82997/hacking/asus-operation-shadowhammer.html"&gt;ASUS fixes supply chain of Live Update tool hit in Operation ShadowHammer&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 07:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: CoinAcquiring adds cryptocurrency-friendly bank accounts -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77840/coinacquiring-adds-cryptocurrency-friendly-bank-accounts?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>CoinAcquiring today announced the addition of cryptocurrency friendly bank accounts to its growing p...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Cluley: Office Depot fined millions for tricking customers into believing their PCs were infected with malware -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://hotforsecurity.bitdefender.com/blog/office-depot-fined-millions-for-tricking-customers-into-believing-their-pcs-were-infected-with-malware-21021.html#new_tab</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://hotforsecurity.bitdefender.com/blog/office-depot-fined-millions-for-tricking-customers-into-believing-their-pcs-were-infected-with-malware-21021.html#new_tab" title="Office Depot fined millions for tricking customers into believing their PCs were infected with malware"&gt;&lt;img width="100" height="100" src="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/tune-up-thumb-150x150.jpeg" class="attachment-100x100 size-100x100 wp-post-image" alt="Office Depot fined millions for tricking customers into believing their PCs were infected with malware" style="float: right; margin-left: 10px; margin-bottom: 10px;" srcset="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/tune-up-thumb-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/tune-up-thumb-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/tune-up-thumb-45x45.jpeg 45w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/tune-up-thumb-190x190.jpeg 190w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/tune-up-thumb.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 100px) 100vw, 100px" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Office Depot, and its partner Support.com, have been fined $35 million for using the PC Health Check tune-up service to dupe people into buying unnecessary computer repair and technical services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read more in my article on the Hot for Security blog.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:05:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Swiss President Says Regulation for Blockchain Firms Should be ‘Fast and Clear’ -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/swiss-president-says-regulation-for-blockchain-firms-should-be-fast-and-clear</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hMWY1NDFlM2M1MzU4MjdkMDJkMTc1YWU1NWYxZjFlYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiss president and finance minister Ueli Maurer has stressed that regulation for the blockchain sector should be fast and clear&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japan Green Lights 2nd Crypto Exchange for April Launch as Data Shows Huge Interest -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japan-green-lights-2nd-crypto-exchange-for-april-launch-as-data-shows-huge-interest</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82NzA0NGY4Y2I4ZjgxMDg1YWIwOTI1NGY3ODM3ZTY0OS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto exchanges are passing Japan’s licensing scheme as figures reveal a total of 23 in pipeline&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LA Times technology: UK report finds technical risks in Huawei network gear -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://www.latimes.com/business/technology/la-fi-huawei-british-security-chinese-telecom-20190328-story.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;British cybersecurity inspectors said Thursday they found significant technical issues in Chinese telecom supplier Huawei's software that pose risks for the country's mobile networks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It's the latest salvo in a global battle over Huawei, which the U.S. says could give the Chinese government backdoor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 05:20:00 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Ledger, Trust Company Legacy Trust to Offer Crypto Custody for Institutional Investors -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-trust-company-legacy-trust-to-offer-crypto-custody-for-institutional-investors</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85MmE0ZTY5MjYyODFlZWVmYTVjYWQwZDQwZGU1YTdmMy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong custodian Legacy Trust has partnered with French hardware wallet producer Ledger to offer institutional cryptocurrency custody services&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Marco Polo Blockchain Built on R3’s Corda Sees First Live Trades -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/marco-polo-blockchain-built-on-r3s-corda-sees-first-live-trades</link><description>The first real transactions have been conducted on Marco Polo, a trade finance blockchain built on R3's Corda platform.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Corda Blockchain Trade Finance Platform Marco Polo Sees First Transactions -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/corda-blockchain-trade-finance-platform-marco-polo-sees-first-transactions</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yNzUxYzEwM2I2MzY0MWRkNGEwYmE2YzZiYTNiNWZkYi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;R3’s Corda-based enterprise trade finance platform Marco Polo enters market with successful pilot, together with major German banks&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: No Portfolio? What’s your excuse? -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/no-portfolio-whats-your-excuse-fc2136a19672?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h4&gt;But first, shoutouts to our investors of the week: &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/satyapadala/"&gt;Satya Padala&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/cherubino/"&gt;Claudio Cherubino&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;amp; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ajeetkhurana/"&gt;Ajeet Khurana&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*eMCXZg5jxV-Vf8PC" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whether you are a &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/tagged/ux-design"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UX designer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, a &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/tagged/python"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Python engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, or anything in between, your portfolio matters. It’s often one of the first things recruiters and prospective employers will see. That being said, not every portfolio will be exactly the same. In the articles in today’s newsletter, we’ll look at ways to make your portfolio stand out, or ways you can change an existing portfolio to make a bigger impact!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/how-to-optimize-your-github-profile-9540f338b2c9"&gt;How to optimize your GitHub profile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@pavel.malos"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel Malos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re having trouble getting started, one of the simplest solutions is to optimize your Github profile. In this article, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@pavel.malos"&gt;Pavel Malos&lt;/a&gt; talks about ways you can make Github stand, and even use it as your portfolio. He also explains how this is a great first step toward a more advanced portfolio:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This guide will help you to create a professional looking GitHub profile intended to use it as a portfolio of your work.You’ll also learn how to impress recruiters by contributing to open source projects. A personal side-project may grow into something bigger. You can’t always predict what will catch the eye of a recruiter or senior software engineer, but when it does, you want to showcase your best work.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/create-your-developer-landing-page-with-github-pages-70c89b40d052"&gt;Create your developer landing page with GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@flexdinesh"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinesh Pandiyan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve already customized your Github profile, the next logical step is to create a developer landing page with GitHub Pages. You likely already use GitHub, so this is a great way to get a simple portfolio site up and running quickly. &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@flexdinesh"&gt;Dinesh Pandiyan&lt;/a&gt; explains:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Usually creating a personal website would involve buying/registering a domain name, finding a free/paid hosting service, developing your site and uploading it to the hosting provider. But with GitHub&lt;a href="https://pages.github.com/"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;Pages, publishing your site is as easy as drinking a coffee.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/if-youre-a-dev-come-and-get-your-own-rockstar-portfolio-102cb30b8668"&gt;If you’re a dev, come and get your own rockstar portfolio!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@pedsmoreira"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pedro Silva Moreira&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his article, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@pedsmoreira"&gt;Pedro Silva&lt;/a&gt; explains why we often don’t even start the process of creating a portfolio:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Creating your own portfolio takes time. First you have to choose the technologies among the overwhelming amount of options we have. Am I going to go for React? Angular? PHP? Ruby? What about SEO? Should I try node? What them, where do I host? Once you decided and set everything up, you’ve got to list all your projects manually, add the descriptions, links, images and decide on a design that shows your very best. Suddenly, the simple task of creating a pretty portfolio is overwhelming.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like you, then read this story, for a practical approach to creating an online portfolio using GitShowcase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’m not a UI or UX engineer!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/@3rdwave_themes/want-a-portfolio-site-in-2016-get-this-free-bootstrap-template-741d40d9af7b"&gt;Developer — Free Bootstrap 4 Portfolio Theme for Developers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/@3rdwave_themes"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xiaoying Riley&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have a lot of time or UI experience, maybe a professional Bootstrap theme is your answer. In this article, &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@3rdwave_themes"&gt;Xiaoying Riley&lt;/a&gt; showcases a developer theme she build, and gives a brief tutorial on how to install and customize it. Here’s a short summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It can be used as a professional portal to your other online portfolios or websites (eg. Linkedin, CoderWall, Blog, GitHub etc) in a modular fashion. The template comes with all of the source SCSS files included so the styling/colour can easily be customised.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/i-created-my-portfolio-with-react-and-some-magic-fda27ba06a06"&gt;I Created My Portfolio with React and Some Magic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@flexdinesh"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinesh Pandiyan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, creating a portfolio can be intimidating if we don’t have a ton of experience with UI or UX. If that sounds like you, this tutorial may help you build a fantastic looking website using React, and a few other front end technologies. In his article, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@flexdinesh"&gt;Dinesh Pandiyan&lt;/a&gt; explains how even if you aren’t an expert in UI, you can still make a stunning portfolio website:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I am no UI expert but in recent times I’ve took a liking towards responsive design, animations, flexbox, and other fancy CSS features. So I thought I’d take my UI skills for a spin and build my portfolio along the way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/8-ux-mistakes-to-avoid-on-your-ux-portfolio-website-4d6dd437cf21"&gt;8 UX Mistakes To Avoid On Your UX Portfolio Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@sarahdoody"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sarah Doody&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to a good portfolio, what you do is sometimes just as important as what you don’t do. Knowing what mistakes to avoid can be a game changer. According to &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@sarahdoody"&gt;Sarah Doody&lt;/a&gt;, even experienced engineers and designers can struggle with this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When it comes to creating your own website, you struggle because you don’t have months or years of experience thinking about content websites, playing with different layouts, understanding how to make it scannable, and considering the behavior of the user on a content website.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I don’t have time to update my portfolio!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/build-a-graphql-api-powered-portfolio-website-e36eb51cf622"&gt;Build a GraphQL API-Powered Portfolio Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@carsoncgibbons"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carson Gibbons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe you already have a website, but it’s outdated. Often the most time consuming part of building an online portfolio is maintaining and updating the content. If you have ever felt like this, maybe using the GraphQL-API powered CMS is the answer you’re looking for. In this tutorial, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@carsoncgibbons"&gt;Carson Gibbons&lt;/a&gt; shows you how to set everything up from start to finish:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I will show you how to pick up an existing codebase example to build your very own beautiful &lt;a href="https://cosmicjs.com/apps/portfolio-website"&gt;Portfolio Website&lt;/a&gt;, powered by the &lt;a href="https://cosmicjs.com/docs/graphql"&gt;Cosmic JS GraphQL API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://cosmicjs.com/apps/landing-page"&gt;.&lt;/a&gt; The portfolio app includes portfolio management, contact form (powered by MailGun) and a beautiful frontend by &lt;a href="http://html5up.net/"&gt;HTML5UP.net&lt;/a&gt;. Install, deploy and edit every part of this portfolio website from your &lt;a href="https://cosmicjs.com/"&gt;Cosmic JS&lt;/a&gt;Bucket Dashboard.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/how-to-build-portfolio-site-using-vue-and-cosmic-js-5832bce7e7dc"&gt;How to Build a Portfolio Site Using Vue and Cosmic JS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@tonyspiro"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tony Spiro&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cosmic JS offers a CMS for any website or portfolio, but setting it up can sometimes seem a little overwhelming. If you’re looking for an easy way to update and manage content on your portfolio website, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@tonyspiro"&gt;Tony Spiro&lt;/a&gt; shows how to build a great site using Cosmic JS and Vue. Here’s a little from his tutorial:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The portfolio site we are going to build will have 4 pages there are home, technologies, projects, and open sources. This site also will have 3 object types there are profiles, technologies, and projects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I just need some inspiration!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/top-12-web-developer-portfolios-to-get-inspirations-b1a54247329e"&gt;Top 12 Web Developer Portfolios to Get Inspirations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@soulless"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amy Smith&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you have the time and the skill set to create your own portfolio. But just having inspiration to get started is challenging. In this article, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@soulless"&gt;Amy Smith&lt;/a&gt; takes a look at some of the best online portfolios and explains what makes them stand out. She also has this to say to get you thinking about what makes a great portfolio:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the toughest things to do as a new developer is to make a personal web developer portfolio that helps to get a potential employer’s attention in the overcrowded job marketplace. Compared with commercial website, web developer personal website will pay more attention to personality and independent thinking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’m happy with my portfolio, but don’t know what else to do!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/how-to-build-an-online-presence-as-a-junior-developer-c90bc096989b"&gt;How to Build an Online Presence as a Junior Developer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@samjarman"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sam Jarman&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are reading this, there’s a good chance you’ve spent a lot of time writing high quality blog posts on Hacker Noon. Maybe you’ve spent more time writing than creating your portfolio. If you fall into this category, then be sure to include your blog posts in your portfolio or website. In this story, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@samjarman"&gt;Sam Jarman&lt;/a&gt; explains that a portfolio or website isn’t all there is to do. Creating an online presence through a blog, or integrating your blog into your portfolio can be a powerful tool:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So, what, as a developer could you create for online? Twitter is trivial, LinkedIn you probably already know about and GitHub we’ve talked about. But how about a blog? A blog is a great way to share your long-form thoughts and they’re very easy to set up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.S. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://Hackernoon.com"&gt;Hackernoon.com&lt;/a&gt; is a top 5k site in the world (source, Alexa), so if you want some great links back to your portfolio site, &lt;a href="http://contribute.hackernoon.com"&gt;consider publishing a tech story on Hackernoon.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.P.S. &lt;/strong&gt;Shoutout to our investors of the week! Cheers to those who make it possible for us to &lt;a href="http://startengine.com/hackernoon"&gt;build a better tech site&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/satyapadala/"&gt;Satya Padala&lt;/a&gt; is a senior engineer who hacked his way into the early investment world.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/cherubino/"&gt;Claudio Cherubino&lt;/a&gt; is a Developer Relations Manager at Google, working on the Google Assistant, Fuchsia, and other IoT projects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Author, investor, speaker, crypto-evangelist &lt;a href="https://in.linkedin.com/in/ajeetkhurana"&gt;Ajeet Khurana&lt;/a&gt; is CEO of &lt;a href="https://www.zebpay.com/"&gt;Zebpay&lt;/a&gt; — a Cryptocurrency exchange founded in 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=fc2136a19672" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/no-portfolio-whats-your-excuse-fc2136a19672"&gt;No Portfolio? What’s your excuse?&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>