<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 20:57:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cointelegraph: Blockchain Insurance Initiative B3i Expands Its Group of Investors -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-insurance-initiative-b3i-expands-its-group-of-investors</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82ZGJjMGVlYzM4NmY3YjY2MDkxZmRhMDcyYzc4Y2M3Yy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockchain startup B3i has added three new insurer and reinsurers to participate in the company’s ongoing funding round&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 21:51:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bosch and Wien Energie Demo Blockchain-Powered Refrigerator -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bosch-and-wien-energie-demo-blockchain-powered-refrigerator</link><description>Electronics giant Bosch and power supplier Wien Energie have revealed a blockchain fridge aimed to enable better control of electricity consumption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 18:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Open beta programme launches for Sila’s API platform -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/open-beta-program-launches-for-silas-api-platform/</link><description>Aims to bridge gap between traditional banking systems and blockchain.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Barclays, RBS Join 40-Strong R3 Blockchain Real Estate Trial -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/barclays-rbs-join-40-strong-r3-blockchain-real-estate-trial</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9kZjI5ZDM5YmVhZDZkNjA1ZTE2NTgyNTk0NzgyMjhkZi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Royal Bank of Scotland tells of renewed blockchain enthusiasm following real estate use case trial&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:17:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Startup Behind Ethereum DEX Releases Lightning Developer Tools -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/startup-behind-ethereum-dex-releases-lightning-developer-tools</link><description>Radar Relay, a decentralized exchange for trading tokens over ethereum, is branching out into bitcoin lightning technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: France in the Blockchain Ecosystem with Karim Sabba from Paris Blockchain Week -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/france-in-the-blockchain-ecosystem-with-karim-sabba-from-paris-blockchain-week-a0c2bd61c1b5?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h4&gt;Episode 35 of the &lt;a href="https://podcast.hackernoon.com/"&gt;Hacker Noon Podcast&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;strong&gt;An interview with Karim Sabba, French entrepreneur and founder of &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://pbwsummit.com"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paris Blockchain Week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. Paris Blockchain Week is April &lt;/strong&gt;16–17, 2019 in Paris, France, Use code: HACKERNOON30 for a 30% discount.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Today’s show would not be possible without &lt;a href="https://do.co/hackernoon"&gt;Digital Ocean&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*P8NUq1SotGYv_chNfH69uA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Listen to the interview on &lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/product-iteration-with-hacker-noon-interim-cto-dane-lyons/id1436233955?i=1000421970409&amp;amp;mt=2"&gt;iTunes&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/music/m/Dfuna5a4pzsmjr76bxabkxdrhim?t=Product_Iteration_with_Hacker_Noon_Interim_CTO_Dane_Lyons-Hacker_Noon_Podcast"&gt;Google Podcast&lt;/a&gt;, or watch on &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/W0nvSoG7ONo"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FVhQCJoCEG04%3Ffeature%3Doembed&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DVhQCJoCEG04&amp;amp;image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FVhQCJoCEG04%2Fhqdefault.jpg&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;schema=youtube" width="854" height="480" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/fc1d92a51507e9eca88d7af519edd8e9/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/fc1d92a51507e9eca88d7af519edd8e9/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode Trent Lapinski interviews Karim Sabba, French entrepreneur and founder of Paris Blockchain Week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I jumped into this new ecosystem where I saw returns that I had never seen in my life. And that was what caught me in. That was the bait, and it was a good bait. But afterwards I started to dive into all those projects and I remember, I don’t want to name it because my apprehension of this was a bit weird, but basically I saw this project and for a long time I thought it was a scam, and maybe it is, but still they showed that you can technically be able to open bank accounts for unbanked people without them having to read or be tech-savvy. And that was my ‘aha!’ moment.” — Karim Sabba&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.podbean.com/media/share/pb-rhnrr-ad19ee"&gt;France in the Blockchain Ecosystem with Karim Sabba from Paris Blockchain Week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Today’s show would not be possible without &lt;a href="https://do.co/hackernoon"&gt;Digital Ocean&lt;/a&gt;. Learn more at &lt;a href="http://do.co/hackernoon"&gt;do.co/hackernoon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Production and music by Derek Bernard — &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://haberdasherband.com/production?fbclid=IwAR2d8t0cNGHRm1ajmUNWKZ-TMUMawREhvIHSy54LKcOElf7v_TOvkAjZ78Y"&gt;&lt;em&gt;haberdasherband.com/production&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Host: Trent Lapinski — &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://trentlapinski.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://trentlapinski.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;P.S. If you dig the new &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://podcast.hackernoon.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hacker Noon Podcast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, consider &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-hacker-noon-podcast/id1436233955?mt=2"&gt;&lt;em&gt;giving us a 5 star review on iTunes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Also check out &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/archive/2019/04"&gt;April top stories&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/latest-tech-stories/home"&gt;the latest stories&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://hackernoon.com/"&gt;today’s homepage&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=a0c2bd61c1b5" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/france-in-the-blockchain-ecosystem-with-karim-sabba-from-paris-blockchain-week-a0c2bd61c1b5"&gt;France in the Blockchain Ecosystem with Karim Sabba from Paris Blockchain Week&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 23:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: AltDex Launches Cryptocurrency Index of Gaming-Related Tokens -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/altdex-launches-cryptocurrency-index-of-gaming-related-tokens</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85NzM1OWMzYTgxNTBlMGI2YjgzMDE4MmIwYjQ0MDA1OS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;AltDex has developed an index designed to track tokens of blockchain-based projects related to video games&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 23:19:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: SEC Releases Framework for “Investment Contract” Analysis of Digital Assets -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/05/sec-releases-framework-for-investment-contract-analysis-of-digital-assets/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/05/sec-releases-framework-for-investment-contract-analysis-of-digital-assets/"&gt;SEC Releases Framework for “Investment Contract” Analysis of Digital Assets&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/secico-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="32382" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/05/sec-releases-framework-for-investment-contract-analysis-of-digital-assets/secico/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/secico.jpg" data-orig-size="736,460" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="secico" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/secico-300x188.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/secico.jpg" /&gt;Before you get too excited, note what it says in fine print at the end: &amp;#8220;This framework represents the views of the Strategic Hub for Innovation and Financial Technology [&amp;#8230;] of the Securities and Exchange Commission. It is not a rule, regulation, or statement of the Commission, and the Commission has neither approved nor disapproved [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/05/sec-releases-framework-for-investment-contract-analysis-of-digital-assets/"&gt;SEC Releases Framework for “Investment Contract” Analysis of Digital Assets&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:17:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Sending Money Home to Myanmar Can Be Cheaper and Less Illegal with Blockchain -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29948/remittance/blockchain-myanmar-thailand-everex/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The central bank governors in both Thailand and Myanmar has just granted their blessing to the KTB Shewbank, a remittance project that uses blockchain to help reduce costs for Myanmarians&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29948/remittance/blockchain-myanmar-thailand-everex/"&gt;Sending Money Home to Myanmar Can Be Cheaper and Less Illegal with Blockchain&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: DLT and hybrid technology solutions are now more readily available -  Puntaje: 1900</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16975/dlt-and-hybrid-technology-solutions-are-now-more-readily-available?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>There has been some exciting news from Digital Asset Holdings (DA) this week, with their announcemen...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 15:01:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Barclays, RBS, R3 Cut Property Transaction Times in Blockchain Trial -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/barclays-rbs-r3-cut-property-transaction-times-in-blockchain-trial</link><description>Barclays, Royal Bank of Scotland, R3 and more say they've reduced property transaction times to "less than three weeks" using a distributed ledger.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: The Quantum Computer: Annihilator of Contemporary Blockchain Technology -  Puntaje: 10400</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/the-quantum-computer-annihilator-of-contemporary-blockchain-technology-447daf5abda2?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h3&gt;With the popularity of cryptocurrencies on the rise, specialists in the area worry about how, when it comes about, quantum computers will threaten blockchain technology, which at the moment still lacks reliable data security.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*sJmz44oOBHGKjNW05JEzpQ.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Photo by &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/UiH8963wYHo?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText"&gt;Pawel Janiak&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/search/photos/bitcoin?utm_source=unsplash&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_content=creditCopyText"&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Looming Threats&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wired.co.uk/article/quantum-computing-explained"&gt;Quantum computers&lt;/a&gt; are our future, not just with cryptocurrency but in all areas of life, though the fear that they could — in the realm where they are seen as being of most use at the moment — crack the cryptography which blockchains use for security.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The threat is a real one.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, some scientists believe the only way to counter this is to use quantum blockchains as a wall against the threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A simple case of ‘like for like’.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Like Sheep in the Brain&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/203/1*nOyDT14nwD0nsmMuV3ETzQ@2x.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Source: Wooden Poster — Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;My whole interest in Bitcoin mining came about after an acquaintance— who takes it quite seriously — introduced me to his ‘side job’ in 2016: at the time I was working as a copywriter and English teacher at the language school he owned and ran with his wife. I had my own classroom. Next to the classroom was a teachers’ room, where we had our registers, textbooks and other educational resources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was summer. Most of the semester-time courses had finished. This meant the language school was quieter than at any other time during the year. As the demand was less, and there were fewer lessons, my acquaintance expropriated ‘his’ teachers’ room for July and August. Anyway, to cut a long story short, one day when I came in for lessons and was heading up the stairs, I heard this irritating ‘humming’ sound coming from the teachers’ room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Being the nosy person that I am, I had an eyeball. Inside the room, on the tables and floor, were five Bitcoin GPU miners. I knew what they were, but had never seen them in the flesh before.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I asked my acquaintance what he was doing and that got me hooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A month or so later, and after some initial conversations with him, I ordered a cheap &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/21-INC-21BC1-Bitcoin-Computer/dp/B014RD021C"&gt;21 Bitcoin Computer&lt;/a&gt; off of Amazon. My acquaintances GPUs were a higher speck and a lot more expensive which he had bought from China. That, however, didn’t bother me. I was just going to see how it worked out. It was all for a bit of fun, a hobby interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I was chuffed: for a few hundred pounds I thought I was going to be rich.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Big chance of that!&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The running costs of it, and the ludicrous noise it created, made the 50 Gigahash per second machine not really a good investment. Although my acquaintance was teaching me all the ins and outs of Bitcoin mining, I soon became disillusioned with it — mainly due to my partner and daughter becoming sick of the racket it was making in the spare bedroom (and my child screaming ‘it sounds like&lt;em&gt; sheep in my brain’&lt;/em&gt;)— and within a month, I switched the machine off, selling it online for a much lower price than I had purchased it for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, that didn’t stop my interest in it, and I would regularly — and still do, in fact — read articles on the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Blockchain&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its essence, a blockchain is a structure of mathematical code which is able to organize and store data safely and securely. Bitcoin, the popular cryptocurrency that is undergoing a boom of late, uses blockchain technology to organize and archive its transactions in that currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Notwithstanding Bitcoin and other financial data tools, blockchains have the potential to store any kind of data, though. Many predict blockchains will be the dominant technology in many fields in the coming years. Yet this doesn’t come without some doubts and reservations.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Standard cryptographic functions are the nursemaid of blockchains. To breach the data in them takes powerful computers and resources which, at the moment at least, are out of reach for the majority. Even the smartest, most expensive and up-to-date computer does not have the power, nor the speed, to crack the standard cryptographic functions…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Yet the tide is turning.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Q System One Quantum Computer&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quantum computers are the new dawn. Only recently, IBM Research announced it had created the &lt;a href="https://www.research.ibm.com/ibm-q/system-one/"&gt;Q System One quantum computer&lt;/a&gt;, which it states on its YouTube &lt;em&gt;channel:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘enables universal approximate superconducting quantum computers to operate outside the research lab for the first time.’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exciting news for tech boffins and the future. IBM also added:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘It’s a major step forward in the commercialization of quantum computing, which could one day enable breakthroughs in such areas as materials and drug discovery, financial services, and artificial intelligence.’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/355/1*Njs1RNPe8HEjYA4b_re3hQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the inception of this revolutionary technology, standard cryptographic functions — and any other level of security used to protect blockchain — will become an easy target for contravention and other kinds of attack from outside the system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To foil this threat, and ease the worries of those with a vested interest in blockchain and cryptocurrencies, scientists agree the only way to combat this is by creating quantum blockchains — for though quantum computers can crack regular blockchains, quantum computers cannot break the cryptographic codes of quantum blockchains, and this is why many advocate adding quantum cryptography to blockchains already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Industry professionals, however, believe there is a far simpler solution to this conundrum: Quantum cryptography, in its very essence, just adds one more level of encryption to the standard blockchain, which does not make a blockchain unbreachable to hackers as long as the quantum computers they are using have the capability to break the code for the quantum blockchain initiated.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Einsteinian Theory 2.0&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://sms.victoria.ac.nz/Main/GradDelRajan"&gt;Del Rajan&lt;/a&gt;, a Ph.D. Student School of Mathematics and Statistics at the Victoria University of Wellington, along with his supervisor, Professor &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Matt_Visser"&gt;Matt Visser&lt;/a&gt;, propose &lt;em&gt;‘making the whole blockchain a quantum phenomenon’.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They suggest — heading into the world of hardcore science fiction and Einsteinian theory — using quantum particles that are, in their very essence, entangled in time. ‘Quantum entanglement’ happens when two particles become intertwined, and from that connection they remain a single entity, or system, disregarding the spatial proximity to each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/207/1*WSo0-Nu4j1bY17KC8P6XEQ@2x.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Erwin Schrödinger, one of the fathers of Quantum Theory&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applying this theory — because that is all it is at the moment in the minds of the two Wellington-based, NZ scientists — would allow a process of encoding to begin, where a single quantum particle could stamp the history of other particles on it. Hacking this particle to gain access to the encrypted data on its predecessors would be impossible without destroying the original quantum particle and blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;This arrangement, nevertheless, depends on the laws of physics to assure a high level of security.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand how this can work, and therefore be applied from the theoretical models issued, it is first important to understand the fundamental quality of a blockchain. In plain English, a blockchain is a log, or an account book, which can evidence different kinds of information. For example, those of financial transactions or an account book ledger. The information is then added to a database, otherwise called a block. This process is repeated until said time, when — using a mathematical tool called a ‘hashing function’ — the information is encrypted. The procedure of hashing creates a unique number which is an exact mirror image of the data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The process is repeated: more information is added to the ‘block’ with the next round of transactions before being, by the hashing function again, encrypted once more as a unique number. And a block and a block and a block. And so a chain of blocks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Foolproof System&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes blockchains a low-risk target for cybercriminals is contemporary computers lack the computational power needed to hack the data set out by the hashing function. Trying to change, or even corrupt, records organized by the hashing function, a least at the moment, is impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, with the advent of quantum computers, this conundrum will be solved or, at the very least, be much easier to crack. A nightmare scenario for banks, dealers in cryptocurrency and others with a vested interest in the new technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Quantum Entanglement&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The solution conceived by Rajan and Visser, as already discussed, is directed toward creating a quantum version of the blockchain, which at its essence is based on the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/entanglement"&gt;quantum entanglement&lt;/a&gt; theory.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;If a hacker, then, for some reason tries to interfere with the ‘connection’, or the particle entanglement, the result is the destruction of the link, guaranteeing the security of the blockchain. The particles entangled are influenced by the overall temporal and spatial possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/266/1*fj1l5Ire6pnXXojrN1fLDw@2x.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Quantum Entanglement in action. Source: WikiCommons&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With this influence of the particles’ entanglement established across all spatial and temporal circumstances, meaning quantum theory allows for things to be influenced in the past, rather than just in the intuitive notion of local realism and causality.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two scientists believe this type of quantum entanglement will be enough to secure quantum blockchains by encoding data on a quantum particle. In this state, they would establish a quantum block by always adding to it. As more data is then connected to the first quantum particle, the data is subsequently merged with the second particle of the entanglement until all the encoded data is on the second particle. The first particle is then dumped and the proceeding record of data is merged to create a block.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blocks and blocks equal a chain.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quantum entanglement is secure as any attempt to hack into the chain will automatically compromise it. Blocks ‘created’ earlier, too, are completely secure and inaccessible as they do not exist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/242/1*nLhpc04Gd0q_DHfZDXficg@2x.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Philip K. Dick — a genius who was ahead of his time. Source: WikiCommons&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Take a deep breath before your brain explodes!&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is all heavy stuff and very nerdy, I know, and seems like it was taken out of a chapter of a Philip K. Dick novel, but if the theoretical model works as planned, the threat of quantum computers and the potential dangers they could have to contemporary blockchains would be a non-starter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;So, children, just maybe the ideas first espoused by the learned bunch of Einstein, Schrödinger, Podolsky and Rosen in the twentieth century could save the world’s future cryptocurrency moguls from a valley of tears.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=447daf5abda2" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/the-quantum-computer-annihilator-of-contemporary-blockchain-technology-447daf5abda2"&gt;The Quantum Computer: Annihilator of Contemporary Blockchain Technology&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 21:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin Holds Recent Gains Near $5,000 as Stocks Report Minor Uptrend -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-holds-recent-gains-near-5-000-as-stocks-report-minor-uptrend</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81YzIyYjA3MmY3YmYxNTNjMzBiZjUzMjg5NzM0ZDBjMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin stays stable at $5,000 as most of the top 20 cryptocurrencies are reporting gains today&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:24:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Now There’s a Canadian Dollar-Pegged Stablecoin on the Way -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/now-theres-a-canadian-dollar-pegged-stablecoin-on-the-way</link><description>Toronto-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinsquare is launching a stablecoin pegged 1:1 to the Canadian dollar.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortune: SEC Guidance Sparks Fear and Loathing in Crypto Industry -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>http://fortune.com/2019/04/05/sec-crypto-rules/</link><description>Chilling effects</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Tax Software CryptoTrader.Tax Integrates With TurboTax -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-tax-software-cryptotradertax-integrates-with-turbotax</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82ODFlMDgyMTg2NTBkYzdkYmFmZTQ0MWYzN2YwZDQ4NC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto tax software startup CryptoTrader.Tax has integrated with major U.S. tax filing software TurboTax&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 02:15:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Google Searches for ‘Bitcoin’ Hit Highest Total Since November -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/google-searches-for-bitcoin-hit-highest-total-since-november</link><description>Google searches for "bitcoin" jumped to its highest level on Tuesday since Nov. 20, 2018 as the cryptocurrency surged above $5,000 on most exchanges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 21:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coinbase Makes LinkedIn’s ‘Top Companies 2019’ List as Lone Crypto Firm -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-makes-linkedins-top-companies-2019-list-as-lone-crypto-firm</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9iOTc2NGYxNDA3ZTE0NTM3NmRiODAwMGZkYmY4NWFkMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn rankings place Coinbase as only crypto player in top 50 U.S. employers&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:30:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Coinbase Tops JPMorgan in LinkedIn List of Most Popular Employers -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/coinbase-tops-jpmorgan-in-linkedin-list-of-most-popular-employers</link><description>Crypto exchange Coinbase has ranked above investment banking giant JPMorgan in LinkedIn’s top 50 U.S. employers list for 2019.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Tron Dapps Saw $1.6 Billion in Volume in Q1 2019, Driven By Gambling -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/tron-dapps-saw-1-6-billion-in-volume-in-q1-2019-driven-by-gambling</link><description>From digital dog racing to a "farm investment game," Tron is finding product-market fit crypto with gambling dapps.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: US CFTC Chair Says Agency Has Resisted Calls to Suppress Development of Crypto Sector -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-cftc-chair-says-agency-has-resisted-calls-to-suppress-development-of-crypto-sector</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83OTI2MzgxZDM3MzcxZGQwY2Q5ZTcyOTNiYzcyZGFhNS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. CFTC Chairman J. Christopher Giancarlo has emphasized the agency’s commitment is to monitor, but not impede, the development of the crypto asset sector&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:53:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, Litecoin, Bitcoin Cash, EOS, Binance Coin, Stellar, Cardano, TRON: Price Analysis April 5 -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-ripple-litecoin-bitcoin-cash-eos-binance-coin-stellar-cardano-tron-price-analysis-april-05</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jN2Y0YzRjZTliYmFlZGY4OTJmOGJhZTRkYTRmMjdiZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss the latest price overview 😉&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 20:49:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Cumberland Crypto OTC Desk Reports Spike in Large-Scale BTC Trades Within One Hour -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cumberland-crypto-otc-desk-reports-spike-in-large-scale-btc-trades-within-one-hour</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81OWNhMGY0NTZlOWE5YzFmYzg1MjNhYzBiZTY5YTE4YS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cumberland, the Chicago-based cryptocurrency trading unit of DRW Holdings LLC, reported a sharp, sudden spike in large Bitcoin transactions on Monday&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:31:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Binance’s Trust Wallet to Launch Staking Service With Tezos -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binances-trust-wallet-to-launch-staking-service-with-tezos</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80YmY0MTEzNzMyMDczOGZmYTQzYWQwMzY1MWFjYTNjZS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binance’s official digital currency wallet app Trust Wallet has announced plans to launch a staking feature for cryptocurrencies&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 21:36:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: AeroGarden maker says hackers stole months of credit card data -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/3kUV3azNeh4/</link><description>Bad news for home gardeners: criminals might have your credit card data. AeroGrow, the maker of the at-home garden kit AeroGarden, said in a letter to customers that its website had credit card scraping malware for more than four months. The company said anyone who bought something through its website between October 29, 2018 and [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : Advanced Persistent Threat: Dark Reading Caption Contest Winners -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities---threats/advanced-persistent-threat-dark-reading-caption-contest-winners/a/d-id/1334330?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>From sushi and phishing to robots, passwords and ninjas -- and the winners are ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC technology: Facebook 'hosts' cyber-crime marketplaces -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-47831216</link><description>Security researchers found credit card numbers and phishing campaigns being openly traded online.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 16:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Step By Step Office Dropper Dissection -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83381/malware/dropper-dissection.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Malware researcher and founder of Yoroi Marco Ramill described a step-by-step procedure that shows how to dissect an Office dropper. During the past few weeks, I received several emails asking how to dissect Office Payloads. While I was thinking about how to answer to such questions I received a MalSpam with a Microsoft Office document [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83381/malware/dropper-dissection.html"&gt;Step By Step Office Dropper Dissection&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : The Matrix at 20: A Metaphor for Today's Cybersecurity Challenges -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities---threats/the-matrix-at-20-a-metaphor-for-todays-cybersecurity-challenges/a/d-id/1334304?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>The Matrix ushered in a new generation of sci-fi movies and futuristic plotlines with a relentless, seemingly invulnerable set of villains. Twenty years later, that theme is all too familiar to security pros.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:30:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Cybercrime groups continue to flourish on Facebook -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/zXpnffHZ4YA/</link><description>You might be surprised what you can buy on Facebook, if you know where to look. Researchers with Cisco&amp;#8217;s Talos security research team have uncovered a wave of Facebook groups dedicated to making money from a variety of illicit and otherwise sketchy online behaviors, including phishing schemes, trading hacked credentials and spamming. The 74 groups [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Ursnif: The Latest Evolution of the Most Popular Banking Malware -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83396/breaking-news/ursnif-banking-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;ZLab Yoroi-Cybaze dissected another attack wave of Ursnif Trojan, aka Gozi ISFB, an offspring of the original Gozi which source code was leaked in 2014. ZLab Yoroi-Cybaze dissected another attack wave of Ursnif Trojan, aka Gozi ISFB, an offspring of the original Gozi which source code was leaked in 2014. Introduction A few days ago, [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83396/breaking-news/ursnif-banking-malware.html"&gt;Ursnif: The Latest Evolution of the Most Popular Banking Malware&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: US Web Servers Hosted 10 Malware Families -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/us-web-servers-hosted-10-malware-1/</link><description>Nevadan bullet-proof hoster enables massive phishing operation</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : Phishing Campaign Targeting Verizon Mobile Users -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/phishing-campaign-targeting-verizon-mobile-users-/d/d-id/1334358?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>Lookout Phishing AI, which discovered the attack, says it has been going on since late November.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 15:15:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Deutsche Bank releases API interface for instant payments in SAP ERP software -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33644/deutsche-bank-releases-api-interface-for-instant-payments-in-sap-erp-software?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Deutsche Bank has joined forces with software firm Serrala to launch an API interface for Sepa insta...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian top stories: Topshop's Philip Green plans to halve Arcadia pension payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/apr/05/topshops-philip-green-plans-to-halve-arcadia-pension-payments</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Billionaire in talks about cutting payments by £25m as part of turnaround plan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sir Philip Green is seeking to halve payments into his Topshop fashion empire’s pension fund as part of a financial &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/mar/28/philip-green-quietly-tries-to-vacate-stores-ahead-of-arcadia-restructure"&gt;restructuring plan&lt;/a&gt; the billionaire says is needed to save the business from collapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former BHS owner is in talks with the pension regulator and the trustees of his Arcadia group’s pension fund about cutting annual payments into the scheme from £50m to £25m. The pension deficit was £300m in 2017, according to the most recently published figures.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/apr/05/topshops-philip-green-plans-to-halve-arcadia-pension-payments"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Deutsche Bank and Serrala launch API interface for SEPA payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/deutsche-bank-and-serrala-launch-api-interface-for-sepa-payments/</link><description>A step towards facilitating real-time treasury.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: IOC resumes fuel supplies to Jet Airways after assurance of payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/ioc-resumes-fuel-supplies-to-jet-airways-after-assurance-of-payments-119040500786_1.html</link><description>Earlier in the day, Jet Airways faced operational disruptions across major airports when IOC refused to refuel its planes without clearing the outstanding amount</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 18:51:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC business: Ten million people face higher pension payments -  Puntaje: 125.0</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-47816511</link><description>A bigger chunk of wages will now be automatically diverted to a pension, but employers will put in more too.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 21:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Business: Workforce diversity needs a rethink in digital economy -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/workplace/workforce-diversity-needs-a-rethink-in-digital-economy-20190328-p518ie.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_business</link><description>Older Australians want to work longer and more flexibly but business and government aren’t really onboard it would seem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Coventry Building Society opens up PSD2 sandbox -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77947/coventry-building-society-opens-up-psd2-sandbox?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Coventry Building Society opened its Payment Services Directive 2 (PSD2) testing environment or ‘san...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: BharatPe Notches $15.5M In Funding; Eika Group Teams With EedenBull -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/international/global-payments/2019/bharatpe-funding-eika-group-eedenbull/</link><description>Welcome to The Axis, your late look at payments news from around the world. Coverage includes the $5 million Series A raise of Nigerian digital payments company Kudi. Norwegian banking alliance Eika Group is teaming up with EedenBull, India’s FinTech startup BharatPe notched $15.5 million in funding and consumers are putting digital assets in their wills […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 20:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Bitcoin trading volume hits two-year low in March: Report -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/bitcoin-trading-volume-hits-two-year-low-in-march-report-11415268</link><description>NEW YORK: Bitcoin's trading volume dropped to a two-year low in March, digital currency trading tool provider TradeBlock said in a report on Thursday, as investors remained spooked by increased regulatory scrutiny.

Bitcoin volume in the top five digital currency exchanges totalled US$2.14 billion ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 15:34:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Firm Bitpanda Secures Payments Service Provider License Under EU Rules -  Puntaje: 3000</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-firm-bitpanda-secures-payments-service-provider-license-under-eu-rules</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80ODllNzRiMmIxMjhjZTMwMjI0ZWZiYjE4NGVmYWYyOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viennese crypto and fintech firm Bitpanda has received a payment service provider license from Austria’s financial regulator in accordance with EU-wide rules&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Endor Protocol Brings Big Data Prediction Power to the People -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://finovate.com/endor-protocol-brings-big-data-prediction-power-to-the-people/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Predictive analytics platform Endor announced the launch of its Endor Protocol this week. Powered by MIT&amp;#8217;s Social Physics technology, the solution empowers organizations and individuals to analyze and query sizable data sets and produce AI-generated business predictions. The technology enables observers to identify patterns in customer behavior that can be used to tailor services and offerings &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/endor-protocol-brings-big-data-prediction-power-to-the-people/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/endor-protocol-brings-big-data-prediction-power-to-the-people/"&gt;Endor Protocol Brings Big Data Prediction Power to the People&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 19:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Bud extols the value of PHP for open banking -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33648/bud-extols-the-value-of-php-for-open-banking?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>In an interview with Finextra, Bud’s chief information and security officer Merlin Gore maintains th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Finovate Alumni News -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-973/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Finovate.com Gusto Teams with Trainual to Automate Job Role Training. Finovate Global: Finn AI Powers Chatbots in South Africa; Token Drives Open Banking in MENA. Around the web Green Dot helps Walmart customers move more than $2 billion through the program’s virtual Vault savings program. Top Image Systems shareholders approve acquisition by Kofax. BuyerQuest &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-973/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-973/"&gt;Finovate Alumni News&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: SocGen Assurances and Roadzen team on contextual insurance venture -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33650/socgen-assurances-and-roadzen-team-on-contextual-insurance-venture?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Societe Generale Assurances has joined forces with AI insurtech specialist Roadzen to build a "digit...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: South Korea, a FinTech Hub-To-Be? -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16972/south-korea-a-fintech-hub-to-be?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The neutral status quo The current situation in South Korea is what you might call “meh” for FinTech...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Top fintech stories this week – 5 March 2019 -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/top-fintech-stories-this-week-5-march-2019/</link><description>Catch up on FinTech Futures' top five fintech stories of the week - all in one place!</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Where customers are also lenders: One fintech's payday alternative -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/where-customers-are-also-lenders-one-fintechs-payday-alternative</link><description>To generate revenue, SoLo Funds depends on consumers willing to front funds through its platform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 01:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: Google dissolves AI advisory board amid employee protest -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/google-dissolves-ai-advisory-board-amid-employee-protest</link><description>The controversy over Google naming a conservative thinker and alleged "anti-trans, anti-LGBT" supporter to a company advisory board has ended with the whole project scrapped.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Time Magazine business: Google Scraps New AI Ethics Council Amid Criticism -  Puntaje: 250.0</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/time/business/~3/HCCktRWnArQ/</link><description>A petition urged Google to remove a conservative think tank president from the panel over her positions on gay and transgender people</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 04:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Cambodia and Singapore strengthen cooperation in fintech innovation -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77946/cambodia-and-singapore-strengthen-cooperation-in-fintech-innovation?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) and the National Bank of Cambodia (NBC) today signed a Mem...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Mitsui Sumitomo Just Launched Their Digital Hub in Singapore -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29939/insurtech/mitsui-sumitomo-digital-hub-singapore-insurtech-insurance/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mitsui Sumitomo an insurance giant hailing from Japan, and they just announced the setup of their global digital hub in Singapore—at its Asia regional office. The digital hub has been&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29939/insurtech/mitsui-sumitomo-digital-hub-singapore-insurtech-insurance/"&gt;Mitsui Sumitomo Just Launched Their Digital Hub in Singapore&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 05:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: JPMorgan's Dimon apprehensive of China's prowess in AI and fintech -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33641/jpmorgans-dimon-apprehensive-of-chinas-prowess-in-ai-and-fintech?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>JPMorgan Chase chief Jamie Dimon has admitted to being worried about the progress China has made in...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: BI’s Top 3 Stories in March: Bank-Fintech Partnerships, Real Estate Tech, More… -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/04/bis-top-3-stories-in-march-bank-fintech-partnerships-real-estate-tech-more/</link><description>With more bank-fintech partnerships, the acceptance of technological change within the C-suite, and an increasing number of entry points connecting banks to new businesses, it's no surprise that these topics resonated with readers in March. Below are Bank Innovation's top 3 posts for the month, based on website traffic and editorial judgment. Citi Venture Investing [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 16:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian technology: Google scraps AI ethics council after backlash: 'Back to the drawing board' -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/04/google-ai-ethics-council-backlash</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Decision comes after employees called for the removal of a rightwing thinktank leader from the council&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google is ending a new artificial intelligence ethics council just one week after launching it, following &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/01/google-kay-coles-james-removal-employees-letter"&gt;protests from employees&lt;/a&gt; over the appointment of a rightwing thinktank leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapid downfall of the Advanced Technology External Advisory Council (ATEAC), which was dedicated to “the responsible development of AI”, came after more than 2,000 Google workers signed a &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@against.transphobia/googlers-against-transphobia-and-hate-b1b0a5dbf76"&gt;petition&lt;/a&gt; criticizing the company’s selection of an anti-LGBT advocate.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/04/google-ai-ethics-council-backlash"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 01:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: How To Avoid Nightmares When Onboarding AI-Powered Regtech -  Puntaje: 1900</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16976/how-to-avoid-nightmares-when-onboarding-ai-powered-regtech?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The rapidly expanding realm of artificial intelligence (AI) presents a powerful tool for meeting the...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 23:52:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Nigerian fintech Kudi raises $5 million -  Puntaje: 2400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77945/nigerian-fintech-kudi-raises-5-million?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Kudi, the Nigerian leader of digital payment and collection for the cash economy, raises a Series A...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: What Dimon’s Shareholder Letter Reveals About JPMorgan’s AI Approach -  Puntaje: 3000</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/04/what-dimons-shareholder-letter-reveals-about-jpmorgans-ai-approach/</link><description>Jamie Dimon’s annual letter to shareholders, published this week, would indicate that if the JPMorgan Chase CEO wasn't a believer in the potential for artificial intelligence and machine learning to improve banking, he is now. “The power of artificial intelligence and machine learning is real,” he declared. Noting that the bank recently sent a senior [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Programming Language Trends (Q2 2019) -  Puntaje: 7200</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/programming-language-trends-q2-2019-3b87860de0f8?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*SKs3gDzZeqDPhW_A" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the timeless words of Taylor Swift, “This is a new year. A new beginning. And things will change.” These words could not be more applicable to the world of modern software development. As we move into the second quarter of the year, which programming languages are trending up and to the right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before we dive in, here’s an overview of some of the exciting trends to look for throughout this year: &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/major-programming-trends-to-prepare-for-in-2019-169987cc75f4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Major Programming Trends to Prepare for in 2019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@constantin_"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Constantin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Finally, here’s a look at some of the specific trends Hacker Noon writers have noticed since the beginning of the year:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Mobile Application Development&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/flutter-vs-react-native-will-flutter-kill-react-native-16f5515e5444"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flutter vs React Native — Will Flutter Kill React Native&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@srimanikantapalakollu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PALAKOLLU SRI MANIKANTA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hybrid Application development is ruling the Mobile Application development industry rather than Native Development from a couple of years onwards. Business needs are changing from day to day because of an increase in growth and demand. One of the most popular frameworks that became a friend for most of the mobile application developers since 2015 is React Native. The introduction of Flutter as a major development platform in 2017 could shake up the status quo for mobile application development. Will Flutter take over as a preferred platform?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/the-future-of-cross-platform-is-native-13cc66bf1c00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Future of Cross Platform is Native&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@piannaf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Justin Mancinelli&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Cross-platform” as a term and a development tool is not held in high regard these days, largely because the apps that purport to provide cross-platform support have never really done the job effectively. The arguments in favor of cross-platform development are the same as they’ve always been (D.R.Y., Risk Mitigation and Feature Parity). Is Native really the future of Mobile Application Development?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Server Side Development&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/is-ruby-on-rails-dead-in-2019-b462e9a65b22"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is Ruby on Rails dead in 2019?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@ramyaraghavan"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ramya Raghavan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rails were created in 2003 by David Heinemeier Hansson, while working on the code base for Basecamp, a project management tool, by 37signals. Ruby on Rails is one of the juggernauts and highly valued skills in the startup ecosystem. The Rails framework is based on the principles of Convention over Configuration. But what does the future look like for this popular tool?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/python-v-s-php-which-programming-language-to-choose-in-2019-45a95249ad8d"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Python v/s PHP: Which Programming Language to Choose in 2019?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@sayonetech"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SayOne Technologies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In today’s disruptive tech world, Python and PHP are the two most-popular server-side languages in use. In many aspects, Python and PHP closely compete with each other because of its almost identical features. Their open-source benefits and productive features attract a majority of the businesses and developers to choose Python or PHP for app development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Client Side Development&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/what-is-the-future-of-javascript-355b1f13b317"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the future of JavaScript?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@akpr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ajay Kapoor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its inception in 1995, Javascript has proved to be a dynamic language that has met the growing needs of web development services. This has been possible with the introduction of constant developments and innovations in its every version. No year in the past two decades has passed without Javascript being the most used programming language. Anyone can predict the same in the future after reading the above statistics. Will these statistics hold true over the coming decade?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/choosing-between-vue-js-and-reactjs-in-2019-whats-best-for-your-project-14e6de33c591"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choosing Between Vue.js and ReactJS in 2019: What’s Best for Your Project?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@codica"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Codica Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, every company aims to create a high-quality web solution within a short period of time. To put it into practice, the developer community is able to choose from many JavaScript libraries and frameworks and debates to find the best one. What are the big things to look for in each language in 2019?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/move-over-next-js-and-webpack-ba367f07545"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Move over Next.js and Webpack!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@patrickleet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Patrick Lee Scott&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parcel is a newer module bundler in Javascript Land that makes it really easy to make universal applications that use all of the latest and greatest in the React ecosystem — code-splitting, streaming rendering, and even differential bundling — making it easy to get the latest in performance optimizations with very little effort!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Data Science&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/r-vs-python-whats-the-difference-4eed706890ae"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R vs Python: What’s the difference?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@moimaere"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Muammer Hüseyinoğlu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the massive growth in the importance of Big Data, machine learning, and data science in the software industry or software service companies, two languages have emerged as the most favorable ones for the developers. R and Python have become the two most popular and favorite languages for the data scientists and data analysts. Both of these are similar, yet, different in their ways which makes it difficult for the developers to pick one out of the two. Which language is the best for your next project?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Systems Level Development&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/programming-in-rust-the-good-the-bad-the-ugly-d06f8d8b7738"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programming in Rust: the good, the bad, the ugly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@brndnmtthws"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brenden Matthews&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rust is a modern systems-level programming language designed with safety in mind. It provides zero-cost abstractions, generics, functional features, and plenty more. Many developers are picking up Rust because of it’s faster compiling times, and it’s gentle learning curve. However, Rust could also make a big impact in areas of gaming, data science, systems engineering, as well as others within the next 5 years. What is the good, bad and ugly of Rust?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Testing&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/why-ai-ml-will-shake-software-testing-up-in-2019-b3f86a30bcfa"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why AI &amp;amp; ML Will Shake Software Testing up in 2019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; by &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@oleksii_kh"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oleksii Kharkovyna&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ML and AI are undeniably growing to be significant elements in software testing and QA as well. And all this is for good reason. AI will advance accuracy, give enhanced revenue and lower costs for all QA processes. Henceforth, it improves competitive positioning and customer experience. Most importantly, AI helps identify bugs quicker and faster. The testers can stop worrying about losing their jobs and start focusing on making better policies. There is no reason to fear &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/artificial-intelligence/home"&gt;AI&lt;/a&gt;, instead, we should think of possible ways to incorporate it in our work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.S. &lt;/strong&gt;To get your software story reviewed for publication by a real live human, visit &lt;a href="https://contribute.hackernoon.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contribute.Hackernoon.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.P.S.&lt;/strong&gt; Talk shop at &lt;a href="http://Community.Hackernoon.com"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community.Hackernoon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=3b87860de0f8" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/programming-language-trends-q2-2019-3b87860de0f8"&gt;Programming Language Trends (Q2 2019)&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 16:29:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: M&amp;A on the rise as Visa &amp; Mastercard go for the Trillion $ Cross Border Payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/04/05/ma-on-the-rise-as-visa-mastercard-go-for-the-trillion-cross-border-payments/</link><description>The Cross border payments market was at $22 Trillion three years ago as per a research by the Boston Consulting Group. Certainly a market to go after, and Visa and Mastercard do not seem to be shy of throwing punches at each other in the process. So who got their nose ahead? Earlier this year, [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 04:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: SocGen to offer payment services throughout Europe with Elavon -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/socgen-to-offer-payment-services-throughout-europe-with-elavon/</link><description>This includes United Kingdom, Austria, Belgium, Germany, Italy, Netherlands, Spain and Switzerland.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Real-time-payments monopoly puts financial system at risk -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/opinion/real-time-payments-monopoly-puts-financial-system-at-risk</link><description>The Fed should continue to play a key role in the new payments system, rather than leaving it in the hands of the country’s largest banks, Thomas Hoenig and Bruce Summers argue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Cluley: Ticketmaster is hit by a £5 million legal action after online payment card theft -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.grahamcluley.com/ticketmaster-is-hit-by-a-5-million-legal-action-after-online-payment-card-theft/</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.grahamcluley.com/ticketmaster-is-hit-by-a-5-million-legal-action-after-online-payment-card-theft/" title="Ticketmaster is hit by a £5 million legal action after online payment card theft"&gt;&lt;img width="100" height="100" src="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-150x150.jpeg" class="attachment-100x100 size-100x100 wp-post-image" alt="Ticketmaster is hit by a £5 million legal action after online payment card theft" style="float: right; margin-left: 10px; margin-bottom: 10px;" srcset="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-45x45.jpeg 45w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-190x190.jpeg 190w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 100px) 100vw, 100px" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A British firm of solicitors, which specialises in helping victims of cybercrime claim compensation, has launched a £5 million (US $6.5 million) legal action against Ticketmaster.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: European fintech in the era of Brexit -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16973/european-fintech-in-the-era-of-brexit?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The world will never be the same again - regardless of when and under what conditions Brexit will ac...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:48:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC technology: Google's ethics board shut down -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-47825833</link><description>Just over a week after it was announced, an ethics board set up to oversee Google's AI has been shut.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 16:10:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Moynihan's call for unity, CFPB payday revamp, Morgan Stanley's AI strategy: Top stories of the week -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/list/moynihans-call-for-unity-cfpb-payday-revamp-morgan-stanleys-ai-strategy-top-stories-of-the-week</link><description>'There is no division in our industry': BofA's Moynihan says; why CFPB's payday revamp is an even bigger deal than you think; Morgan Stanley's new data strategy for higher quality AI; and more from this week's most-read stories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 18:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BusinessLine Money &amp; Banking: BharatPe raises $15 m in Series A round -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/money-and-banking/bharatpe-raises-15-m-in-series-a-round/article26749734.ece</link><description>BharatPe, a fintech start-up that provides  merchants with interoperable UPI QR codes, has raised $15.5 million in Series A funding. Insight Partners</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 21:49:20 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Russian Gas Giant Gazprom to Execute Business Contracts on a Blockchain -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/russian-gas-giant-gazprom-to-execute-business-contracts-on-a-blockchain</link><description>Russian state-owned gas giant Gazprom may soon begin using blockchain to execute and monitor contracts as part of its digitization plans.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coinbase CEO Names Three Things Crypto Needs for Mass Adoption -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-ceo-names-three-things-crypto-needs-for-mass-adoption</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82NzI4N2Y2MWUxZWU3YWUxNjUzYzA2NzFkZTJlMWNkMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong believes that crypto mass adoption mostly depends on volatility, scalability and usability&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:41:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: Amazon slammed by AI researchers for selling ‘biased’ facial recognition tech to cops -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/amazon-slammed-by-ai-researchers-for-selling-biased-facial-recognition-tech-to-cops</link><description>CAMBRIDGE, Mass. (AP) — Facial recognition technology was already seeping into everyday life — from your photos on Facebook to police scans of mugshots — when Joy Buolamwini noticed a serious glitch: Some of the software couldn't detect dark-skinned faces like hers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Xwo Malware scans the Internet for Exposed Services, Default Passwords -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83402/malware/xwo-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Researchers at AT&amp;#38;T Alien Labs have spotted a malware called Xwo that is actively scanning the Internet for exposed web services and default passwords. Experts at AT&amp;#38;T Alien Labs discovered a new piece of malware called Xwo that is actively scanning the Internet for exposed web services and default passwords. The name &amp;#8216;Xwo&amp;#8216; comes from [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83402/malware/xwo-malware.html"&gt;Xwo Malware scans the Internet for Exposed Services, Default Passwords&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Thai, Myanmar Central Bank Governors Endorse Blockchain Remittance Service -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/thai-myanmar-central-bank-governors-endorse-blockchain-remittance-service</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8wYWY4Yjc0MWMwZGZmOWY4ZDc0MDU4ZmQ5NWNmZDEwYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veerathai Santiprabhob, the Central bank governor of Thailand, reportedly endorsed startup Everex’s blockchain remittance system&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 16:05:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: Commercial Banks Turning to Fintechs to Improve Customer Experience, Report Says -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/04/commercial-banks-turning-to-fintechs-to-improve-customer-experience-report-says/</link><description>U.S. commercial banks are increasingly looking to fintechs to improve customer experience. In fact, a new Fraedom report shows that 73% of U.S. commercial banks are considering new fintech partnerships for improving either customer experience or security, and in some cases -- both. Customer experience has increasingly become a central theme in banking, both retail [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 16:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coinsquare Crypto Exchange Launches Canadian Dollar-Backed Stablecoin -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinsquare-crypto-exchange-launches-canadian-dollar-backed-stablecoin</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85OGMwYjc3YjA5MDBjNzk3OGI0ZTE2NDY2OTdlOGVlYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major cryptocurrency exchange Coinsquare will release a stablecoin pegged to the Canadian dollar&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 01:45:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Google to pull plug on AI ethics council -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/google-to-pull-plug-on-ai-ethics-council-11416582</link><description>Alphabet Inc's Google said on Thursday it was dissolving a council it had formed a week earlier to consider ethical issues around artificial intelligence and other emerging technologies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:50:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: RBS and Barclays trial blockchain tech to slash property transaction times -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33647/rbs-and-barclays-trial-blockchain-tech-to-slash-property-transaction-times?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>RBS and Barclays Bank have completed a blockchain trial with R3's distributed ledger software which...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: 13 Startups Making a Difference – Ireland FinTech Landscape -  Puntaje: 2800</title><link>https://gomedici.com/13-startups-making-difference-lreland-fintech-landscape/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/13-startups-making-difference-lreland-fintech-landscape.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;The year 2018 was a good year for FinTech startups in Ireland. The market witnessed increased optimism in the form of increased hiring by FinTech players and plans to raise more funds. In Ireland, RegTech &amp;amp;amp; digital identity, payment &amp;amp;amp; remittances, asset management solutions, and financial software are key categories in terms of the number of FinTech players. Here is a list of 13 startups making a difference in Ireland’s FinTech landscape: Future Finance was founded in 2013 and has raised $103.1 million in total funding. Future Finance offers student loans to undergraduate and postgraduate students in the UK within a range of £2,500–£40,000 per academic year. It offers education loans for covering living expenses and tuition fees. It claims to look at factors like the course and the university the student is attending as well as future career and income potential in order to arrive at credit decision. Future...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:56:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Finn AI Powers Chatbots in South Africa; Token Drives Open Banking in MENA -  Puntaje: 3700</title><link>https://finovate.com/finn-ai-powers-chatbots-in-south-africa-token-drives-open-banking-in-mena/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Finovate Global is our weekly look at fintech innovation in developing economies in Asia, Africa, the Middle East, Latin America, and Central and Eastern Europe. Central and Eastern Europe NF Innova to power “Customer-First” experience for APS Bank. Tinkoff Group of Russia builds supercomputer dubbed the most powerful in financial sector. Raiffeisen Bank Serbia picks Asseco &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/finn-ai-powers-chatbots-in-south-africa-token-drives-open-banking-in-mena/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/finn-ai-powers-chatbots-in-south-africa-token-drives-open-banking-in-mena/"&gt;Finn AI Powers Chatbots in South Africa; Token Drives Open Banking in MENA&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>