<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:33:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CoinDesk: Russian Gas Giant Gazprom to Execute Business Contracts on a Blockchain -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/russian-gas-giant-gazprom-to-execute-business-contracts-on-a-blockchain</link><description>Russian state-owned gas giant Gazprom may soon begin using blockchain to execute and monitor contracts as part of its digitization plans.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Open beta program launches for Sila’s API platform -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/open-beta-program-launches-for-silas-api-platform/</link><description>Aims to bridge gap between traditional banking systems and blockchain.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Sending Money Home to Myanmar Can Be Cheaper and Less Illegal with Blockchain -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29948/remittance/blockchain-myanmar-thailand-everex/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The central bank governors in both Thailand and Myanmar has just granted their blessing to the KTB Shewbank, a remittance project that uses blockchain to help reduce costs for Myanmarians&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29948/remittance/blockchain-myanmar-thailand-everex/"&gt;Sending Money Home to Myanmar Can Be Cheaper and Less Illegal with Blockchain&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: DLT &amp;amp; hybrid technology solutions are now more readily available -  Puntaje: 1900</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16975/dlt-amp-hybrid-technology-solutions-are-now-more-readily-available?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>There has been some exciting news from Digital Asset Holdings (DA) this week, with their announcemen...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 15:01:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Barclays, RBS, R3 Cut Property Transaction Times in Blockchain Trial -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/barclays-rbs-r3-cut-property-transaction-times-in-blockchain-trial</link><description>Barclays, Royal Bank of Scotland, R3 and more say they've reduced property transaction times to "less than three weeks" using a distributed ledger.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Now There’s a Canadian Dollar-Pegged Stablecoin on the Way -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/now-theres-a-canadian-dollar-pegged-stablecoin-on-the-way</link><description>Toronto-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinsquare is launching a stablecoin pegged 1:1 to the Canadian dollar.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortune: SEC Guidance Sparks Fear and Loathing in Crypto Industry -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>http://fortune.com/2019/04/05/sec-crypto-rules/</link><description>Chilling effects</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coinbase Makes LinkedIn’s ‘Top Companies 2019’ List as Lone Crypto Firm -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-makes-linkedins-top-companies-2019-list-as-lone-crypto-firm</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9iOTc2NGYxNDA3ZTE0NTM3NmRiODAwMGZkYmY4NWFkMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn rankings place Coinbase as only crypto player in top 50 U.S. employers&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:30:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Coinbase Tops JPMorgan in LinkedIn List of Most Popular Employers -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/coinbase-tops-jpmorgan-in-linkedin-list-of-most-popular-employers</link><description>Crypto exchange Coinbase has ranked above investment banking giant JPMorgan in LinkedIn’s top 50 U.S. employers list for 2019.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: US CFTC Chair Says Agency Has Resisted Calls to Suppress Development of Crypto Sector -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-cftc-chair-says-agency-has-resisted-calls-to-suppress-development-of-crypto-sector</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83OTI2MzgxZDM3MzcxZGQwY2Q5ZTcyOTNiYzcyZGFhNS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. CFTC Chairman J. Christopher Giancarlo has emphasized the agency’s commitment is to monitor, but not impede, the development of the crypto asset sector&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:53:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Cumberland Crypto OTC Desk Reports Spike in Large-Scale BTC Trades Within One Hour -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cumberland-crypto-otc-desk-reports-spike-in-large-scale-btc-trades-within-one-hour</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81OWNhMGY0NTZlOWE5YzFmYzg1MjNhYzBiZTY5YTE4YS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cumberland, the Chicago-based cryptocurrency trading unit of DRW Holdings LLC, reported a sharp, sudden spike in large Bitcoin transactions on Monday&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:31:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: AeroGarden maker says hackers stole months of credit card data -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/3kUV3azNeh4/</link><description>Bad news for home gardeners: criminals might have your credit card data. AeroGrow, the maker of the at-home garden kit AeroGarden, said in a letter to customers that its website had credit card scraping malware for more than four months. The company said anyone who bought something through its website between October 29, 2018 and [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Step By Step Office Dropper Dissection -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83381/malware/dropper-dissection.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Malware researcher and founder of Yoroi Marco Ramill described a step-by-step procedure that shows how to dissect an Office dropper. During the past few weeks, I received several emails asking how to dissect Office Payloads. While I was thinking about how to answer to such questions I received a MalSpam with a Microsoft Office document [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83381/malware/dropper-dissection.html"&gt;Step By Step Office Dropper Dissection&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Xwo Malware scans the Internet for Exposed Services, Default Passwords -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83402/malware/xwo-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Researchers at AT&amp;#38;T Alien Labs have spotted a malware called Xwo that is actively scanning the Internet for exposed web services and default passwords. Experts at AT&amp;#38;T Alien Labs discovered a new piece of malware called Xwo that is actively scanning the Internet for exposed web services and default passwords. The name &amp;#8216;Xwo&amp;#8216; comes from [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83402/malware/xwo-malware.html"&gt;Xwo Malware scans the Internet for Exposed Services, Default Passwords&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Ursnif: The Latest Evolution of the Most Popular Banking Malware -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83396/breaking-news/ursnif-banking-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;ZLab Yoroi-Cybaze dissected another attack wave of Ursnif Trojan, aka Gozi ISFB, an offspring of the original Gozi which source code was leaked in 2014. ZLab Yoroi-Cybaze dissected another attack wave of Ursnif Trojan, aka Gozi ISFB, an offspring of the original Gozi which source code was leaked in 2014. Introduction A few days ago, [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83396/breaking-news/ursnif-banking-malware.html"&gt;Ursnif: The Latest Evolution of the Most Popular Banking Malware&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: US Web Servers Hosted 10 Malware Families -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/us-web-servers-hosted-10-malware-1/</link><description>Nevadan bullet-proof hoster enables massive phishing operation</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Deutsche Bank releases API interface for instant payments in SAP ERP software -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33644/deutsche-bank-releases-api-interface-for-instant-payments-in-sap-erp-software?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Deutsche Bank has joined forces with software firm Serrala to launch an API interface for Sepa insta...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Where Electronic Payments Fall Short In B2B Commerce -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2019/velocit-electronic-procurement-digital-invoicing/</link><description>Adoption of electronic procurement, online B2B commerce and digital invoices are all on the rise, yet just because a company uses an online platform to sell or procure goods does not mean the actual payment for those goods will be digital, too. Indeed, an eProcurement system will often still require that companies complete the transaction […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: SocGen to offer payment services throughout Europe with Elavon -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/socgen-to-offer-payment-services-throughout-europe-with-elavon/</link><description>This includes United Kingdom, Austria, Belgium, Germany, Italy, Netherlands, Spain and Switzerland.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: IOC resumes fuel supplies to Jet Airways after assurance of payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/ioc-resumes-fuel-supplies-to-jet-airways-after-assurance-of-payments-119040500786_1.html</link><description>Earlier in the day, Jet Airways faced operational disruptions across major airports when IOC refused to refuel its planes without clearing the outstanding amount</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 18:51:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Business: Workforce diversity needs a rethink in digital economy -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/workplace/workforce-diversity-needs-a-rethink-in-digital-economy-20190328-p518ie.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_business</link><description>Older Australians want to work longer and more flexibly but business and government aren’t really onboard it would seem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Bitcoin trading volume drops to a two-year low in March: Report -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/international/bitcoin-trading-volume-drops-to-a-two-year-low-in-march-report-119040500094_1.html</link><description>Bitcoin volume in the top five digital currency exchanges totalled $2.14 billion last month, the lowest since April 2017 when volume was just $845.7 million</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Bitcoin trading volume hits two-year low in March: Report -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/bitcoin-trading-volume-hits-two-year-low-in-march-report-11415268</link><description>NEW YORK: Bitcoin's trading volume dropped to a two-year low in March, digital currency trading tool provider TradeBlock said in a report on Thursday, as investors remained spooked by increased regulatory scrutiny.

Bitcoin volume in the top five digital currency exchanges totalled US$2.14 billion ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 15:34:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: PayPal’s Blockchain First; Mastercard’s B2B FinTech Unicorn -  Puntaje: 3000</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2019/startup-investments-venture-capital-paypal-mastercard/</link><description>This week’s B2B venture capital funding rounds were particularly focused on the enterprise cybersecurity space, though B2B payments caught the attention of investors, too, with another industry unicorn making its debut. But just as noteworthy in this week’s roundup are the investors themselves, which include PayPal and Mastercard. Here’s a look at how more than […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Bud extolls the value of PHP for open banking -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33648/bud-extolls-the-value-of-php-for-open-banking?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>In an interview with Finextra, Bud’s chief information and security officer Merlin Gore maintains th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: SocGen Assurances and Roadzen team on contextual insurance venture -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33650/socgen-assurances-and-roadzen-team-on-contextual-insurance-venture?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Societe Generale Assurances has joined forces with AI insurtech specialist Roadzen to build a "digit...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Google pulls the plug on AI council that included Heritage Foundation leader -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/GVqd1XuA60Y/</link><description>Google has abandoned an advisory board on ethics in AI after critics questioned the inclusion of Kay Coles James, leader of the right-wing think tank the Heritage Foundation, on the 8-person panel. Google employees and thousands more concerned people called for this mistake to be corrected, and in response the company has apparently chosen to drop the whole thing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Where customers are also lenders: One fintech's payday alternative -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/where-customers-are-also-lenders-one-fintechs-payday-alternative</link><description>To generate revenue, SoLo Funds depends on consumers willing to front funds through its platform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 01:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Time Magazine business: Google Scraps New AI Ethics Council Amid Criticism -  Puntaje: 250.0</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/time/business/~3/HCCktRWnArQ/</link><description>A petition urged Google to remove a conservative think tank president from the panel over her positions on gay and transgender people</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 04:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Cambodia and Singapore strengthen cooperation in fintech innovation -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77946/cambodia-and-singapore-strengthen-cooperation-in-fintech-innovation?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) and the National Bank of Cambodia (NBC) today signed a Mem...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Mitsui Sumitomo Just Launched Their Digital Hub in Singapore -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29939/insurtech/mitsui-sumitomo-digital-hub-singapore-insurtech-insurance/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Mitsui Sumitomo an insurance giant hailing from Japan, and they just announced the setup of their global digital hub in Singapore—at its Asia regional office. The digital hub has been&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29939/insurtech/mitsui-sumitomo-digital-hub-singapore-insurtech-insurance/"&gt;Mitsui Sumitomo Just Launched Their Digital Hub in Singapore&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 05:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: JPMorgan's Dimon apprehensive of China's prowess in AI and fintech -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33641/jpmorgans-dimon-apprehensive-of-chinas-prowess-in-ai-and-fintech?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>JPMorgan Chase chief Jamie Dimon has admitted to being worried about the progress China has made in...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian technology: Google scraps AI ethics council after backlash: 'Back to the drawing board' -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/04/google-ai-ethics-council-backlash</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Decision comes after employees called for the removal of a rightwing thinktank leader from the council&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google is ending a new artificial intelligence ethics council just one week after launching it, following &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/01/google-kay-coles-james-removal-employees-letter"&gt;protests from employees&lt;/a&gt; over the appointment of a rightwing thinktank leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapid downfall of the Advanced Technology External Advisory Council (ATEAC), which was dedicated to “the responsible development of AI”, came after more than 2,000 Google workers signed a &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@against.transphobia/googlers-against-transphobia-and-hate-b1b0a5dbf76"&gt;petition&lt;/a&gt; criticizing the company’s selection of an anti-LGBT advocate.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/04/google-ai-ethics-council-backlash"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 01:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Nigerian fintech Kudi raises $5 million -  Puntaje: 2400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77945/nigerian-fintech-kudi-raises-5-million?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Kudi, the Nigerian leader of digital payment and collection for the cash economy, raises a Series A...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: What To Expect With The Future Of AI Technology -  Puntaje: 3200</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/what-to-expect-with-the-future-of-ai-technology-782aec311a54?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are many new technological innovations that are changing how we live our lives, but artificial intelligence, or AI, may present the most exciting changes. While AI has been around for a while now, recent improvements have made the technology much more adaptable. Looking into the future, it’s easy to predict a world in which artificial intelligence plays a more significant role in our daily lives.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*inrFYFWZ_e1QrZO72J49NQ.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Most Promising AI Innovations on the Horizon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, artificial intelligence is going to change almost every aspect of daily life. While we will look for ways to make use of it in the home, AI will also be adopted by local and state governments, as well as by the business sector. Before long, there will be few things unaffected by AI technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting Around with AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Self-driving cars are already beginning to make their way on the roadways, but we can expect this technology to advance considerably in the coming years. The &lt;a href="https://www.transportation.gov/AV"&gt;U.S. Department of Transportation has started making regulations about the use of AI-driven vehicles&lt;/a&gt; and, as a result, they have designated three levels of self-driving vehicles. Currently, we’re at the lowest level with Google’s version of the vehicle, which still requires a human driver to be at the wheel. Ultimately, the goal is to create an entirely automated self-driving car, which is expected to be much safer. Logistics companies and public transportation services are also looking at incorporating AI technology to create self-driving trucks, buses, taxis, and planes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI and Robotics Will Come Together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The field of cybernetics has already begun to meld with artificial intelligence and that trend is expected to continue. By incorporating AI technology into robotics, we’ll soon be able to enhance our own bodies, giving us greater strength, longevity, and endurance. While cybernetics may help us enhance our healthy bodies, the application of this technology is really aimed at helping the disabled. Those individuals, who have amputated limbs or permanent paralysis, can be given a much higher quality of life. Cybernetic limbs that can communicate with the brain can become almost as useful as natural limbs. In the future, artificial limbs may even become stronger, faster, and more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Will Help Create Fully Functional Robots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to helping us enhance our bodies, AI technology is also expected to help us create artificial lifeforms. Science fiction has long suggested the concept of human-like robots that are capable of complex interactions. That future may not be very far off at this point. As the field of robotics advances and incorporates AI technology, robots will become useful in a variety of ways. They can take on dangerous jobs and do work that poses health risks to people. Even today, drones and less sophisticated robots are performing welding and other hazardous tasks, though they’re typically controlled by an operator via a remote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Will AI Technology Change Our Lives on a Personal Level?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence has already made its way into many homes, but it will soon be indispensable in most households. As we move closer toward becoming a technologically driven society, AI applications will fulfill the promise that computers would make our lives easier. AI technology will help us live happier and healthier lives, while also helping us conserve time, energy, and money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll Have a Virtual Assistant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people already make use of AI-driven personal assistants. Amazon’s Echo and Alexa currently dominate the market, but the competition is beginning to offer more virtual assistants to choose from. What can they do for you? Currently, they can provide information, such as a weather report, and order services, such as place your weekly pizza delivery order. They’re also used to control smart home devices from the stereo to the thermostat. In the future, AI-driven virtual assistants will anticipate your needs and fulfill them without the need to give them instructions. For instance, if you grill steaks every Friday, your virtual assistant can have fresh steaks delivered to the home every Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Face Will Become Your ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re already seeing biometric incorporated into our daily lives and that technology is expected to evolve. Eventually, many in the tech industry anticipate AI-driven applications allowing machines to recognize your face to complete transactions. Your credit cards and driver’s license may be linked to your face, allowing pattern recognition devices to know you instantly. This can make everyday transactions far more efficient, saving us from having to wait in line at the store, bank, or movie theater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Receive Better Medical Care&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research is already underway to develop new software applications that use AI to help doctors diagnose and treat patients. It won’t be long before wearable devices can measure blood sugar levels for diabetics and transmit that data to the patient’s doctor. Already, devices are in use that measure heart rate, respiration, and other vital functions. Artificial intelligence may also help patients better understand their care options and communicate more effectively with their caregivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Responses Will Be More Empathetic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internet users have already seen the effect artificial intelligence has had when they visit a website with a chatbot. In the past, chatbots were pre-programmed to give specific answers to specific inquiries. Today, artificial intelligence software allows chatbots and virtual personal assistants to research any question and provide an accurate response. While that is impressive, there’s still room for advancement. Ultimately, AI-driven devices will analyze our speech or actions to interpret our needs, so they can offer more insightful information. This type of programming might best be described as “digital empathy” and it may provide the best human-device interactions possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Caring for Children and the Elderly Will Be Easier&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both virtual assistants and robots may advance to a &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/artificial-intelligence-is-becoming-better-than-human-expertise-16903f4fc3c0"&gt;level nearing human efficiency&lt;/a&gt;, which means these devices will be able to care for those needing supervision. Down the line, robots may be able to care for your child or elder parent. This can free up your time and, in cases of the elderly, prevent them from needing to move into an assisted living facility. Elders can stay at home, where they feel more comfortable, while the robot performs functions to keep the individual healthy and safe from harm. The rising concern over elder abuse and neglect may make this one of the most anticipated applications for artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hollywood May Become Obsolete&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, streaming sites, like &lt;a href="http://moviesjoy.net/"&gt;moviesjoy.net&lt;/a&gt;, use a form of AI to offer suggestions, based on your previous television and film viewing patterns. Similarly, sites like Spotify and Pandora use AI to help you create stations that exclusively play your favorite music. This is just the beginning, as far as how AI will cater to our entertainment interests. In the future, AI applications may analyze our interests and draw upon them to create music and shows that use digital performers. Since everything will be based on personal preferences, we’ll rarely have to sit through a “flop” or a bad song.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As artificial intelligence continues to evolve, these innovations will likely be overshadowed by even greater advancements. While there’s no way to know for sure how far AI technology will advance, it does seem obvious that it will become an integral part of our lives. Already, we often use AI-driven technology without even realizing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fupscri.be%2Fdde502%3Fas_embed%3Dtrue&amp;amp;dntp=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fupscri.be%2Fhackernoon%2F&amp;amp;image=https%3A%2F%2Fucarecdn.com%2F57662ddc-da7c-407b-afcb-cb45184b2705%2F&amp;amp;key=d04bfffea46d4aeda930ec88cc64b87c&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;schema=upscri" width="800" height="400" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/3c851dac986ab6dbb2d1aaa91205a8eb/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/3c851dac986ab6dbb2d1aaa91205a8eb/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=782aec311a54" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/what-to-expect-with-the-future-of-ai-technology-782aec311a54"&gt;What To Expect With The Future Of AI Technology&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 07:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: M&amp;A on the rise as Visa &amp; Mastercard go for the Trillion $ Cross Border Payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/04/05/ma-on-the-rise-as-visa-mastercard-go-for-the-trillion-cross-border-payments/</link><description>The Cross border payments market was at $22 Trillion three years ago as per a research by the Boston Consulting Group. Certainly a market to go after, and Visa and Mastercard do not seem to be shy of throwing punches at each other in the process. So who got their nose ahead? Earlier this year, [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 04:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Deutsche Enables Instant SEPA Payments Within Treasurers’ ERP Platforms -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2019/deutsche-bank-serrala-real-time-api-solution-erp/</link><description>Deutsche Bank is collaborating with financial software company Serrala to roll out an API interface aimed at linking corporate treasurers across Europe with real-time payments access. New reports in DerTreasurer this week said the companies have launched the API interface, which links corporate customers to SEPA instant payments as part of the Serrala FS2 Payments […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Deutsche Bank and Serrala launch API interface for SEPA payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/deutsche-bank-and-serrala-launch-api-interface-for-sepa-payments/</link><description>A step towards facilitating real-time treasury.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Cluley: Ticketmaster is hit by a £5 million legal action after online payment card theft -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.grahamcluley.com/ticketmaster-is-hit-by-a-5-million-legal-action-after-online-payment-card-theft/</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.grahamcluley.com/ticketmaster-is-hit-by-a-5-million-legal-action-after-online-payment-card-theft/" title="Ticketmaster is hit by a £5 million legal action after online payment card theft"&gt;&lt;img width="100" height="100" src="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-150x150.jpeg" class="attachment-100x100 size-100x100 wp-post-image" alt="Ticketmaster is hit by a £5 million legal action after online payment card theft" style="float: right; margin-left: 10px; margin-bottom: 10px;" srcset="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-45x45.jpeg 45w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb-190x190.jpeg 190w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/ticketmaster-thumb.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 100px) 100vw, 100px" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A British firm of solicitors, which specialises in helping victims of cybercrime claim compensation, has launched a £5 million (US $6.5 million) legal action against Ticketmaster.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: South Korea, a FinTech Hub-To-Be? -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16972/south-korea-a-fintech-hub-to-be?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The neutral status quo The current situation in South Korea is what you might call “meh” for FinTech...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Top fintech stories this week – 5 March 2019 -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/top-fintech-stories-this-week-5-march-2019/</link><description>Catch up on FinTech Futures' top five fintech stories of the week - all in one place!</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: Google dissolves AI advisory board amid employee protest -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/google-dissolves-ai-advisory-board-amid-employee-protest</link><description>The controversy over Google naming a conservative thinker and alleged "anti-trans, anti-LGBT" supporter to a company advisory board has ended with the whole project scrapped.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Tax Software CryptoTrader.Tax Integrates With TurboTax -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-tax-software-cryptotradertax-integrates-with-turbotax</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82ODFlMDgyMTg2NTBkYzdkYmFmZTQ0MWYzN2YwZDQ4NC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto tax software startup CryptoTrader.Tax has integrated with major U.S. tax filing software TurboTax&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 02:15:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News technology: Amazon slammed by AI researchers for selling ‘biased’ facial recognition tech to cops -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/amazon-slammed-by-ai-researchers-for-selling-biased-facial-recognition-tech-to-cops</link><description>CAMBRIDGE, Mass. (AP) — Facial recognition technology was already seeping into everyday life — from your photos on Facebook to police scans of mugshots — when Joy Buolamwini noticed a serious glitch: Some of the software couldn't detect dark-skinned faces like hers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Barclays, RBS Join 40-Strong R3 Blockchain Real Estate Trial -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/barclays-rbs-join-40-strong-r3-blockchain-real-estate-trial</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9kZjI5ZDM5YmVhZDZkNjA1ZTE2NTgyNTk0NzgyMjhkZi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Royal Bank of Scotland tells of renewed blockchain enthusiasm following real estate use case trial&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:17:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coinsquare Crypto Exchange Launches Canadian Dollar-Backed Stablecoin -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinsquare-crypto-exchange-launches-canadian-dollar-backed-stablecoin</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85OGMwYjc3YjA5MDBjNzk3OGI0ZTE2NDY2OTdlOGVlYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major cryptocurrency exchange Coinsquare will release a stablecoin pegged to the Canadian dollar&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 01:45:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Google to pull plug on AI ethics council -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/google-to-pull-plug-on-ai-ethics-council-11416582</link><description>Alphabet Inc's Google said on Thursday it was dissolving a council it had formed a week earlier to consider ethical issues around artificial intelligence and other emerging technologies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:50:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: ACI Worldwide Exec Warns APIs, ISO 20022 ‘Completely Incompatible’ -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2019/aci-worldwide-api-iso-20022/</link><description>Payments messaging firm SWIFT announced Thursday (April 4) the establishment of an ISO 20022 working group to promote adoption of the payments messaging standard. But as the financial services industry embraces ISO 20022, the market is also shifting toward an open banking model and API adoption — two trends an ACI Worldwide executive warns are […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: RBS and Barclays trial blockchain tech to slash property transaction times -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33647/rbs-and-barclays-trial-blockchain-tech-to-slash-property-transaction-times?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>RBS and Barclays Bank have completed a blockchain trial with R3's distributed ledger software which...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: 13 Startups Making a Difference – Ireland FinTech Landscape -  Puntaje: 2800</title><link>https://gomedici.com/13-startups-making-difference-lreland-fintech-landscape/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/13-startups-making-difference-lreland-fintech-landscape.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;The year 2018 was a good year for FinTech startups in Ireland. The market witnessed increased optimism in the form of increased hiring by FinTech players and plans to raise more funds. In Ireland, RegTech &amp;amp;amp; digital identity, payment &amp;amp;amp; remittances, asset management solutions, and financial software are key categories in terms of the number of FinTech players. Here is a list of 13 startups making a difference in Ireland’s FinTech landscape: Future Finance was founded in 2013 and has raised $103.1 million in total funding. Future Finance offers student loans to undergraduate and postgraduate students in the UK within a range of £2,500–£40,000 per academic year. It offers education loans for covering living expenses and tuition fees. It claims to look at factors like the course and the university the student is attending as well as future career and income potential in order to arrive at credit decision. Future...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:56:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Firm Bitpanda Secures Payments Service Provider License Under EU Rules -  Puntaje: 3000</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-firm-bitpanda-secures-payments-service-provider-license-under-eu-rules</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80ODllNzRiMmIxMjhjZTMwMjI0ZWZiYjE4NGVmYWYyOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viennese crypto and fintech firm Bitpanda has received a payment service provider license from Austria’s financial regulator in accordance with EU-wide rules&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: 10 Top Industries To Be Transformed By Artificial Intelligence, Soon -  Puntaje: 6400</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/10-top-industries-to-be-transformed-by-artificial-intelligence-soon-4eb807551f82?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/700/0*SD5p-tRXdmqxXe2c" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence has revolutionized the way people work today. From streamlining business operations to better decision-making process, it has shown its real potential across different industries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a study by &lt;strong&gt;PWC&lt;/strong&gt;, the global GDP is going to be 14% increased in 2030 that will result in higher AI adoption. Thus, it will contribute an additional $15.7 trillion to the whole economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;In this blog, we will discuss some of the top industries that will be revolutionized by Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check out the list below.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/industries/manufacturing?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manufacturing Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/750/0*n2LSI9OOwwH00syI" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This tech has unlimited potential in the world of manufacturing. From preventive maintenance to the human tasks automation, AI will allow a more efficient work that will be much error free and has higher quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The initiatives of technology giants like Microsoft (AI for accessibility) and smaller leading companies like AtBot will revolutionize AI for all information workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/industries/education-elearning-software-development?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we are moving ahead with a new generation in the &lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/industries/education-elearning-software-development?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;educational industry&lt;/a&gt;, it becomes quite obvious that the change is needed to make their basic concepts clear. The most pressing question is what that change should be and how to achieve it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leveraging artificial intelligence to create a customized, dynamic and effective learning path for any subject can be an incredible facilitator for such a revolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/industries/healthcare-software-development-services?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Healthcare Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/790/0*XxA63u96htwcKu5k" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This industry has transformed with AI and benefitting a number of people across the globe. Computerized X-ray vision shows promises to help detect diseases, natural language processing (NLP) shows promise in drug safety, and ML shows promises of finding patterns within a population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of true interoperability of information, which supports the safe exchange of health data, all these promises will join forces to become advances for patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Related Blog: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/9-ways-blockchain-iot-union-help-elevate-your-business-value-36337ee7bafc?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;9 Ways Blockchain-IoT Union Help Elevate Your Business Value&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/it-strategy-consulting-firms?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IT Service Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI technology, when used in corporate and government networks, will be a dominant feature of IT service management (ITSM) in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI will improve the use of technology in homes and in the workplace. AI technology will cause a disruptive change in ITSM offers in three key areas of Point of Entry (creation of incidents/requests), automated back-end processes and knowledge management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI will affect the IT services management industry in the coming years, mainly due to the resolution of recurring losses, self-service for low-level incidents, improved organization and optimization and instant information, such as meeting times through personal assistants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5) Energy &amp;amp; Mining&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence industry can be implemented in smart power grids to be more efficient in the supply of energy and to predict when batteries and other equipment will fail. The implementation of AI will make energy exploration an easier and more economical task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence &amp;amp; Future, &lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/hire-developers/hire-machine-learning-experts?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt;, are trends that will disturb the energy industry, which will generate huge savings opportunities. Large companies like &lt;a href="https://www.ge.com/"&gt;General Electric&lt;/a&gt; are looking to the future to use artificial intelligence to optimize the way electricity comes out of batteries and points of consumption. According to Bloomberg News reports, artificial intelligence technology in energy and mining could eventually save $ 200 billion worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/industries/logistics-transportation-software-development?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply Chain Management Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The future of artificial intelligence can account for more factors and complicated non-linear dependencies and correlated data much better than a human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence can predict the future without human bias, but with an adequate risk assessment, and find optimal decisions even under an asymmetric cost profile. This leads to improvements in each decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/industries/retail-ecommerce-software-development?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fashion Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/770/0*gQc6mJfmlmsDLDpS" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this industry, change has been seen by the revolution of artificial intelligence for learning about purchasing patterns of consumers across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence in industry predicts the latest fashion trends which is a great implementation till now. It helps users choosing their desired clothes from their favorite fashion store and they can easily choose from as engine backed by AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8) Agriculture industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using artificial intelligence in industry, Agricultural specialists are developing autonomous robots programmed to handle routine agricultural tasks, such as harvesting crops in a larger volume of human workers. The most popular applications of AI in agriculture range from robotics to crop and soil monitoring to predictive analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI is implemented in the monitoring of crops and soils, implementing computer vision and deep learning algorithms to process data captured by drones and/or software-based technology to monitor the health of crops and soil. Predictive models of automated learning guided analysis are being developed to track and predict the impact on crop yields that face erratic climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9) Infrastructure Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The revolution of artificial intelligence is going to give a boost to this industry. It ensures the data can be systematically processed and organized in order to help in knowing the urban areas and how they are changing at a fast pace these days. Artificial intelligence industry provides a different and new way of looking at the growth and development, safety, utility use, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.valuecoders.com/industries/retail-ecommerce-software-development?utm_source=ai_industries_alka_medium=alka_medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Retail &amp;amp; e-commerce Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*EIEKlZhUEcOpOjeR" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This industry is greatly impacted by AI 2019. The global spending of this is expected to increase to $ 7.3 billion per year by 2022. Retailers will use virtual reality and augmented functionality in advertising. The immersive display of the product catalog will grow dramatically, and shoppers will experience the products before buying. It is anticipated that by 2020, chatbots will boost 85% of all customer service interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far we have seen the list of industries to get transformed with the revolution of artificial intelligence in 2019. It is redefining industries by automating processes, disrupting how business work and automating processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a tremendous opportunity for AI to increase human capabilities in all industries while capitalizing on unique human capabilities for creativity and agility, human characteristics that are hard to imitate for computers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence, Businesses expect AI to have a positive impact on growth (90%), productivity (86%), innovation (84%) and job creation (69%) in their country and industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fupscri.be%2Fdde502%3Fas_embed%3Dtrue&amp;amp;dntp=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fupscri.be%2Fhackernoon%2F&amp;amp;image=https%3A%2F%2Fucarecdn.com%2F57662ddc-da7c-407b-afcb-cb45184b2705%2F&amp;amp;key=d04bfffea46d4aeda930ec88cc64b87c&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;schema=upscri" width="800" height="400" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/3c851dac986ab6dbb2d1aaa91205a8eb/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/3c851dac986ab6dbb2d1aaa91205a8eb/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=4eb807551f82" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/10-top-industries-to-be-transformed-by-artificial-intelligence-soon-4eb807551f82"&gt;10 Top Industries To Be Transformed By Artificial Intelligence, Soon&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 07:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>