<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:41:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cointelegraph: Blockchain Art Registry Acquires Database With Info From 4K Auction Houses -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-art-registry-acquires-database-with-info-from-4k-auction-houses</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83NDk5Zjc4ZGZjMTYxNjJiMWYzNjA5NDIyN2M1NzMxMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockchain art startup Artory acquires art auction database that hosts info from 4,000 art auction houses&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Duke University Partners for Blockchain Lab, Education Program -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/duke-university-partners-for-blockchain-lab-education-program</link><description>Duke University is teaming up with Citizens Reserve to help students learn about blockchain tech and get hands-on with real projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 19:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Blockchain in Biometrics Could be Used in Travel Security, US Customs Rep Says -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-in-biometrics-could-be-used-in-travel-security-us-customs-rep-says</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9kMjU3NGFhMDNjY2VmYmE1NzQxMTdkMTk4MTIwNzlkNC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using blockchain for biometric tracking would be the technology’s killer app in the travel security sector, a rep from the U.S. Customs and Border Protection stated&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: The UAE is the happiest Arab country in the world, for the 5th year in a row -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/trending/uae-happiest-country-2018/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1052977871-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1052977871-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1052977871-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;The UAE might be investing in blockchain, IoT and other non-oil sectors and technologies, but most importantly, it has been investing in the happiness of its citizens, both local and expat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It launched its National Programme for Happiness in 2016, and appointed a Minister of State for Happiness. In 2017, Dubai launched the world's first "World Happiness Council."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, it is reaping the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the International Happiness Day which coincides on March 20th, the United Nations Sustainable Development Solutions Network (SDSN) released its annual World Happiness Report (WHR), ranking 156 countries based on their happiness averages from 2016-2018. Once more, the UAE has continued to outperform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the 5th consecutive year, the UAE has ranked 1st in the Gulf region. Internationally, it came 21st, one spot below last year's, replaced by the Czech Republic. It ranked better than countries like Spain and France.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saudi, on the other hand, came in 28th place. Bahrain followed at 37th. Kuwait ranked 51st.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere in the Middle East and beyond, Lebanon came in at 91st. Jordan ranked 101st. Egypt was 137th. India came in at 140th. The United States secured a position for itself in the top 20, coming it at 19th place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for the top 10 happiest countries, the list goes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Finland&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Denmark&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Norway&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Iceland&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. Netherlands&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6. Switzerland&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7. Sweden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8. New Zealand&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9. Canada&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10. Austria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to a statement issued by the SDSN, "Results from the most recent World Happiness Report, released on March 20, 2019 at the United Nations Headquarters in New York, indicate positive trends for the UAE since 2016."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The UAE nationals recorded high happiness scores," the statement continued. "Furthermore, living in the UAE shows a positive impact on the lives of residents; the happiness scores of residents living in the UAE are higher than their scores in their home countries."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In recent years, the UAE has implemented several pieces of legislation to make the lives of expats better. In 2018, the country announced a 10-year expat visa which went into effect this year. It also made it possible for foreigners to obtain 100% ownership of a business in certain trade zones. To encourage young talent to remain in the country, students with exceptional academic performance will qualify for a five-year visa for themselves and their families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/trending/uae-happiest-country-2018/"&gt;The UAE is the happiest Arab country in the world, for the 5th year in a row&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 08:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Market Networks: A Four Year Perspective -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/market-networks-a-four-year-perspective-2193f16d6e5e?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*LVJq74bWeUBwaRp0fmp2rw.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Networks as a term today still has no clear definition or even a wiki page, yet it’s pretty easy to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Networks as a concept made a relatively big splash among VCs back in 2015 as evidenced by publications in TechCrunch and NFX (a venture fund):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;TechCrunch: &lt;a href="https://techcrunch.com/2015/06/27/from-social-to-market-networks/"&gt;From Social Networks To Market Networks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NFX: &lt;a href="https://www.nfx.com/post/10-years-about-market-networks"&gt;The Next 10 Years Will Be About “Market Networks”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s been four years, however, where’s the hype?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this article I am going to do a bit of explanation of what a market network is and offer a perspective. (Spoiler: if you follow me, you know it’s about blockchain).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What is a market network?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make it really short, a market network is a blend of a marketplace and a social network with a SaaS solution to help the service providers — who are individuals in the market network as opposed to companies — work with customers and other service providers on longer-lasting and more complex projects instead of just quick transactions like on Uber or eBay. Although, as one user on Hacker News remarked, “the SaaS part seems just thrown in there, like ketchup on French food.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marketplaces are primarily about transactions, even though there are definitely reviews and the overall score that potential customers base their purchasing decisions on. Most people check the driver score when ordering a ride on Uber, same with eBay and purchasing products, and so on. These, however, are marketplaces since buyers and sellers meet there for a one-off transaction. Marketplaces are aggregators of sellers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social networks are — well, they are social networks. People communicate and build relationships on LinkedIn, Facebook and so on. Commerce is not the core objective of social networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, now you have two separate places for your online presence and commerce: a marketplace to sell stuff, and a social network to build relationships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What, however, if you provide a service that is more complex than a mere buy-sell transaction. And on top of that, what if you need collaboration with other professionals in your industry to form a team to provide an end-to-end service?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, that’s where market networks come in. In the market network, you are a service provider, but also a person with a profile, with history, reviews, score, etc. You can team up with other people to provide a complex service to a customer and channel the workflow through a SaaS solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four years ago HoneyBook was lauded as the prime example of this new class of market network startups, and VCs competed to invest in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HoneyBook was a market network for the events planner industry. A typical HoneyBook scenario would be:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;You sign up as an event planner — an individual willing to provide the service.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You build your profile with HoneyBook, and it’s your home on the Web.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You use the built-in SaaS solution to work with your customers, send proposals, digitally sign contracts and so on.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You also team up with other professionals in the HoneyBook network, those that have profiles and reputation, to provide end-to-end service for an event. An example would be you doing all the planning for a customer’s wedding, working with a person who does photography, and signing up a florist for the event. When the event is done, everyone gets paid.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Makes sense, right? The world is ultimately moving towards the highest granularity level in how people work with each other — the level of an individual — including the provision of services. Market networks seem to be in tune with this, and back in 2015 it was proclaimed that the next decade was going to be about market networks, just like the previous one was about social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s been four years, however, and the hype is just not there. Honeybook seems to have pivoted to a project management SaaS solution. What happened?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t have any insider knowledge, but I do have a perspective that I’d like to share.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;A quick stroll down the web evolution lane&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might have heard the word Web 1.0, Web 2.0, and Web 3.0 ad nauseam, but I am going to use these terms since they are easiest to set the right context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Web 1.0&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The very loose period for Web 1.0 is the 90s to early 2000s. This was when suddenly anyone was able to turn their connected computer into a web server and become an active part of the Internet. The ease of feeding your information to the anyone online was a great business and entrepreneurship opportunity, and it peaked roughly at the turn of the century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Web 2.0&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mid-2000s to roughly present days. While Web 1.0 was more of an online bulletin board where you could publish anything but in one direction and have no real feedback, Web 2.0 was more about collaboration and cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term that marked Web 2.0 was &lt;em&gt;platform&lt;/em&gt;. The Internet was now all about platforms where you could communicate with other people online, exchange information, and create things together. Platformization became the new king. And it was great too. Instead of having a constellation of very different and wacky websites that you could check for information — as you would a billboard — you were able now to become an active part of a platform. Not only that, but you were able to earn too — for example, by renting out your room on Airbnb and building customer rapport through a review system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The thing with Web 2.0 is that it’s all about &lt;em&gt;platforms&lt;/em&gt; — from Reddit to Uber. And platforms are containerized versions of the network economy. They are isolated networks that can’t communicate with each other. And on top of that, they really don’t want to, because they always belong to someone. And that someone is never the community that brings value to the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Web 3.0&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of opinions on what Web 3.0 is or should be, with the key point being that its defining characteristic is true collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;True collaboration, however, is a pretty vague phrase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make Web 3.0 more specific and in context with the two previous stages of the World Wide Web development, I’d propose the following two defining characteristics that are not vague:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The isolated economy networks currently represented by and embodied in platforms cannot be isolated.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The platforms must belong to the members that bring value to them and so they must be a network.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;That platforms cannot be isolated is illustrated by the history repeating itself — there was no World Wide Web in the 80s, it was all isolated networks. Just like you weren’t able to browse the Internet at the time and willy-nilly hop from one web server to a different one when viewing a document online, you can’t use, for example, your Reddit karma to run a shop on Amazon today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which brings to the second point: platforms cannot be platforms. Currently, the level of granularity on the Internet is per platform, not per person. You can have an account on Kickstarter, but you can’t use it on GitHub. These are two completely isolated networks. The level of granularity must go one order lower — to the person. People — or more like our digital representations — a) must be able to operate independently from platforms, and b) the network they operate in and bring value to must belong to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Where does that put market networks?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;See, I think that market networks, while in a way in tune with where the world is moving in terms of granularization to an individual, are stuck in the Web 2.0 mindset, while we are transitioning to Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, market network platforms are platforms and are seen as platforms. They are isolated and containerized. They further fragment the web. To be successful in operating a business in this vast digital space that only keeps growing in user numbers, you must maintain your profile in many networks — social or market — and you can’t effortlessly scale your reputation from one network to a different one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What if your digital selfhood on the Web always belonged to you — not to a service — and the reputation of your digital selfhood was maintained by the network. The network that also belongs to you? That would be the decentralized reputation that you’d be able to plug into any other centralized network, including market networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not that easy for a centralized market network to differentiate among service providing platforms and it takes a lot of effort to build a platform profile that you can use only in an isolated network. When your reputation is decentralized, the entirety of the digital space becomes your market network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockchain is the ultimate infrastructure tool that gives individuals true ownership of their digital selfhood and reputation. And that’s the biggest differentiator that matters in the transition to Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decentralized, pluggable, or portable — call it what you will — is the key component, not a SaaS solution in an isolated network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, this is what we are doing with &lt;a href="https://u.community/faq"&gt;U°Community&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=2193f16d6e5e" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/market-networks-a-four-year-perspective-2193f16d6e5e"&gt;Market Networks: A Four Year Perspective&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Crypto Lawyer Drew Hinkes Joins Firm to Help ICO Issuers Fight Back -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/blockchain-lawyer-drew-hinkes-joins-new-firm-to-help-ico-issuers-fight-back</link><description>Blockchain lawyer Andrew Hinkes has joined has joined legal services firm Carlton Fields, where he will focus on litigating cases for token sellers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Is Blockchain Really Immutable? -  Puntaje: 4800</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/is-blockchain-really-immutable-a527d10f4977?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*mxwl0_gdFfhnpXeh8RozCA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;While the Bitcoin boom may have given blockchain the wings to fly, this emerging technology has managed to soar to new heights all by itself. As it has flown higher, further, faster, it has been fueled by qualities unique and sublime, one of them being the so-called trait of immutability.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockchain’s widely lauded immutability entails that data once entered cannot be modified by unscrupulous actors, or anyone for that matter. While this may sound like the perfect way to send the auditors packing, we cannot help but wonder:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;is blockchain’s supposedly perfect immutability too good to be true?&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Immutability in Blockchain?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before dissecting the issues that threaten to derail the golden promise of immutability, we must briefly have a look at what it is, how it works. Each block of information, be it facts or transaction details, is processed using cryptographic principles so that a hash value, represented by an alphanumeric string, can be generated for that block. Each block bears the hash value, or digital signature for not just its own block, but also the one previous to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This process ensures that all the blocks are retroactively chained together quite inexorably. This aspect of the blockchain is responsible for making sure that nobody can break in and change the data recorded in one block without effectively dismantling the entire system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given that blockchain is developed as being decentralised and distributed, a consensus reached between the numerous nodes that store a copy of the data, is responsible for making sure that a single version of truth is maintained. No single entity has overarching control and any changes must be simultaneously reflected in all the node servers involved. However, even such a robust mechanism is not without its challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threats to Blockchain’s Immutability.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first chink in this shining armour is the possibility of a 51% attack. In blockchain networks supporting transactions, like the Bitcoin blockchain or any blockchain underlying a cryptocurrency, this could translate to being a “double spending attack”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have already mentioned that this decentralised form of technology has no single entity pulling all the strings of a network. Yet, if miners band together in a group and become strong enough to amass a majority of the hashing power, it can spell doom for the immutability factor of a blockchain. Today, with the rise in mining marketplaces and the ability to rent out mining capacity, it is becoming increasingly easy to orchestrate such an attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be slightly more difficult and expensive to execute in the case of large blockchain networks, especially those run using the proof-of-work consensus protocol (like Bitcoin) because of the sheer amount of hashing power it would require to bring them down. Even so, the smaller coins and blockchain startups seem to be at definite risk, as exemplified by the double spending attacks waged on &lt;a href="https://medium.com/u/651c03c5e4c2"&gt;Bitcoin Gold&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://medium.com/u/23b9ad8fa8a1"&gt;Litecoin Cash&lt;/a&gt;, Monacoin and so on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By modifying the transaction data that was supposed to be “immutable”, the attackers managed to reverse high-value transactions and spend those amounts for a second time. Keeping the gains of the attackers in context, there have been several attempts to calculate the amount required to launch a 51% attack on various well-known cryptocurrency-oriented blockchain networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As revealed by researchers like NYU’s Joseph Bonneau and tracked by websites such as &lt;a href="https://www.crypto51.app"&gt;https://www.crypto51.app&lt;/a&gt;, the cost of attacking a small-scale blockchain network may be quite little for the amount of access it promises. For example, according to the latter, the cost of attacking the Litecoin blockchain for an hour is about $39,018, which can be recouped if enough high-value transactions are tapped into and reversed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another new challenge that is threatening to strip blockchain of its prized trait of immutability is the power of quantum computing. Very recently, top managers of tech behemoth &lt;a href="https://medium.com/u/4fc26a87d76"&gt;IBM&lt;/a&gt; have stated that quantum computing can potentially reverse engineer public keys of blockchain networks to find the private keys with which to break in to the system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per &lt;a href="https://medium.com/u/80bcb5edce04"&gt;Jesse Lund&lt;/a&gt;, the vice president of blockchain and digital currencies at IBM, it is a “real and credible threat” that is likely to affect nearly 50% of all blockchains. A while back, even the &lt;a href="https://medium.com/u/defe73a9b0ba"&gt;MIT Technology Review&lt;/a&gt; had drawn attention to the problem, suggesting that it would be mere “child’s play” for powerful quantum computers to shatter the cryptographic protection standing at guard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So, What Is the Solution?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To tackle the blockchain bully that is 51% attack, experts often suggest building a stronger protocol, and using consensus algorithms like Proof of Stake (because it is more difficult to stake a majority of tokens on a network than rent out a majority of computing power) or delegated Proof of Stake. Yet, none of these solutions seem to be quite foolproof enough to combat the enormity of the threat at hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the risks posed by quantum computing, many have recommended the addition of quantum cryptography to the basis of blockchain. Del Rajan and Matt Visser of the Victoria University of Wellington in New Zealand have suggested using quantum particles entangled in time to construct the blockchain architecture itself, so that each particle can record all preceding history in a way that prevents hacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, the latter solution is quite futuristic in nature and we can hardly guarantee that there will never be another technology to disarm a quantum blockchain too. As of now, it would be advisable to remain mindful of the risks that underlie the benefits of blockchain technology and try to build robust structures that hackers find harder to catch up to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=a527d10f4977" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/is-blockchain-really-immutable-a527d10f4977"&gt;Is Blockchain Really Immutable?&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 20:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Markets Report Slight Gains While Gold Rises -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-markets-report-slight-gains-while-gold-rises</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81NmI1ZjI4MmU5N2Q4OGVlYzcxOGU3M2E0OTQyZDViZi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most top coins are seeing minor gains on the day, with Bitcoin hovering around the $4,000 price point&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: SBI Holdings Latest Crypto Venture Will See It Make Mining Chips -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/sbi-holdings-latest-crypto-venture-will-see-it-make-mining-chips</link><description>Japan's SBI Holdings has teamed with an unnamed “large” semiconductor firm in the U.S. to make crypto mining chips and systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: FIS-Worldpay's impact, OCC's Wells Fargo rebuke, lifetime banker bans: Top stories of the week -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/list/fis-worldpays-impact-occs-wells-fargo-rebuke-lifetime-banker-bans-top-stories-of-the-week</link><description>What the FIS-Worldpay deal means for banks; behind the OCC's public rebuke of Wells Fargo; ripple effect feared as Fed mulls lifetime bans for two bankers; and more from this week's most-read stories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 18:56:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: CFTC: We’re ‘Diligently’ Working on All Crypto-Related Applications, Including Bakkt’s -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cftc-were-diligently-working-on-all-crypto-related-applications-including-bakkts</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lYjhlNjQ2ODRhZGMyMGRkYTUyMjJiZjljM2VhOGFhMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The delayed launch of Bakkt belies the ongoing liaisons with U.S. regulators, commissioner suggests&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Crypto Lender BlockFi Cuts Interest Rates Paid to Largest Account Holders -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/crypto-lender-blockfi-cuts-interest-rates-paid-to-largest-account-holders</link><description>Just weeks after launching the product, BlockFi has cut the interest rate paid to large customers on its crypto deposit account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BankNews.com: NBA Bankers Association Establishes Disaster Relief Fund -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.banknews.com/blog/nba-bankers-association-establishes-disaster-relief-fund/</link><description>As devastation from the recent flooding continues to ripple through communities across the state, the Nebraska Bankers Association has begun working closely with local banks and Nebraska United Way to establish the Bank on Nebraska Strong fund to assist in recovery efforts. This fund has been selected with a $50,000 initial contribution from the NBA. [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 13:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitwise Tells US SEC That 95% of Volume on Unregulated Crypto Exchanges is Suspect -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitwise-tells-us-sec-that-95-of-volume-on-unregulated-crypto-exchanges-is-suspect</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hNDljNTRhYTE5MmE0YzRhOWJmMzFhMDkyZjRjNDI3Ni5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;95 percent of volume on unregulated exchanges appears to be fake or non-economic in nature, an analysis from Bitwise Asset Management argues&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Major Crypto Exchanges Huobi Global and OKEx Launch Support for Tron-Based USDT -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/major-crypto-exchanges-huobi-global-and-okex-launch-support-for-tron-based-usdt</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yMmY0YjJiZDlhMTNlZDcwMjVkYjFkZWMzNDhiN2ViZi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two major crypto exchanges — Huobi Global and OKEx — have announced their support of the Tron-based version of stablecoin USDT&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bain-Backed Crypto Exchange Seed CX Is Expanding to Asia -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bain-backed-crypto-exchange-seed-cx-is-expanding-to-asia</link><description>Chicago-based cryptocurrency exchange Seed CX, which Bain Capital backed last year, is expanding to Asia via a local partnership.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 14:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Bitcoin (And Other Crypto) Use Cases Fizzle, Bit By Bit? -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/sizzlefizzle/2019/bitcoin-crypto-use-cases-fizzle/</link><description>Much hype and hope surrounds the adoption of cryptocurrencies — bitcoin among them as the marquee name in the space, of course — beyond the Wild West of speculative trading that exists now. Favor has met with disfavor, and bitcoin now trades at $3,990 — a bit above nadirs around $3,400 and well off highs […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 16:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, Litecoin, EOS, Bitcoin Cash, Binance Coin, Stellar, Tron, Cardano: Price Analysis, March 22 -  Puntaje: 3200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-ripple-litecoin-eos-bitcoin-cash-binance-coin-stellar-tron-cardano-price-analysis-march-22</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85YmRiY2QyYzc2NWQ5M2JmOWY3YWI4NTQ1MGJjOTgyMS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;New reports claim that most reported volumes on crypto exchanges are faked. How have major coins reacted? Let’s look at the charts&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cooperativa economía: Investigan traspaso de fondos de Cuprum a cuentas de Provida -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.cooperativa.cl/noticias/economia/sistema-previsional/afp/investigan-traspaso-de-fondos-de-cuprum-a-cuentas-de-provida/2019-03-22/143158.html</link><description>El hecho afectó a cuatro clientes de la primera AFP, que se querelló por este hecho. La compañía descartó un ciberataque.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker News: Get 4 Essential CyberSecurity Software For Less Than $10 Per Month -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~3/HYgnOCcEIgI/best-cybersecurity-software.html</link><description>Major data breaches and cyber attacks are occurring at an alarming rate, and if you are still not using a VPN and password manager app, you are seriously out of excuses.

Not just VPN software and a password manager, cybersecurity experts also recommend using antivirus and backup solutions to protect your computers and precious data stored on them. Unfortunately, to cover these bases, one&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~4/HYgnOCcEIgI" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 04:57:30 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Business: This email subject line could well be a business scam -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/small-business/this-email-subject-line-could-well-be-a-business-scam-20190321-p5165p.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_business</link><description>As phishing scam losses stack up, warnings issued about the everyday brands getting impersonated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 12:43:15 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker News: Microsoft Announces Windows Defender ATP Antivirus for Mac -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~3/L26_1K2xrFU/microsoft-defender-antivirus-macos.html</link><description>Brace yourself guys.

Microsoft is going to release its Windows Defender ATP antivirus software for Mac computers.

Sounds crazy, right? But it's true.

Microsoft Thursday announced that the company is bringing its anti-malware software to Apple’s macOS operating system as well—and to more platforms soon, like Linux.

As a result, the technology giant renamed its Windows Defender Advanced&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~4/L26_1K2xrFU" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:55:57 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: FIN7 is back with a previously unseen SQLRat malware -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82733/cyber-crime/fin7-sqlrat-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The financially-motivated hacking group FIN7 is back and used a new piece of malware in a recent hacking campaign. Security experts at Flashpoint revealed that the financially-motivated cybercrime group FIN7 (aka Anunak and Carbanak) used new malware in a recent hacking campaign. The group that has been active since late 2015 targeted businesses worldwide to [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82733/cyber-crime/fin7-sqlrat-malware.html"&gt;FIN7 is back with a previously unseen SQLRat malware&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 08:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Facebook: Up to 600 million users’ passwords were visible to employees -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/facebook-user-passwords-plain-text-visible/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1107237284-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1107237284-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1107237284-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Facebook must be held together by bits of tape, at this point. Earlier this week, we were wondering if Mark Zuckerberg could help his company navigate these dire straits it has found itself in. Amid bailing employees, the Cambridge Analytica scandal, and last year's hack, it's a wonder the company's reputation hasn't collapsed on itself just yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it can't get any worse, now, can it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh yes, it can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANOTHER user privacy debacle?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, Facebook... why do you keep putting yourself in these situations?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to a report by IT security blog Krebs on Security, hundreds of millions of Facebook users had their account passwords stored in plain text and searchable by thousands of Facebook employees — in some cases going back to 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between 200 and 600 million users' passwords were stored in this way, and supposedly accessible by 20,000 Facebook employees, the site said, citing an anonymous source within Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon after this report came, Facebook responded in a blog post: "As part of a routine security review in January, we found that some user passwords were being stored in a readable format within our internal data storage systems. This caught our attention because our login systems are designed to mask passwords using techniques that make them unreadable. We have fixed these issues and as a precaution we will be notifying everyone whose passwords we have found were stored in this way."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"To be clear, these passwords were never visible to anyone outside of Facebook and we have found no evidence to date that anyone internally abused or improperly accessed them," the blog post continued. "We estimate that we will notify hundreds of millions of Facebook Lite users, tens of millions of other Facebook users, and tens of thousands of Instagram users."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So it seems that Facebook had knowledge of this since January, but did not share it with the public until Krebs on Security exposed the issue. It's not clear if this was intended as a cover-up left to deal with an internal misfire, but it would seem so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Despite the recent public struggles Facebook has had with respect to privacy and security, this incident is a little different," John Shier, senior security advisor at cybersecurity firm Sophos commented on the issue. "Authentication data is something that Facebook treats very seriously and has put in place many mechanisms, both externally and internally, to ensure that user credentials are safeguarded."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"While the details of the incident are still emerging, this is likely an accidental programming error that led to the logging of plain text credentials," he continued. "That said, this should never have happened and Facebook needs to ensure that no user credentials or data were compromised as a result of this error. This is also another reminder for people who are still reusing passwords or using weak passwords to change their Facebook password to something strong and unique and to turn on 2-factor authentication.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what should you do with your Facebook account? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity company Sophos wrote to AMEinfo offering advice on what people can do in the current situation. Below is a brief Q &amp;amp; A for users worried about their data, with advice from Paul Ducklin, senior technologist at Sophos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should I change my Facebook password?&lt;br /&gt;
Sophos: Why not? It's perfectly possible that no passwords at all fell into the hands of any crooks as a result of this. But if any passwords did get into the wrong hands (and you can bet your boots that the crooks are trawling through any old data they might have right now, to see if there is anything they missed before), then you can expect them to be abused. Hashed passwords still need to be cracked before they can be used; plaintext passwords are the real deal without any further hacking or cracking needed.&lt;br /&gt;
So our advice is: change your password now.&lt;br /&gt;
Should I turn on two-factor authentication?&lt;br /&gt;
Sophos: Yes, turn on two-factor authentication (2FA) now. We've been urging you to do use two-factor authentication everywhere you can anyway - it means that a password alone isn't enough for crooks to raid your account.&lt;br /&gt;
If you are reluctant to give Facebook your phone number, use app-based authentication, where your mobile phone generates a one-time code each time you log in.&lt;br /&gt;
Should I close my Facebook account?&lt;br /&gt;
Sophos: We can't answer that for you. Given that the wrongly-stored passwords weren't easily accessible in one database, or deliberately stored for routine use during logins, we don't think this breach alone is enough reason to terminate your account. On the other hand, it's a pretty poor look for Facebook, and it might be enough, amongst all the other privacy concerns that have dogged Facebook in recent years, to convince you to take that final step. In short, you have to decide for yourself. (If it helps you decide, we're not closing our accounts.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/facebook-user-passwords-plain-text-visible/"&gt;Facebook: Up to 600 million users&amp;#8217; passwords were visible to employees&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 15:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Finovate Alumni News -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-963/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Finovate.com Streamdata.io Acquired by Axway. Around the web Avaloq signs clients for PSD2 service. Kontomatik enters Southeast Asian market. Feedzai named best in class in fraud and AML vendor market by Aite Group. Yahoo! Finance features SocietyOne and the growth of P2P lending in Australia. American Banker: Jumio teams up with ComplyAdvantage to help banks &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-963/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/finovate-alumni-news-963/"&gt;Finovate Alumni News&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 15:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: 84% of MENA’s youth: Growth of private sector is the way forward -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/economy/mena-youth-private-sector-growth/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_724096318-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_724096318-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_724096318-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;A survey conducted by Oliver Wyman in collaboration with INJAZ Al-Arab in the MENA region, has revealed 84% of the region’s youth respondents believe the private sector will continue to grow in the region. More than half (56%) hold a positive opinion on the sector overall - a high ‘approval’ rate for the private sector given the dominant role of the public sector in many countries. The survey evaluated demands of the future labor market and perspectives of the young generation shaping the private sector’s potential contribution to overall economic growth.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While 40% of the youth population believe future growth in the private sector will be driven by multinationals, 25% are inclined to believe that this will be driven by SMEs rather than large national enterprises and startups. 35% of the youth believe that privatizing education will be beneficial to the economy, followed by professional services (30%), human health (29%) and agribusiness (28%).  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Infographic by Oliver Wyman) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One implication found in the survey was that despite the manufacturing sector being relatively small, it is where private firms are most beneficial due to the potential creation of high-skilled jobs and low dependency on imports. When asked about the digital economy, 88% of the respondents said would be a major driving force of the private sector; however, 45% also felt that digital skills are insufficiently reflected in the current curriculum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“While the private sector has grown significantly over the last years, historically the public sector has remained dominant across the MENA region. Diversification is the key economic growth driver and the private sector has a key role to play in supporting governments efforts towards this. Perhaps more important than its fiscal effects is that privatization has the potential to offer a number of economic and social benefits,” said Greg Rung, Partner and Head of Social Impact at Oliver Wyman (MEA).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With industries across all sectors of the economy evolving through institutional reforms and an increased focus on digital economies by regional governments, the survey shows that the youth are increasingly aware of the value of the private sector. They have clearly outlined the areas that need to be focused on as they enter the workforce in the current economic climate,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The survey was taken by 949 respondents between the ages of 16 and 35 and covered four specific areas including the demographics of the respondents, private sector growth drivers and industries, challenges and successes of entrepreneurs and employees and implications of the digital economy on the education system. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The youth is currently facing challenges such as an overall shortage of job opportunities, uncompetitive salaries, and opportunities for career development. The collaboration with Oliver Wyman has produced strategic results for the consideration of all stakeholders involved in youth empowerment and allows in turn, for solution-based growth on major issues as the sector advances,” said Akef Aqrabawi, President &amp;amp; CEO of INJAZ Al-Arab/JA MENA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study revealed three broad strategic initiatives required by governments to sustain economic growth, create jobs in the private sector, and to reap the benefits of the future digital economy. These include improving institutional capabilities and regulations, adapting the educational system to have a stronger focus on skills, and attracting domestic and foreign investments in key sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/economy/mena-youth-private-sector-growth/"&gt;84% of MENA’s youth: Growth of private sector is the way forward&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 09:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: IBM World wire – the inevitable rise of Centralized Blockchains -  Puntaje: 3200</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/03/22/ibm-world-wire-the-inevitable-rise-of-centralized-blockchains/</link><description>72 countries, 47 currencies, 44 banking endpoints and more than 1081 unique currency trading pairs. IBM Blockchain World Wire is here. IBM Press release on World Wire In the last four weeks, we have had JPM Coin announcement by JP Morgan, followed by Facebook&amp;#8217;s ambitions to plug crypto payments into Whatsapp, and now IBM have [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Middle East bank chief calls for more regtech spending -  Puntaje: 1100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33573/middle-east-bank-chief-calls-for-more-regtech-spending?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The secretary general of the Union of Arab Banks has called on financial institutions in the region...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Instarem Raises Capital; TurnKey Lender Goes Live in Malaysia -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://finovate.com/instarem-raises-capital-turnkey-lender-goes-live-in-malaysia/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Finovate Global is our weekly look at fintech innovation in developing economies in Asia, Africa, the Middle East, Latin America, and Central and Eastern Europe. Asia-Pacific TurnKey Lender opens new office in Malaysian capital, Kuala Lumpur. Instarem raises $41 million to fund global expansion. Singapore FinTech Association and FinTech Australia ink Memorandum of Understanding. Sub-Saharan Africa &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/instarem-raises-capital-turnkey-lender-goes-live-in-malaysia/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/instarem-raises-capital-turnkey-lender-goes-live-in-malaysia/"&gt;Instarem Raises Capital; TurnKey Lender Goes Live in Malaysia&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Technology: Facebook to re-examine how live videos are flagged after Christchurch shooting -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/technology/facebook-to-re-examine-how-live-videos-are-flagged-after-christchurch-shooting-20190322-p516f1.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_technology</link><description>Facebook said it would re-examine its "reporting logic" after its artificial intelligence systems failed to automatically detect the New Zealand mosque shooting video.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 02:51:53 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: 'If the product is good, it should sell itself': A Q&amp;A with Earnest's CEO -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/if-the-product-is-good-it-should-sell-itself-a-q-a-with-earnests-ceo</link><description>Susan Ehrlich, the fintech lender's new chief, discusses what she learned working at Amazon and Simple and how her firm is approaching consumer loans differently.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:45:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of England Publications: Embracing the promise of fintech -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://www.bankofengland.co.uk/quarterly-bulletin/2019/2019-q1/embracing-the-promise-of-fintech</link><description>Quarterly Bulletin 2019 Q1</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 12:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Project BankNorth Partners with nCino Ahead of 2020 Launch -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://finovate.com/project-banknorth-partners-with-ncino-ahead-of-2020-launch/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Project BankNorth, a U.K.-based SME lender, has teamed up with nCino, and will leverage the fintech&amp;#8217;s Bank Operating System to better serve the financing needs of small businesses when it goes live in 2020. nCino International Managing Director Pullen Daniel praised BankNorth as an &amp;#8220;up-and-coming challenger.&amp;#8221; He said, &amp;#8220;The BankNorth team is extremely experienced and &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/project-banknorth-partners-with-ncino-ahead-of-2020-launch/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/project-banknorth-partners-with-ncino-ahead-of-2020-launch/"&gt;Project BankNorth Partners with nCino Ahead of 2020 Launch&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 16:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: An Indonesian Plot Twist: Fintech Akulaku Buys Stake into a Bank -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29656/indonesia/akulaku-bank-yudha-bhakti-invest-buy-technology-fintech/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Alibaba-backed Akulaku is the top funded fintech startups in Indonesia, and now a shareholder of a local bank as reported by Katadata. Akulaku reportedly made an Rp 500 billion (approximately&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29656/indonesia/akulaku-bank-yudha-bhakti-invest-buy-technology-fintech/"&gt;An Indonesian Plot Twist: Fintech Akulaku Buys Stake into a Bank&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 04:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC technology: AI turns scribbles into masterpieces and other news -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-47555566</link><description>BBC Click's Omar Mehtab looks at some of the best tech news stories of the week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 08:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Top fintech stories this week – 22 March 2019 -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/top-fintech-stories-this-week-22-march-2019/</link><description>Catch up on FinTech Futures' top five fintech stories of the week – all in one place!</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 09:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Google requests meeting with top US general amid China AI debate -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/international/google-requests-meeting-with-us-general-amid-row-over-it-ai-work-in-china-119032201254_1.html</link><description>Google's relationship with the Pentagon has been strained since it retreated from an AI defense contract last year following employee protests</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 23:56:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Swiss Federal Council Initiates Blockchain Law Consultation Period -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/swiss-federal-council-initiates-blockchain-law-consultation-period</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82MmUxMDRmY2ViMTAxZWRmNTU1YjFlNzdjNmJjZDc1NC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Swiss Federal Council has started its consultation on the adaptation of federal law for blockchain development&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Road to Consensus with Kadena’s Will Martino: Who Needs Private Blockchain? -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/road-to-consensus-with-kadenas-will-martino-who-needs-private-blockchain</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 15:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Daily Crunch: Facebook admits password security lapse -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/bXL8TkDlXcM/</link><description>The Daily Crunch is TechCrunch&amp;#8217;s roundup of our biggest and most important stories. If you&amp;#8217;d like to get this delivered to your inbox every day at around 9am Pacific, you can subscribe here. 1. Facebook admits it stored ‘hundreds of millions’ of account passwords in plaintext Prompted by a report by cybersecurity reporter Brian Krebs, [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 16:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: NSE subsidiary buys cybersecurity company Aujas for undisclosed sum -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/nse-subsidiary-buys-cybersecurity-company-aujas-for-undisclosed-sum-119032200953_1.html</link><description>Aujus has a 'security operations centre' to help enterprises foil cyberattacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 19:30:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: How 6 million Bank of America customers are using Erica -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/how-6-million-bank-of-america-customers-are-using-erica</link><description>The most popular features of the AI-driven virtual assistant include transaction search and spending alerts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 13:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japan: SBI Group Sets Up Spin-Off to Manufacture Crypto Mining Chips -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japan-sbi-group-sets-up-spin-off-to-manufacture-crypto-mining-chips</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy84YTJjOGQ3NzY4N2I3MTJkYjdjZjhiNDk4NjIxMjBmMi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Financial giant SBI prepares for major mining market entry after mixed experiences mining Bitcoin Cash&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: 10 UAE-Based FinTech Startups You Don't Want to Miss -  Puntaje: 7200</title><link>https://gomedici.com/10-uae-based-fintech-startups-you-don't-want-to-miss/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/11-uae-based-fintech-startups-you-don't-want-to-miss.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;The UAE is leading the Middle East in terms of FinTech startup concentration. The country is continuously focusing on strengthening its position as a FinTech destination through initiatives such as crypto forums, sandbox, blockchain, strategy, and others. The market is optimistic about the UAE’s emergence as FinTech hub for the larger geography. Here is a list of 10 UAE-based FinTech startups you don’t want to miss: Channel VAS was founded in 2012 and has raised $49.8 million in total funding. The company leverages big data and analytics to provide mobile financial and air-time credit services, enabling users to avail credit facilities through their network operators. Cash Credit was founded in 2011 and has raised $25 million in total funding. The company is NBFC which offers instant microcredit up to BGN 2,000 through mobile subscribers against an identity card. Aqeed was founded in 2016 and has raised $18 million in total...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 12:30:00 +0530</pubDate></item></channel></rss>