<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 21:14:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>finextra: TradeIX to hire 70 more staff for Dublin HQ -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33540/tradeix-to-hire-70-more-staff-for-dublin-hq?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Trade finance blockchain network TradeIX is to hire 70 more staff at its Dublin HQ, in a variety of...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: SEC to hold DLT and digital asset-focused public forum -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77681/sec-to-hold-dlt-and-digital-asset-focused-public-forum?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Securities and Exchange Commission today announced that its staff will host a public forum focus...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: FCA pioneers digitising regulatory reporting using DLT and NLP -  Puntaje: 2500</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/03/15/fca-pioneers-digitising-regulatory-reporting-using-dlt-and-nlp/</link><description>Too many TLAs (Three Letter Acronyms), I agree. Earlier this week the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) published the results of a pilot programme called Digital Regulatory Reporting. It was an exploratory effort to understand the feasibility of using Distributed Ledger Technology (DLT) and Natural Language Processing (NLP) to automate regulatory reporting at scale. Let me [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Canadian regulators consult on framework for crypto-asset trading platforms -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77674/canadian-regulators-consult-on-framework-for-crypto-asset-trading-platforms?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) and Investment Industry Regulatory Organization of Cana...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Exiger names Alex Ceponkus global head, software engineering -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77680/exiger-names-alex-ceponkus-global-head-software-engineering?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Exiger, the leader in the provision of technology-enabled regulatory, financial crime, risk, and com...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: The platform ecology model: A deep dive -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33539/the-platform-ecology-model-a-deep-dive?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Eating the dust of Barclaycard’s partnership with Alipay, Finextra reports on the dominance of Ant F...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Esma issues favourable report on RegTech developments -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77679/esma-issues-favourable-report-on-regtech-developments?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA) has carried out an analysis of the regulatory a...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: AR and VR in Fintech: Benefits and Pitfalls -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16814/ar-and-vr-in-fintech-benefits-and-pitfalls?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Are you using VR or AR in banking? Not yet? Looks like you are not trendy! Virtual reality is commo....</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: 9 Startups Inducted Into Inaugural Apollo Munich InspireNext Program -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://gomedici.com/9-startups-inducted-into-inaugural-apollo-munich-inspirenext-program/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/9-startups-inducted-into-inaugural-apollo-munich-inspirenext-program.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;Apollo Munich Health Insurance, a leading health insurance company, has always endeavored to be at the forefront of technology innovation. In alignment with its focus on leveraging cutting-edge technology to deliver world-class banking services to its clients, the company launched its first accelerator program called ‘InspireNext’ on March 12, 2019, at its corporate headquarters in Gurugram, NCR. InspireNext was created by Apollo Munich with a view to support and collaborate with entrepreneurs who are driving innovation in the FinTech/InsurTech ecosystem and to leverage their expertise for co-creating solutions that can benefit the company’s consumer base. The InspireNext program, in its inaugural year, intends to work on areas such as Customer Onboarding, Augmenting Customer Engagement, Claims Management, New-Age Risk Management Solutions, Operational Efficiencies, and HR Tech. This 15-week program will comprise of 5 weeks of on-site interactions and 10 weeks of off-site collaboration, where startups can work from their base locations,...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 18:12:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Danske Bank joins Lighthouse fintech engagement programme -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33541/danske-bank-joins-lighthouse-fintech-engagement-programme?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Denmark's Danske Bank is partnering with Mastercard and NFT Ventures on Nordic fintech engagement pr...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: When a Dragon Births Unicorns – 5 In 2018 -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://gomedici.com/when-dragon-births-unicorns-5-in-2018/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/when-dragon-births-unicorns-5-in-2018.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;China has always had a solid reputation for high-speed manufacturing, but when it comes to highly-valued ventures, the country may just have outdone itself last year. Consider this: in 2018, in spite of an extended trade war with the US and in the face of an economic slowdown, 25 private Chinese companies were valued at a total of $58.05 billion. In 2018’s H1, China’s FinTech companies raised ~$35 billion (over 80% of the global total) and three giants took more than half of the amount fundraised in China. Which giants? Ant Financial, Du Xiaoman Financial, and the new one on the block, JD Finance, raised ~$17.8 billion, accounting for more than half the total amount of funding in China for the year. A lot has been said about China’s growing tech unicorn culture. Some contend that such growth is inevitable, considering the overwhelmingly massive number of mobile and internet users...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:01:00 +0530</pubDate></item></channel></rss>