<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 21:51:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cointelegraph: Facebook Announces New Blockchain Jobs at Its California HQ -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/facebook-announces-new-blockchain-jobs-at-its-california-hq</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jMWIzZDcwZjVmYWE5ZDI5YjAyZDY0OGU1NWNjNTRhZS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook HQ in Menlo Park announces five new positions in its blockchain team, including for a data scientist and software engineer&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bittrex-Backed Euro Stablecoin Can Be Staked for 8% Interest -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bittrex-backed-euro-stablecoin-can-be-staked-for-8-interest</link><description>A group of blockchain firms called Universal Protocol Alliance is launching a euro-pegged stablecoin that can be staked to earn annual returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bitmain’s Jihan Wu: ASICs Are Making Ethereum More Decentralized -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bitmains-jihan-wu-asics-are-making-ethereum-mining-more-decentralized</link><description>The Bitmain co-founder says ASIC miners are making blockchains more decentralized and ethereum's ProgPow proposal could still be "ASICable."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 09:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Universal Protocol Alliance to Launch Euro-Pegged Stablecoin in April -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/universal-protocol-alliance-to-launch-euro-pegged-stablecoin-in-april</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xYjViNDc5ZDY3MDNiZWE0MzQ1MWMxOTcxNzgzN2ExOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Universal Protocol Alliance, a coalition of blockchain firms including Bittrex and Brave, will launch its own euro-pegged stablecoin UPEUR in April&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: USB's mobile app, BofA and Wells cool on blockchain, GSEs too big: Top stories of the week -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/list/usbs-mobile-app-bofa-and-wells-cool-on-blockchain-gses-too-big-top-stories-of-the-week</link><description>Under the hood of U.S. Bank's new mobile app; BofA, Wells Fargo sour on blockchain; are Fannie and Freddie too big?; and more from this week's most-read stories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: ‘Big Four’ Consulting Firms Dominate Blockchain Jobs Market, Says Indeed -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/big-four-consulting-firms-dominate-blockchain-jobs-market-says-indeed</link><description>Deloitte, KPMG and EY are all in the top five when it comes to posting blockchain and crypto job ads in the U.S., according to Indeed.com data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Craig Wright’s nChain Is Hiring a Lawyer to Protect Its Crypto Patents -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/craig-wrights-nchain-is-hiring-a-lawyer-to-prosecute-its-crypto-patents</link><description>nChain, founded by self-styled bitcoin inventor Craig S. Wright, is looking for a patent counsel to manage its portfolio of blockchain-related IP.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 03:06:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Cybersecurity Firm WISeKey Launches Blockchain-Powered ID Solution for IoT Devices -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cybersecurity-firm-wisekey-launches-blockchain-powered-id-solution-for-iot-devices</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xNDBiMjBkNzQyMjA1NThhMjFlMTZjNGUwYjY0ODI1Mi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Switzerland-based firm WISeKey has launched a blockchain-powered digital identity solution to protect Internet of Things devices and their data&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Fidelity Poaches Coinbase Institutional Sales Head Christine Sandler -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/fidelity-poaches-coinbase-institutional-sales-head-christine-sandler</link><description>Coinbase's director of institutional sales, Christine Sandler, has left the crypto exchange for Fidelity Investments, sources said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 18:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Exchange HitBTC Appeals to Cryptography in Dispute With Altcoin BTCP -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exchange-hitbtc-appeals-to-cryptography-in-dispute-with-altcoin-btcp</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80MmQxMzExZjllZDFhN2EwZTIwNjM5MTkwMTJkYWU5Zi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;HitBTC accuses the Bitcoin Private team of creating custodial risk and ecosystem instability in ongoing controversy &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Coinbase Leads Wall Street to Brave New World of Crypto Staking -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/coinbase-leads-wall-street-to-brave-new-world-of-crypto-staking</link><description>Coinbase Custody has launched staking services for institutional clients, starting with Tezos and touting 6.6 percent yields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 08:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitmain Announces Launch Date for Antminer S17 Series -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitmain-announces-launch-date-for-antminer-s17-series</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hMTIzNzQwZDkyMjNiZDc1OGI0N2FiYTBmMGUwMDRiOC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese crypto mining giant  Bitmain has announced a launch date for its new energy-efficient Antminer S17 series miners&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japanese E-commerce Giant Rakuten to Launch Its Crypto Exchange in June -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japanese-e-commerce-giant-rakuten-to-launch-its-crypto-exchange-in-june</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xZDQ4OTRiNDY5ZWQ1NTliMmMwMjE2NzViYWVjMWIzMy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese e-commerce giant Rakuten announced the launch date for its crypto exchange, dubbed Rakuten Wallet, following its approval by the FSA&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Major Private Indian Bank Partners With Ripple for Cross-Border Remittances -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/major-private-indian-bank-partners-with-ripple-for-cross-border-remittances</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82MmJkYTU1NDlhMTc4NmZiYjhhY2IwYWZiOWQ0ZTQ4ZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal Bank, a major private Indian commercial bank,  has partnered with Ripple for its cross-border remittances network&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Indian Street Protests for Cryptocurrency -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/indian-street-protests-for-cryptocurrency</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hZDZlNTI0OTcwYmE1YTU0YzYxMWQyOWUwNDA4YzgxYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian developers are set to protest the ban on crypto.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Argentina’s Dep. Finance Minister: Crypto Adoption Could Reduce Demand for US Dollar -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/argentinas-dep-finance-minister-crypto-adoption-could-reduce-demand-for-us-dollar</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9kZTNiNmRkYjA4NzY2NmE4MzU4YWIyZmVhZWM2NzRlNy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Argentina wants to reduce demand for U.S. dollars by adopting crypto and blockchain with the help of Huobi exchange&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japan: 13 Banks Invest in SBI’s Ripple-Powered Blockchain Payment App -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japan-13-banks-invest-in-sbis-ripple-powered-blockchain-payment-app</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8zOWU0ZjY0NjAzNDU2N2VmZGQwZTc5NzhjYmZkZTYyMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ripple-powered app MoneyTap from SBI Holdings receives investments from 13 Japanese banks&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, EOS, Litecoin, Bitcoin Cash, Binance Coin, Stellar, Cardano, Tron: Price Analysis, March 29 -  Puntaje: 2600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-ripple-eos-litecoin-bitcoin-cash-binance-coin-stellar-cardano-tron-price-analysis-march-29</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85ZmI2NTFkNTFjOTc0OGNhMDA3YmYzZjQzNGFlNzU2My5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the gradual recovery in crypto markets continues, let’s see which major coins looks strong&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: About Removing Medium from Hackernoon.com -  Puntaje: 14400</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/about-removing-medium-from-hackernoon-com-7c72353ba6e?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hy4Lduu9CKg&amp;amp;t=1915s"&gt;Watch Video&lt;/a&gt; (you can also listen to this story on &lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/why-is-hackernoon-com-leaving-medium/id1436233955?i=1000431854486&amp;amp;mt=2"&gt;iTunes&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/music/m/Dtae7ck4fdsfwrpy5hjy64l6rsq?t=Why_is_Hackernooncom_leavingMedium-Hacker_Noon_Podcast"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4&gt;TL;DR: The business interests of these two entities have changed. Hacker Noon has to rip and replace its software infrastructure to make its land a viable business again. This is an important discussion to the state of digital publishing, the value of URLs, the dependencies of startup , and the effects of platform growth strategies. Jump ahead by clicking on the subject matter below:&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#ffb2"&gt;About David’s Past on Wordpress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#9265"&gt;The Rise of Hackernoon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#b863"&gt;Community Content Ownership&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#9e76"&gt;Medium.com Priority Shift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#de16"&gt;Where Hackernoon’s At&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#22ab"&gt;Who Owns Hackernoon?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#c6f4"&gt;Medium Emails All Hackernoon Contributors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#3547"&gt;Burnt Publishers &amp;amp; Low Buyout Offers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#6cbb"&gt;Medium’s Ban of 3rd Party Ads on Other People’s Domains&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#be55"&gt;Small Business Dependencies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#69b7"&gt;Transition Proposal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#5205"&gt;Depreciation of Medium Publications Functionality&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#7343"&gt;Link Shenanigans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#4ab3"&gt;Community Funds Hackernoon 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#31aa"&gt;Building Hacker Noon 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#674f"&gt;Two Viral Tweets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#333f"&gt;The Nonexclusive License on Hackernoon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#ad6c"&gt;Medium’s Transition Plan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#9ca4"&gt;Progress on Hackernoon’s Upcoming Product&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#6c0e"&gt;Hackernoon Revenue and Future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#a10b"&gt;Creating a Bed by Destroying a Frame&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="#c8a2"&gt;Conclusion: State of Hackernoon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*ZTh6irqvujxVCiAIgAUGYA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*wr25aB3U9Vm-9IeRl1b8yg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*7RX93H-7HzwPyq_mkzNDaA.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*_Omq217iS8j8UvMutMyQ0Q.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*O3yt_lvXAZlJGNvTqicTjg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*JjTug7Ogg1xGcwF2GAiZXg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*sA9H5rZYP94YHJEgMMpJYQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*zFQofDY_l55TFsZMlTucCg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*FG1bHOLU9cV52_xnFoEYTg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*29WRWGYWVVs55IO9OUI10A.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*UThiixqpcGLGYhaBeWgDPg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hy4Lduu9CKg"&gt;Here is the video&lt;/a&gt; (you can also listen to this story on &lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/why-is-hackernoon-com-leaving-medium/id1436233955?i=1000431854486&amp;amp;mt=2"&gt;iTunes&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/music/m/Dtae7ck4fdsfwrpy5hjy64l6rsq?t=Why_is_Hackernooncom_leavingMedium-Hacker_Noon_Podcast"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;), and below is the transcript:&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@trentlapinski"&gt;Trent&lt;/a&gt;: All right. Welcome to the Hacker Noon Podcast. This is a very special episode so I’ve got a very special guest with us. He’s actually the CEO and founder of Hacker Noon and in this episode, we’re gonna be talking about something a little different than what we’re used to. So, we’ve got a little bit more of a situation with Hacker Noon and we wanted to talk directly to our audience and let them know what’s going on straight from &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/davidsmooke?lang=en"&gt;David&lt;/a&gt;’s mouth and my mouth a little bit as well, I guess, but mostly David’s about what’s going on with this situation with Medium, and moving off Medium and launching Hacker Noon 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hacker Noon has recently done a &lt;a href="https://www.startengine.com/hackernoon"&gt;successful crowdfund&lt;/a&gt; and there’s been a lot of different things going on. So, I’m gonna kick it off to David. David, can you tell us a little bit about the background of how we got here and why you chose Medium as a content management system?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@davidsmooke"&gt;David&lt;/a&gt;: Hey, Trent. It’s really cool to be on the &lt;a href="https://podcast.hackernoon.com/"&gt;Hacker Noon Podcast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: I didn’t really intend to set out and make this technology blog. I kind of always worked in tech and I really like publishing but early in my career, I was being paid more for writing and marketing as opposed to growing your own site. I wanted to go all in on my own site and I didn’t know what the site would be. I know I like building community and I love reading and hearing directly from people what their stories. And so, we started 16 different publications on Medium. And the thing with Medium, in the early days of their content management system, they really cut out a lot of the bullshit that other CMSs do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that there’s always a left and a right column while reading is insane to me. It is so distracting. It is so hard to focus on the text with these left and right-hand columns, and most WordPress sites have ’em and most sites across the internet do. So, that one thing that they did was really just great. If you’re looking at the screen and you wanna read, you don’t want anything else. You just want the story there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I thought that was really cool and they really just made it easy for people to come in and start their own publication. You could bring in your own friends and then they had a network behind and then they recruited tons of publishers: Pacific Standard, Think Progress, The Ringer…. And it was like “Okay, all these kind of cool publishers are getting on board here. Maybe a young publisher like me should follow the news and learn from this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also, before this, with the &lt;a href="https://www.smartrecruiters.com/blog/"&gt;SmartRecruiters blog&lt;/a&gt;, I did a very similar model where I opened it up completely for any recruiting expert to come in and publish about recruiting and I offered curation, distribution, and editing, and it was a lot of manual work with WordPress. Creating the user account: do you manage their user account or not? That’s the annoying thing about WordPress and Medium was like “No, the user manages their account and they can publish on all these different sites.” They just make an agreement with the site and they publish in that publication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Before this, with the &lt;a href="https://www.smartrecruiters.com/blog/"&gt;SmartRecruiters blog&lt;/a&gt;, I did a very similar model where I opened it up completely for any recruiting expert to come in and publish about recruiting and I offered curation, distribution, and editing, and it was a lot of manual work with WordPress.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it was a more open way to see the web in the early days. If you were a writer, you could publish in many different places by starting one account which is pretty cool. So, that’s what attracted me in the beginning and, plus, Blogger, Twitter, Medium … Just a lot of respect for Ev Williams and the things he built. I don’t think he thinks the same thing about me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Well, okay. So, let’s set some context here. For the average listener, I’m not sure that they even know that Ev Williams is necessarily behind all those three projects. So, he’s a Twitter co-founder, he founded Blogger, and then, now, his latest project is Medium. He’s had a very long interesting career in Silicon Valley that’s kind of lead up to this point and, again, like I said, I’m not sure if everyone listening knows that he … He was one of the original co-founders of Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah, and I’ve watched a lot of … His earlier videos are funny. He’s like “I’m Ev Williams and this is an internet company” and he’s like in Nebraska like selling some internet services and I was like … I remember my first business card at SmartRecruiters. First I was an unpaid intern and then I was the marketing department but my first business card, I just wrote “Internet Enthusiast.” I was a 20 year old in San Francisco, like “Oh, yes, I’m very enthusiastic about the internet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s like “What do you do?” Like “I grow the site.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Well, you then grew Hacker Noon, here. Let’s catch up to the present a little bit here and, I mean, what’s the Alexa ranking now? It’s crazy. And we’re not talking about the robot, we’re talking about a ranking site, here, that ranks all the top sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;A lot of the time it was just me for the company, and then part time people, and then it was me and my wife Linh and now we’re up to four people and a whole part time team of 8 but getting to a &lt;a href="https://www.alexa.com/siteinfo/hackernoon.com"&gt;top 5,000 site in the world&lt;/a&gt;, a lot of it is just showing up to work every single day.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: But Alexa is owned by Amazon. Alexa.com to rank sites but yeah, not the robot but yeah. We’re around top 5,000 in the world. So, I think it’s pretty significant and for most … A lot of the time it was just me for the company, and then part time people, and then it was me and my wife Linh and now we’re up to four people and a whole part time team of 8 but getting to a top 5,000 site in the world, a lot of it is just showing up to work every single day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s like figuring out what works and every morning digging into stories for the first half of the day no matter what and that’s four hours every day. Just getting the story submissions, hit this baseline of quality stories out, and try to raise the quality which is a pretty big challenge but, for the most part, what Hacker Noon is is a place for tech professionals to publish their stories and meet other great people in the community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, the community aspect of this is really what’s grown it because all the content is owned by the community — the individual community members — and we have a non-exclusive license to publish here. So, we’re kind of in that spot where it’s like kind of like a Huffington Post just for technology professionals or a Linkedin publishers just for technology professionals but a little bit more of that rawness and we don’t really want all this formal stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;like, i’m fine if you wanna go all lowercase. like i’m not gonna style guide you. if that’s your tone at the time, be honest and publish in your voice and publish in your tone and i’m not gonna go up there and say “hey, this is the ap style guide. let’s clean this up, dude.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Well, that’s what I personally got attracted to Hacker Noon and started writing for it ’cause it was like “Hey, …” So, for me as a writer, I wanted to reach a bigger audience and Hacker Noon was a great way for me to do that. When I write, I’m writing it so I can reach people. I’m not wiring it because I wanna make money necessarily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it was really powerful to be able to add my publication, the content I was writing, to your publication and, all of a sudden, I’m getting 10, 20,000, 50,000 reads on some of my articles and that was really powerful. Like if I had just published that to my profile, it would have went into a black hole and like 10 people would have read it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it was great to be able to get that exposure and to have access to an audience and I think a lot of the writers who have written for Hacker Noon over the years can probably relate to my experience but, at the same time, it’s kind of a different model than where Medium’s kind of taken things now. Can you talk a little bit about how Medium went from being this really open publishing platform and content management system to what it is now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah. Yeah, I mean I think a lot of it comes down to incentives and when you take on a lot of money and you say you’re gonna change the whole world, you have to take big shots. So, they made a pretty big pivot to say “Contributor, instead of having your story publicly available for free, we would prefer that your story’s behind a paywall and we will pay you for it, and our pay walled readers will read it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, they switched from saying “Let’s empower tons of people to grow their sites and bring in their communities, have the readers and writers create Medium accounts to do so,” and then change to “The only thing we want writers to do is publish on medium.com and we don’t want any other sites to really grow, and if you want to curate content on medium.com, you can do it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;When you take on a lot of money and you say you’re gonna change the whole world, you have to take big shots.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean, I get some of this why it make sense. I mean, first of all, the URL. Like how cool is that? They really do have a super valuable URL that you don’t wanna give up on. So, with this business model they’re taking now, they’re trying to be like the Comcast of text and they’re trying to get ever human in the world to pay them $5 a month to read stories. Except those stories, instead of being created by TNT or ABC like channels, they want it to be created by individuals like you and me and put our stuff behind the pay wall and tell well written stories. They publish thousands of stories a day so the quality varies tremendously within the site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re looking at like 20 stories a day right now and as we move into our own infrastructure and we empower community editors, I think we’ll get to a higher volume of stories per day but yeah. It’s a tough pivot. It changed my entire life. I mean, I bet my business on this content management system and trusted that area of the technology was taken care of and I could focus on growing the site, getting better content, building a better community, looking at having events, having a community forum, and just …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was nice to not have to worry about what the content management system will do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;It’s a tough pivot. It changed my entire life. I mean, I bet my business on this content management system and trusted that area of the technology was taken care of…&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: And then-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: And the infrastructure behind it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely, and I made trade offs. I mean, they paid for &lt;a href="https://www.webhostinghero.com/#hackernoon.com"&gt;our hosting&lt;/a&gt; but they took all of our reader data and now they own our e-mail list. So, these trade offs that I made in the beginning to start growing, at the time, I didn’t think that “Oh my gosh, you would steal this?” It’s not stealing but it’s all the reader data. It’s not mine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Okay. Some context for the people listening right now, who owns hackernoon.com? Let’s get that out of the way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;We own the site and the content is owned by the contributors and we have a non exclusive license to it.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: We do. So, our formal name is ArtMap Inc and that’s what we started as. It’s kind of our … and then our DBA is Hacker Noon and Hacker Noon is what everybody is focused on. So, we own the site and the content is owned by the contributors and we have a non exclusive license to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Okay, and what the heck just happened with Medium recently? Because they sent an e-mail. Can you talk a little bit about that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah. So, Monday at 4, people start forwarding me … All these contributors are forwarding me this e-mail from Medium to them and it’s talking about what Hacker Noon is doing or not doing. And basically, it boils down to our whole site is just a container and all the work of this company is one container and that’s what it is which was extremely confusing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Paul__Walsh/status/1105243072273637377"&gt;The first tweet&lt;/a&gt; that came out was something like, Medium sent me an e-mail to clarify about Hacker Noon and I have no idea what they’re talking about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;...it boils down to our whole site is just a container and all the work of this company is one container…&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And I think a lot of contributors don’t even … Maybe they haven’t even followed that Hacker Noon is working on 2.0 and is potentially leaving Medium. Some people, they haven’t read those articles. They knew about the crowd fund maybe but maybe they didn’t pay attention to all the details….&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: And, I mean, a lot of the people that we attract, a lot of them like “Oh, we’re gonna write a couple blog posts a year. Hacker Noon is a great place to publish it. So, I’ll come there, I’ll read sometimes,” but some of our best contributors, it’s not like they’re publishing every day and it’s not like I want them to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want people to publish on our site that are doing great things in their day to day lives and they come to us when they have a story and they wanna amplify that story. And they can come to many sites with that story because it is a non exclusive license and we believe writers should publish many places. Like it’s better for the writer if they’re all over the place and their story’s many places. It’s just better for getting your story out there and getting people like you or people that should read the story out there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;I want people to publish on our site that are doing great things in their day to day lives and they come to us when they have a story and they wanna amplify that story.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t make sense to keep it hidden in one place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Medium disagrees with you on that one. They think it should be behind a pay wall now. They think you should have to pay to read that content and they also aren’t being too nice to publishers because, apparently, you’re just a container now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah, I mean, a lot of publishers got pretty burnt. I waited it out longer, I guess. Seeing some of these guys like The Awl is now dead. It’s just like they couldn’t handle the transition off and it killed the company and, frankly, it probably should have killed ours. We got low buyout offer from Medium to buy us so they were in this spot where they’re trying to not give us other options and push us into a low offer and the offer was, frankly, less than they’re paying their marketing professionals and their head of advertising for like one year salary and it’s like “Dude.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;We got low buyout offer from Medium to buy us ….and the offer was, frankly, less than they’re paying their marketing professionals for like one year salary.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Isn’t that funny how that works? Also, let’s set some context here again for the listener because we need to establish what happened in … What was it? June of last year? You just randomly heard from Medium that you could no longer run advertising on the site. Can you talk a little bit about that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: So, we found, in terms of being a sustainable business for enough to pay for two people and run the site, we would do a weekly sponsor and we wouldn’t track the reader at all. It would just be co-branding across the top. “Hacker Noon sponsored by PubNub. Check out PubNub.” Something very simple like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it was a pretty good thing where we weren’t taking up any more space from the reader. We kept within our same area that we were just putting our logo so it didn’t really affect our experience much and that was growing to a steady business where we were booked for all of 2018 and then, in the summer, they tell me they want me to stop doing this and it has to happen September 1st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;to me, it was insane because I own hackernoon.com and I’m advertising Medium all over it.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;And now, in this time, okay. As a bootstrap business, we had to find a new revenue stream or have someone buy us and put their own logo at the top because then it would be a first party ad. They were drawing this really strong distinction between first and third party of what is an ad and what is not. And to me, it was insane because I own hackernoon.com and I’m advertising Medium all over it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, they’re a third party to me. So, I said to them “How does that work? How can I be both?” And this is where, when you pivot hard, in the beginning, you’re a content management system helping all these other sites grown and then you’re not, there are residual things that don’t make sense about how you’re doing business in the present because you told people you’d do business this way in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it’s a pretty tough spot to be in and I had just hurt my knee so I was like working my way back to work when I got all this. So, I had surgery and it just took a while to recover so it was like just … It was emotionally difficult. You know, I work with my wife, &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/linhdaosmooke/"&gt;Linh&lt;/a&gt;, so she’s the chief operating officer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, our whole family is dependent on this business. So, it was either-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: You’ve got a child, as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah. Yeah. I have …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Or two, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah (she’s two). So, it’s a lot riding on it but they say … What is it? Innovation is the child of necessity or necessity is the mother of invention? One of those.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Well, it’s a lot of responsibility. You’re running a website that traffics about, what, 8 million people a month?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: 8 million page views. More like one to two million people per month. So, a pretty good … It’s a large community. It’s something that I’m proud that it’s gotten to this point and it’s having problems now that are large community problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;When I was a kid, growing up in the country, I always just wanted to become a container.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Right. But you’ve got the responsibility of running that. You’ve got the responsibility of a family. You’ve got a lot of stuff going on and, basically, the infrastructure that you built all this on is just all of a sudden like “Oh wait, no. We actually own you.” Can you go into that? What is a good analogy here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: When I was a kid, growing up in the country, I always just wanted to become a container.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Don’t we all?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: You know, so … I mean it’s dehumanizing. That’s what they call me. They call me on the thing I’m a container. Whatever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: In an e-mail to every contributing writer. So, this was, what? Several thousand contributing writers who have all written for Hacker Noon? This e-mail was sent to all of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah. So, I mean, it was a really aggressive surprising move. It was a surprising Monday. The really surprising thing was I had been working towards what I thought was the best transition plan; and that is to have a subdomain on Hacker Noon. Something like archive.hackernoon, or even medium.hackernoon.com and keep all the content there and open up the root, hackernoon.com, the root domain for the new environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And this transition made the most sense because, while the vast majority of the links to all these stories go to hackernoon.com/storytitle. So, we’re the gateway to get to these stories. Medium’s internal links go medium.com. So, those links would break and I don’t wanna break any links. So, I’m trying to serve the writer first and keep bringing them traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;If you’re really looking to serve the writer first, you want to keep growing traffic to their past stories. So, it would be a commitment to working together to continue to both of us drive traffic to those stories&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of why we’ve had success is we’ve become authority on subject matter and the community helps grow that authority and then that helps the next community member get more readership. So, because we published on machine learning before, the next story that comes in will have better distribution on machine learning if that’s what they’re writing about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, that’s kind of like the … If you’re really looking to serve the writer first, you want to keep growing traffic to their past stories and that’s what serving it would be. So, it would be a commitment to working together to continue to both of us drive traffic to those stories and, on our end, we would stop publishing on Medium and they would be more branded in the URL ’cause if the first word is medium.hackernoon.com, people see medium first and I’m giving them this branding gift that they do not have right now and I thought they were gonna take this. And their most recent e-mail-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Sounds reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: It’s very reasonable and the most recent e-mail a month ago was “We’re open to taking this.” And then, they cut off communication, I follow up multiple times, and the next communication I hear from them is all these writers forwarding me this e-mail that they e-mailed all the writers. It’s just like … And then after that, on Monday night, they reach out to me and say something about changing our terms which we did just change our terms to make it more clear that the contributor owns their story and they can remove it at any time if they want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don’t want any stories on our site for people that don’t wanna be on our site. Never did, never will, not interesting to me. And then we also made it more clear that, no matter what we do with the content, we’re gonna accredit you appropriately which is something I think we’ve always done. We’ve always tagged people in every newsletter, we’re tagging people as much as we can on Twitter, and on 2.0, we’ll have better automation to distribute the tweet and make sure that we tag the writer every single time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it’s like putting the writer first is what got us here and it’s what helped Medium grow so much, too, that this subdomain compromise, I thought, was great and it gives a clean break and we don’t have all these confused writers complaining but that’s not the … They chose instead to e-mail all the writers and say ‘Don’t do this.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: They made some other decisions as well. It’s not like this e-mail came totally out of the blue. Obviously, it was unexpected but, since I’ve been involved with Hacker Noon in a more official capacity, I’ve been watching as features within Medium are getting depreciated. Ability to access everything from the newsletter to being able to curate stories. Even just loading the necessary windows to be able to curate and do certain things in the settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s almost as if they’ve turned caching off or something. Things are breaking on a regular basis and Hacker Noon’s been losing access to features that have been available for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;I’ve been watching as features within Medium are getting depreciated…..It’s almost as if they’ve turned caching off or something.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah. Yeah. I mean, the one that’s bothering me right now, a lot of the value is … Writing a good headline changes the whole trajectory of a story. It just completely changes it. What is the headline is such an important decision and we’re rewriting most of our headlines and they know this ’cause they wanted our behavior and I’ve told them this and now, if you rewrite the headline, and then you hit the publish button, they keep the SEO settings of the old headline and they keep the URL of the old headline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Whatever the content is, should be what the URL is, and should be what the H1 is to the search engine. It’s like total common sense but (when) you just take that feature away, you now steal more time from the editor.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the content is should be what the URL is and should be what the H1 is to the search engine. It’s like total common sense but you just take that feature away, you now steal more time from the editor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Let’s talk about links for a second. So, when you used to link to Hacker Noon, it showed up in every social network, it showed up all over the internet, on Twitter, on Facebook, or whatever as a link from Hacker Noon. Now when you try to do that, it’s showing up as a Medium link and it redirects you through Medium before you even get to Hacker Noon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can you talk a little bit about that link change and what happened there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: I mean, it’s not happening everywhere. They’ve built the strongest relationship with Twitter in terms of embedding a URL and then having a rich embed and trying to make it go from Twitter to Medium to Hacker Noon even when the user types in hackernoon.com/storytitle and it’s something that you have to be a more powerful person and you have to be interacting with these social networks and you have to change the way embedding works and talk to them and do that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I used to get upset about it. I remember the day they changed the tweet button on my site … So, if it’s like you wanna tweet a Hacker Noon story, you hit the tweet button and now, they auto do text of Medium.com/something. So, you’re literally on hackernoon.com hitting a button and they wanna send it back to Medium and it’s such low hanging fruit to make a better site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s like “Oh, how do you make a better share button?” You don’t send the link to a different site. Like how much else can you make it less misleading? Well yeah, you send it to the site you’re on! It’s like pretty simple. It’s like do you rip a band aid off or do you try and make the person bleed out?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of it is, I think, internally, they didn’t seem very empowered. Like when I’m talking to them, it’s like “Okay, if you’re gonna kill custom domain, just tell me, and I will evolve and move forward appropriately” but its’ like “Oh no, we’re just gonna stop offering it to new users” and then “No, no. It’s gonna be fine” and they’re calling everybody up asking them to move their custom domain to medium.com and they’ll give them some other benefit and that’s the reason they tried to buy us out. So, it’s a tough …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I look back on them, it’s like it would have been so much cooler if they had just kept going down this path of a better Word Press empower millions of sites to be better across the internet and cut out most of this noise and have a simple way to make some money and that’s such a better thing to me. And if you are gonna fully pivot to helping all these people publish on all these different sites to just publish on my site, start a new company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t take all the good will you created in this cool business model but a cool business model can still fail. If it was going to fail, let it fail and then start something new as opposed to trying to switch so that everyone now has a different behavior and all these people that grew businesses with you are now in a tough spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that is something that’s not unique at all for small businesses. Like first when this news happens, I’m upset about it, but then it’s like “Okay, maybe I made the wrong dependency. Maybe I’m part of the problem here and if my business isn’t strong enough to survive this, it’s not a good business and I should be doing a different business and if it’s not a good enough business, I will. I will kill it and go on to something else because it’s something different.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, here-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: But the community rallied. I mean, over a thousand investors have invested in Hacker Noon. No one has done this in publishing that I’m aware of. This is significant and you pulled together a crowd fund like overnight. This was no easy-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: No, it wasn’t overnight. I mean, one of the good things about having a big community is there were a bunch of people interested in buying us. I explained my story. I talked to them. There were people interested in investing in us and it became clear to each person I talked to the solution is to have more resources and move off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Dude. You have 200,000 readers a day that want this thing to continue to exist. You have all these thousands of writers depending on you. Just ask them.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one hears the story that I have talked to and they’re like “Yeah, figure out a way to work with them.” So, it’s kind a challenge of how do you do that? So, we got some solid buyout offers; a couple that were 10x Medium’s offer and, frankly, we considered pretty strongly but the more people we talked to, the more we understood our situation and how to grow from it and Howard Marks is the CEO of Start Engine and he’s been writing on our site for a year and whenever he heard this story, he’s like “Dude. You have 200,000 readers a day that want this thing to continue to exist. You have all these thousands of writers depending on you. Just ask them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And so, we ran an equity crowdfunding campaign with Start Engine and Linh, my wife, did most of the work because it’s a ton of work. It’s so much work behind the scenes that you don’t see. The review with third party accountants, with third party lawyers, with getting all of your information, it’s a mini public offer. So, I don’t have to go through the same level as an IPO. At the time, we were a two person company, so obviously it doesn’t make sense but we released hundreds of pages and worked on telling our story and it forced us, also, to think bigger and plan about how we’re gonna be a better company and model it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it was …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: But you did that while you were still running Hacker Noon which was already a full time job and you’re being undermined left and right by Medium and they kind of cut you off from your revenue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yep. Yep. So, revenue was cut off and then … Yeah. That was pretty tough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: And at the time that we’re-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: You know what was tougher about it? So, they cut it off in September, we’re booked through the end of December. So, I’m over there picking up the phone “Hey. So happy that you trusted to work with us. Love that we signed that contract. Love that you’re a third time renewal customer. Guess what? I can’t serve you. We can’t do a sponsorship. I can only advertise myself and I can only advertise Medium and those are the rules they’ve placed upon me while making me a low ball offer to try and get the asset.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it was a very tough spot. I mean, really, the company would be dead if my wife wasn’t working with me. She led the crowd funding, wrote most of the messaging, did most of the work, and it was pretty simple. This is the story, we’re gonna build a small tech team to build our own infrastructure, and have the building. We own the land, the URL is the location, land is location. We owned the land, we did not own the building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;When people say “Funded by readers…”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had the infrastructure. If they wanna come in and say “You don’t have a bathroom here” and you’re like “Oh, I need to pee.” It’s like “Tough, dude.” So, it was a lot of ups and downs. It really was. Some of the harder things, you know, but like seeing the community believe in us ’cause all we … The marketing of the campaign was so simple; put it atop our site. Put the crowd funding campaign atop our site and that’s where 90% of the traffic … 88, 90%, whatever ended up at, that’s where all the traffic to the page came from.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, when people say “Funded by readers,” people are coming from our site and saying “We want this site to get bigger and better and I like your plan for how you’re gonna do it.” So, it’s a pretty empowering thing and now we have this community of 1200 people ready to go to battle for us and giving us tons of ideas about how to grow it and introductions and …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yeah, crowdfunding is not right for everyone but if you have a large online community and either your business model isn’t figured out or your business model is being threatened by a larger company, it makes perfect sense because now you’re getting people that like your site and believe it will be bigger to own a piece of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, when you’re paying a subscription fee to Netflix, you don’t own some of Netflix. You’re not buying shares. We’re gonna keep all of our content free and we can do that if we have a sponsor on each page and someone sponsors the page and it’s not an intrusive ad. It’s just there and, hopefully, it fits to the content. We’ve rejected a lot of companies that we don’t think fit the content and if you’re not a good tech company or a good blockchain company, or having something about how technology changes the world, you’re not a good sponsor for our site. I’m not interested in selling party supplies or balloons. That’d be a bad site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sponsor should be relevant to the community. When you go to events, if you’re going to a concert, the sponsors there … They fit more to the community and you’re not like “I can’t believe they’re hear asking me for money.” You’re like “No. It’s sweet. I wanted a cheeseburger. This is the place that I would eat a cheeseburger so I will pay them. I’ll go from the concert to the cheeseburger stand and buy the cheeseburger.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I think the model’s gonna work pretty well. I think we can get back to profitability in the fall ’cause it’s a pretty tough move. We were relying on a lot of free technology. We’re gonna continue to have free hosting. Google gave us $100,000 grant in credits. So, that was gonna be our largest non people expense. So, that’s definitely reducing a lot of risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Well, you brought in a new head of product. What title is Dane going by these days? I’m not even sure anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: He started as interim CTO and then he got really into it and really liked working with him. I used to work for him on his old startup and we’ve kinda come full circle. Dane Lyons is the Chief Product Oficer and then Austin Pocus is our Full StackDdeveloper and that’s our four person team. Then, we have part time people around it in editing, design, front end, and podcasting, of course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Myself included in that. So, for the listener, yes, I joined Hacker Noon right as it was a sinking ship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Smart man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Not sure if you’ve heard the full story here but we’re hoping to write this thing. The reason we did the podcast was … It was another way to further the intentions of what Hacker Noon was doing. I was already running your crypto podcast. It just made sense. I was getting most of my traffic from Hacker Noon ’cause I was publishing all my episodes on Hacker Noon. I was like “Why am I doing my own thing?” It just made total sense to join Hacker Noon and do this and then continue to work with you and see this process through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re potentially weeks away from getting Hacker Noon 2.0?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Yeah. So …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Things are happening fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Yeah, and we need to get our CEO off Twitter arguing with the former Twitter co-founder about e-mails that are being sent. So, I hate to bring it back to that but let’s talk about the last three or four days here. I mean — how to put it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: I mean, a lot of it really started with two viral tweets: One is &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/garrytan/status/1105311939066884096"&gt;Garry Tan from Initialized Capital &lt;/a&gt;who invested in our crowdfunding campaign talking about what this message that they sent to our contributors is insane and that really resonated with a lot of people and then &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ow/status/1105462220517969920"&gt;Owen at OW on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, he got the message and he was extremely confused and thought that we were trying to take their content and own it and have like this license that we didn’t intend to have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;We wrote it a while ago and, frankly, did not spend much on it because we did not have much money and that shows you, RICH PEOPLE PAY FOR GOOD PAPERWORK.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there was truth and the community came out and said “We didn’t write our nonexclusive license as clean as we should.” We wrote it a while ago and, frankly, did not spend much on it because we did not have much money and that shows you rich people pay for good paperwork. That is the lesson here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, we’re getting attacked for these things that we didn’t even intend to do. So, then the next day, we’re e-mailing the lawyers, we’re getting on the phone with them, we’re cleaning up the terms and conditions. We’re like “Hey. You can remove your content at any time. You will always be accredited. We just wanna publish people that wanna be here.” That’s our intention here. A simple non exclusive license which is not a simple thing to do. It sounds like it is but it’s really not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, that was pretty stressful and then writing statements ’cause our response when we saw this e-mail from them was like “We have to respond to that.” So, I wrote &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/DavidSmooke/status/1105520864043261953"&gt;my own statement&lt;/a&gt;, we had &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hackernoon/status/1105290961100259328"&gt;a company statement&lt;/a&gt;, so I’m @DavidSmooke on Twitter and Hacker Noon is @HackerNoon on Twitter so you can see on there if you want but they’re essentially saying “No, we’re not trying to take any content. We’re trying to keep it on the land that it is, on the URL, on the location that it is where all the links go to. We’re serving the writers and writers now have a choice. You can either opt in to keeping your content on hackernoon.com or you can choose to remove it and a bunch of links to your story will break and it’s up to you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Our success is not going to be determined by the transitioning of past stories.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;They’re past stories. Our success is not going to be determined by the transitioning of past stories but they’re stories that all the writers wanted to publish on Hacker Noon and they are in hackernoon.com. It’s a tough process and I talked to multiple lawyers as these threats were going on and many people think there’s no reason to even go get another license and another agreement from these writers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: I’m one of these people. Can you talk a little bit about this ’cause I think this is really important? Why can’t you just take the content that everybody submitted to hackernoon.com as its own, essentially, independent site … Why can’t you just take that content and move it to hackernoon.com?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: I mean, the short answer is I believe I can but lawyers have different points of view and amongst themselves they do. So, I think it’s better to cover my ass and get additional agreements and also it means I’m working with more of the writers who believe in us more which is what I wanna do, too. So, the process has been really fun and just, in terms of getting to communicate with the best writers in the community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, the short answer is if you agree to publish on hackernoon.com and Hacker Noon changes its hosting provider or changes its whatever which goes from react to vue on the front end. It’s still on the same URL and it’s never been on a different URL. So, to me it’s pretty simple but it’s never simple. It’s just like if it’s affecting another business, another business is gonna react and they’re gonna have their own point of view.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;There’s no writer on the site that didn’t agree to publish on the site but it’s better to be thorough and, as the little guy, it’s better to be thorough than spend money on lawyers.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, we’re putting in the extra work and we’re communicating one on one with thousands of writers and it is a lot of work. I wish we were just putting all of our labor into just growing the site and having ways to raise the quality and grow the community. It’s frustrating to be wasting time on things that were already done. There’s no writer on the site that didn’t agree to publish on the site but it’s better to be thorough and, as the little guy, it’s better to be thorough than spend money on lawyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d rather engage with the community and I’d rather do it this way but it’s definitely more work than a riskier person would do. A riskier person would just keep the content where it is on hackernoon.com and move on with their life but I think this is better and, really, I just wish the transition plan was smooth and I wasn’t getting Yes, no, yes, no, yes … Silence, silence, silence, what’s going on? Follow up, follow up. Nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, yeah it’s been a pretty tough time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: You’d think Medium would have put together some kind of transition terms or figured out what this is-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: They did. “Don’t do anything else. Take our low ball offer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: That was their ideal transition terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: That’s not right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Don’t do anything else. Take our low ball offer.” That was their ideal transition terms.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: I mean, it’s not really about right or wrong. I would not do business that way and I did not agree to that deal but other people did, you know? The Bold Italic is now not The Bold Italic anymore. So, for some people, it’s the right decision, but to me, the idea that I would take literally two cents on the dollar is infuriating and it’s insulting to the thousands of hours and thousands of hours of labor that me, my team, and the community, and the part time people have put into this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Yep, and now those people are being e-mailed from Medium with disparaging remarks and just kind of muddying the waters. I don’t know how else to put it. I mean, systemically, this isn’t just happening to Hacker Noon and Medium, this is happening with Twitter, this is happening with Facebook. There’s actually gonna be another episode of the podcast soon where I talk to Christian Warren. She’s formally of Mashable and Gizmodo and I go into detail about this so I won’t talk too much on it right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When that episode comes out, definitely take a listen. It’s pretty awesome but this is happening in Silicon Valley. This is happening with all of these major social media sites. They’ve changed their algorithms, they’ve changed how they operate with publishers, they’ve changed how they operate with their users. Just the other day, I think, Facebook is being criminally investigated with how they’ve handled user data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, there’s a lot of different things going on right now in Silicon Valley, in this tech space, and what’s happening to Hacker Noon is a symptom of this same disease or disorder that’s happening across all of these social network sites right now and it’s kind of sad to see but on the other hand, there is a silver lining here because Hacker Noon 2.0 has a future. Can you talk a bit about where you’re going now? What does the future look like for Hacker Noon? What are some of the things that this team is working on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah. Yeah, these social media sites, man, they change so much over time. It is frustrating. With Hacker Noon 2.0, we wanna raise the quality of the content and that starts with editors. So, we’ve already brought on more part time editors and we’re gonna have a minimum baseline of how much time they spend on each story and then we’re also … We wanna get towards great expertise leads editorial line and that’s’ where the authority on Bitcoin, now because they’ve written so much on Bitcoin and they have proved the authority of the site, they now have the power to publish other people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, we wanna keep the essence of … There’s also a second person to review your story if you want and there’s always someone in the community to help you make a better story and that simple level of quality control makes … It’s so much better. It’s not the same as an editor spending three hours rewriting your story, but it’s so much better than you just hitting the publish button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;(We can) tighten that communication and empowering contributors and editors, (so) contributors to know when their draft is open, know what changes the editor made, and know when the story’s scheduled.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, there are many features where the community wants to help but they cannot because of the way the software is designed. The way Medium designed their software is there’s one editor, they can edit every single page on the site, and that’s it. The communication is private, no … Hard to get history. So, looking at tightening that communication and empowering contributors and editors, contributors to know when their draft is open, to know what changes the editor made, and to know when the story’s scheduled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are simple communication points that we just can’t do with our current software and editors are a gateway. They’re a gateway to contributors getting published and right now, we have too many contributors and the volume of submissions is too high. So, there’s always gonna be a balance between the amount of editing and the amount of stories submitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, that’s kind of the rate of publishing side of things. On the reader side of things, we wanna keep what’s working in the current environment and with this content management system. Making it just text for a bunch of it and never interrupting the story with anything else is in our blood and we’re gonna stick to it and we’re not …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because our model is a sponsorship, an eyeball that’s not logged in is still valuable to us. If your model is not that, that’s not true. So, we’re not gonna have a pop up ad when you get to the story to create an account for us. It’s your content. There’s not business of Hacker Noon putting a pop up ad on top of your content when you or someone else drove traffic to the story. So, that flow is infuriating whenever the traffic’s coming from elsewhere and then someone else is putting a pop up ad in front of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Because our model is a sponsorship, an eyeball that’s not logged in is still valuable to us….Our readers will create accounts when they wanna take actions.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our readers will create accounts when they wanna take actions. If you wanna react to the story, if you wanna comment on the story, if you wanna build a book mark list. If you wanna do those types of things, you’ll create an account in the moment you wanna do the thing. You don’t create an account just to access the free content. So, that’s what we wanna stick very firm to and I think it’s gonna service very well because we’re reducing barriers for people to read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you put an ad, or you put a layover, or you put a prompt or whatever you wanna call it in the way of people reading, people read less and I’ve seen, in our bounce rate as I’m monitoring how often the Medium account creation comes over the hackernoon.com story. So, it’s a tough balance and it just doesn’t make sense to us ’cause I don’t wanna read all that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s also that level when you’re building something of like “Would I use it?” And if I don’t endorse it, I cannot put other people onto it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Well, hopefully here, that’s gonna be changing very soon with Hacker Noon 2.0 which, from a user standpoint, all you have to do is continue to go to Hacker Noon. There’s not really much else for them to do. They might have to re-register an account or maybe go through some kind of process like that but is there anything else that users can anticipate other than, potentially, a better experience?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: I think we’re gonna be a little softer on the green. With Medium, we don’t have much control over the design. We basically just pick a color right now and our green is 0 red, 255 green, and 0 blue on the RGB scale. That makes it green; very green. Some people have complained and I think we’ll have better design. We’re never gonna lose the green. It’s just it won’t be as many pixels but I think we’ll create a great community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We really wanna just have … Those first person stories are my personal favorite just in terms of like really getting into the expertise of your job or where your field is headed but there’s a lot of great how to and how they’re building and we’ve had a lot of cryptocurrency content and a lot of block chain content because I believe cryptocurrency is where technology has the potential to change the world the most in cutting out these institutions and intermediaries and letting peer to peer people make decisions and interactions without having to pay a transaction fee on all that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a real-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: There’s some parallels there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah, and I mean, long term, I firmly believe the highest … In the short term, we’re going to make money with the top navigation sponsor and the brands that we’ve been publishing like &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@alitech_2017"&gt;Alibaba Tech&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/@angellist"&gt;AngelList&lt;/a&gt;, we’ve been doing that for free but in the future, if you want the brand as author, it’s gonna be a small fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, that’s gonna be our group of small payments and subscription payments and if it’s great content … And that’ll still go through the same editorial process, it’s just if you want the actual author accreditation to be a logo instead of a human, that’s something that people will pay for and that’s where I believe the Google developer blog and all these top tech company’s blogs are content tech professionals should read and they are reading and it’s something they could read on Hacker Noon instead of going to the Google developer’s blog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I think it’s a nice happy medium of serving the reader by getting them content that they wouldn’t normally read but also, if the brand wants their logo there, there’s a small fee. So, that’s kinda the two that’s gonna take us, I believe, to profitability but the longest term (highest ceiling) path of this company is all the contributions not to a cryptocurrency and that cryptocurrency has a price and it can be bought and sold elsewhere. And every time you hit some mile stone, you create a day of time reading. Like you write a good story, people literally spend a day’s worth of time on it across all the thousands of readers, that’s a mile stone I think would earn a currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;I believe the longest term (highest ceiling) path of this company is all the contributions not to a cryptocurrency and that cryptocurrency has a price and it can be bought and sold elsewhere.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, that’s kind of the highest future we have and we may not get there. We may just successfully have these two, three revenue streams, events, podcasts, and grow from four to eight to 10 people and serve contributors and grow their communities but I just think … You’ve seen the community. 1200 people own shares in the company and wanna own it. There’s a reality that this community can become much bigger and tech is infiltrating everything and the stories of how technology’s built, why it’s built, where it’s built, when it’s built, those stories are going to get more readership in the future whether it’s on my site or elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s something that’s just going to happen in my opinion. So, I think we’re gonna end up with a much better site than we have today. I definitely have better people on it; people that are better than me. When it’s just me, it’s my fault so now I have other people to blame, too, which doesn’t really work. All the blame still ends up falling on me but it’s fun. It’s so cool to have a team and I’m really excited to go to work. I’m excited to move past Medium and stop using their content management system and just have that be a story of the past ’cause I am thankful that they helped us grow. I’m thankful that they offered a CMS that was so plug and play and people like me could get started and see if their thing is true ’cause I failed in 15 other publications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of them would have peaks, some of them would make some money, sometimes it would work but the reality was it wasn’t a strong enough fit and it didn’t hit the spot like Hacker Noon did as a place to read and enough people that really … Well over the thousand true fans and so the idea that a company could … Like I said in the beginning, I didn’t set out to build Hacker Noon. I set out to try things in publishing and do things that worked and if it made more money, do it again, and if drew more traffic, do it again and it’s like through this process of iteration, I ended up at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s the same problem. You run into a problem, do you kill it or do you iterate? And we’re people that are just gonna keep iterating on this thing so when Hacker Noon 2.0 launches in late March or April, it’s not going to be perfect. There are gonna be key things that are better about the site than it is today but it’s made by four people in four months and we’re trying to like … It’s just not going to be perfect and I’m totally happy with it because there are key things about it that are gonna be better in how the community can interact with each other and I think there’s just a lot of activity that is happening around the site that …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best part is when the contributors interact with each other. That is happening in Facebook groups, or WhatsApp groups, or Discourse instance. It’s happening all over the place and we can bring it together, I think, and create a thoughtful, intelligent, and respectful technology community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: So, David. I gotta stick with tradition here so I gotta ask you what’s some time in your life you had to hack something? I know you just probably listed about ten examples but I’m gonna need one more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Oh, one more. A good one of hacking something. I mean, let’s see … I guess I should’ve been prepared for this question, huh?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: I think, actually, you originally came up with this question and told me I should start asking all the guests this at the end of each episode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah, I did do that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: So, I’m throwing it back at you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: So, this may sound like a silly one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Go for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: My daughter’s in that age where we’re almost moving from the crib to a bed and right now, in her room, the way we set it up is there’s the crib and then there’s this guest bedroom, basically, a guest bed next to her and I was like “Okay, are we gonna get her a kid bed? I don’t want her to fall off the bed” and the way I hacked it was I just took apart the bed frame, got rid of it, and put the mattress on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, now, she has a giant bed on the floor, no threat of rolling off, and instead of buying a two year old to five year old bed or some one of those little kiddie beds, I just destroyed the guest bed and have a mattress on the floor. So, less is more. She loves it. Plenty of room for all these stuffed animals and that’s a story of how I threw away a bed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: But also gained a bed at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Yeah, yeah, that I didn’t have. If she was on a real bed and she falls off, that’s super scary. I reduced a lot of risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: There we go. Let’s summarize this kind of for the audience. Just kind of recap what happened with the Medium situation quickly and where Hacker Noon 2.0 is going now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: So, we build on their content management system, we’re moving off their content management system, building our own infrastructure on hackernoon.com. In the transition, writers can either keep their stories with us or remove ’em and they can always remove their stories if they want and they can always get their stories review by an editor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They can’t always publish with us. It depends on the quality of it but it’s going to be a much better site, I believe. I think it’s gonna be a more open site, less barriers to reading, and I think more experts curating the content is gonna create a better experience to get to your next story as opposed to machines curating it or someone like me curating. I’m not an expert on block chain, I shouldn’t be curating the blockchain page.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I think empowering the community to curate and empowering the community to publish others is going to raise the quality of the content on the site and just make it to readers not … Like don’t get in the way. That’s like the primary job. You found our site somehow on the internet and you’re gaining value from it, I’m just not gonna get in the way. That’s the like the main thing I’m going to strive for and then, hopefully, with the community curating better and the community being empowered to curate, the reader will get a better next story and when they get to a group of stories, they’ll have a more relevant collection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;You found our site somehow on the internet and you’re gaining value from it, I’m just not gonna get in the way.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I think it’ll be a better reading experience. I think we’ll publish more people and I’m looking forward to Hacker Noon 2.0 and I hope you’ll just give it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Yup, and we’re gonna continue to have a lot of those contributing writers on the podcast, as well, and we’re going to keep pushing forward with the show, as well and, continue-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Oh, we set up &lt;a href="https://contribute.hackernoon.com/"&gt;contribute.hackernoon.com&lt;/a&gt; for anyone to submit a story. So, it’s a pretty simple workflow if you wanna share the cool stuff you’re building, we’ll be happy to review, improve, distribute, and get your story out there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Awesome. And where else can people find Hacker Noon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/"&gt;Hackernoon.com&lt;/a&gt; is where it’s been and where it’ll be so that’s the primary thing people should remember… but &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/hackernoon/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/hackernoon"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/domain/hackernoon.com/"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;, all that fun stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Or on &lt;a href="http://hackernoon.video"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;, too, where this video is right now. So …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Oh, yeah. You can type in &lt;a href="http://hackernoon.video"&gt;hackernoon.video&lt;/a&gt; and you’ll end up on our YouTube channel or YouTube, if you’ve heard of it, they host videos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Well, thank you for coming on the show, man. We’re gonna have to get you on more often hopefully under better circumstances but I thought it was really important to have you on and clarify to the Hacker Noon community what’s going on and, hopefully, we’ve accomplished that and things continue to move forward with Hacker Noon 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Thanks for nudging me to do this, Trent. It was fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trent: Alright.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David: Back to the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FHy4Lduu9CKg%3Ffeature%3Doembed&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DHy4Lduu9CKg&amp;amp;image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FHy4Lduu9CKg%2Fhqdefault.jpg&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;schema=youtube" width="854" height="480" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/bd1d8b6216368afc620e3fd0176c1015/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/bd1d8b6216368afc620e3fd0176c1015/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=7c72353ba6e" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/about-removing-medium-from-hackernoon-com-7c72353ba6e"&gt;About Removing Medium from Hackernoon.com&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 21:11:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bakkt Taps Former IBM and Cisco Exec Tom Noonan to Chair Its Board -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bakkt-taps-former-ibm-and-cisco-exec-tom-noonan-to-chair-its-board</link><description>Bakkt has tapped Tom Noonan, a founder of multiple cybersecurity startups, to chair its new board.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : NDSU Offers Nation's First Ph.D. in Cybersecurity Education -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/ndsu-offers-nations-first-phd-in-cybersecurity-education/d/d-id/1334292?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>The new program focuses on training university-level educators in cybersecurity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 13:30:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Cluley: New Zealand shooter’s manifesto used to spread disk-wiping malware -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.grahamcluley.com/new-zealand-shooters-manifesto-used-to-spread-disk-wiping-malware/</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.grahamcluley.com/new-zealand-shooters-manifesto-used-to-spread-disk-wiping-malware/" title="New Zealand shooter’s manifesto used to spread disk-wiping malware"&gt;&lt;img width="100" height="100" src="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/this-is-not-us-thumb-150x150.jpeg" class="attachment-100x100 size-100x100 wp-post-image" alt="New Zealand shooter&amp;#039;s manifesto used to spread disk-wiping malware" style="float: right; margin-left: 10px; margin-bottom: 10px;" srcset="https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/this-is-not-us-thumb-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/this-is-not-us-thumb-75x75.jpeg 75w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/this-is-not-us-thumb-45x45.jpeg 45w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/this-is-not-us-thumb-190x190.jpeg 190w, https://www.grahamcluley.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/this-is-not-us-thumb.jpeg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 100px) 100vw, 100px" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone has taken a copy of the shooter’s Word document and weaponised it to download malicious code from the internet.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 15:05:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker News: Learn Ethical Hacking with 180 Hours of Training — 2019 Course Bundle -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~3/T92C0mCzVoY/ethical-hacker-training.html</link><description>The world of cybersecurity is fast-paced and ever-changing.

New attacks are unleashed every day, and companies around the world lose millions of dollars as a result.

The only thing standing in the way of cybercrime is a small army of ethical hackers. These cybersecurity experts are employed to find weaknesses before they can be exploited. It’s a lucrative career, and anyone can find work&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~4/T92C0mCzVoY" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 07:09:27 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Malware researchers decrypted the Qrypter Payload -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83042/malware/decrypting-qrypter-payload.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Malware researchers at Cybaze-Yoroi ZLAB team dissected a new sample of Qrypter malware that revealed an interesting evolution of the threat. Introduction During the last weeks, Yoroi’s monitoring operation intercepted some malicious emails required further attention: they were sent to a very few organizations and the content was specifically tailored for Italian speaking targets. This [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83042/malware/decrypting-qrypter-payload.html"&gt;Malware researchers decrypted the Qrypter Payload&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 12:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker News: Here's the List of ~600 MAC Addresses Targeted in Recent ASUS Hack -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~3/1bku-D3eo-s/asus-hack-mac-addresses.html</link><description>EXCLUSIVE — While revealing details of a massive supply chain cyber attack against ASUS customers, Russian security firm Kaspersky last week didn't release the full list all MAC addresses that hackers hardcoded into their malware to surgically target a specific pool of users.

Instead, Kaspersky released a dedicated offline tool and launched an online web page where ASUS PC users can search&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~4/1bku-D3eo-s" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 05:39:19 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Peace offering made to small financial institutions on fast payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/peace-offering-made-to-small-financial-institutions-on-fast-payments</link><description>The Clearing House announced moves to attract community banks and credit unions to its real-time payments system. Smaller depositories have generally been reluctant to sign up with what is seen as a large-bank effort.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 18:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Canadian Municipality Set to Accept Bitcoin for Property Tax Payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/canadian-municipality-set-to-accept-bitcoin-for-property-tax-payments</link><description>The Town of Innisfil, Ontario, will accept bitcoin for property tax payments from next month in a one-year trial project.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 22:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Comviva bids to accelerate growth of contactless digital payments in India -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77846/comviva-bids-to-accelerate-growth-of-contactless-digital-payments-in-india?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Comviva, the global leader in providing mobility solutions, announced that its mobiquity Wallet Tap...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 09:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Virtual Banks Launch in Hong Kong; Can Bitcoin Save Argentina? -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://finovate.com/virtual-banks-launch-in-hong-kong-can-bitcoin-save-argentina/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Finovate Global is our weekly look at fintech innovation in developing economies in Asia, Africa, the Middle East, Latin America, and Central and Eastern Europe. Sub-Saharan Africa Nigerian payments company Amplify has been acquired by OneFinance (OneFi). Terms of the deal were not disclosed. Tech in Africa profiles Kenyan fintech Branch. Compelo features insurtechs and savings &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/virtual-banks-launch-in-hong-kong-can-bitcoin-save-argentina/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/virtual-banks-launch-in-hong-kong-can-bitcoin-save-argentina/"&gt;Virtual Banks Launch in Hong Kong; Can Bitcoin Save Argentina?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: India’s Federal Bank Teams Up With Blockchain Co Ripple For International Payments -  Puntaje: 2600</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/blockchain/2019/india-federal-bank-cross-border/</link><description>Federal Bank in India has partnered with blockchain payments company Ripple to facilitate cross-border payments, according to reports. Federal Bank confirmed the collaboration in an announcement to the Bombay Stock Exchange on Thursday (March 28). “This is to inform Federal Bank has entered into a partnership with Ripple Inc, a blockchain supported global remittance company, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 17:07:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Billions in remittances to cross through ABER benefitting inter-Arab trade -  Puntaje: 11400</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/billions-in-remittances-to-cross-through-aber-benefitting-inter-arab-trade/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_621927125-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_621927125-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_621927125-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Economic growth among Arab countries is expected to be 3% this year and 3.5% in 2020, according to the director general of Arab Monetary Fund, Dr Abdul Rahman Al Hamidy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arab countries traded what amounted to $585 bn between themselves without the recourse to any fintech-facilitating tool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s about to change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABER&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Arab Regional Payment System (ARPS) that Saudi Arabian Monetary Authority (SAMA) and the UAE Central Bank (UAECB) piloted in January 2019 aims at expanding intra-Arab trade and investment activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The crypto-based system through the use of blockchain technology named ABER ffavoursArab currency for cross-border payments among 22 member countries and has the added-value of cutting the cost and duration of remittances and payments between them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The project is in the final stages and we are close to finalising the articles of establishment like building the system for smooth transactions. We will soon release the date when the actual transactions will start,” said Al Hamidy last Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The investment involves putting an initial capital of $100 million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arab business deals&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The total value of economic and financial transactions among Arab nations is estimated to have reached up to $830 billion per year, of which $245 billion is attributed to intra-Arab trade in 2018, according to estimates by the Arab Monetary Fund (AMF), Al Hamidy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ARPS will also foster the economic, trade, and investment relations with the region’s main trade partners from all parts of the world, considering that trade between the Arab region and the global economy amounted to roughly $1,960 billion in 2018, which equates to 5% of total global trade,” Al-Hamidy added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fintech such as blockchain enhance the efficiency of payments and create new opportunities such as access to remittances amounting to billions of dollars, not only among expats living in Arab countries but also Arab expats living abroad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zawya said that a recent KPMG report revealed global funding in financial technology increased by 120% in 2018 to $111.8 billion up from $50.8 billion in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chief executive of Bahrain Fintech Bay told Zawya earlier this month that Middle East fintech investments make up just 1% of the global total, but he added that cross-border collaboration could significantly boost the industry’s growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/billions-in-remittances-to-cross-through-aber-benefitting-inter-arab-trade/"&gt;Billions in remittances to cross through ABER benefitting inter-Arab trade&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 12:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Who your competitors are in today's tech-focused economy depends on your strategy -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/videoarticle/2024/who-your-competitors-are-in-todays-tech-focused-economy-depends-on-your-strategy?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Sairam Rangachairi Executive Director, Head of Open Banking &amp; API Strategy, JP Morgan, speaks at Mon...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 15:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Taking a commercial approach to Open Banking and APIs -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/videoarticle/2023/taking-a-commercial-approach-to-open-banking-and-apis?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Sairam Rangachairi, Executive Director, Head of Open Banking &amp; API Strategy, JP Morgan, speaks at Mo...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 11:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: Klarna Launches Open Banking Platform -  Puntaje: 5500</title><link>https://finovate.com/klarna-launches-open-banking-platform/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;#160; Klarna is the latest fintech to embrace the open banking revolution. The payments company has announced the launch of its own Open Banking Platform, which will enable access to more than 4,300 banks in 14 different markets across Europe via a single Access to Account (XS2A) API &amp;#8211; all in accordance with PSD2 guidelines. &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/klarna-launches-open-banking-platform/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/klarna-launches-open-banking-platform/"&gt;Klarna Launches Open Banking Platform&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 15:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: ICO Fines Pensions Firm for Spamming Millions of Users -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/ico-fines-pensions-firm-millions-1/</link><description>Kent-based Grove Pensions Solutions received inaccurate legal advice</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 09:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Fintech startups: a modern Trojan horse story? -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16908/fintech-startups-a-modern-trojan-horse-story?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>After several years of fruitless siege, Greeks hid their best warriors in a giant wooden horse and l...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 11:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Qupital raises $15m Series A to expand into mainland China -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/qupital-raises-15m-series-a-to-expand-into-mainland-china/</link><description>Hong Kong fintech plans to hire and grow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 12:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Mail: Pentagon will be 'unapologetic' about using artificial intelligence -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6865045/Pentagon-unapologetic-using-artificial-intelligence.html?ns_mchannel=rss&amp;ns_campaign=1490&amp;ito=1490</link><description>Robert Work (pictured), who was Deputy Defense Secretary under Barack Obama, said the U.S. armed forces will 'have to grasp the inevitability' of artificial intelligence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:56:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC technology: AI judge to settle small claims disputes and other news -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-47555567</link><description>BBC Click's Dan Simmons looks at some the week's best technology stories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 08:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Singaporean Personal Loan Startup Helps to Fill up Tedious Application Loans for You -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29806/lending/credit-culture-startup-personal-loan-cloud-singapore-application-form-automation/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As part of a pilot by the Ministry of Law, a Singaporean fintech startup Credit Culture has just launched its cloud-based loan platform, the first pilot licensee to launch its&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29806/lending/credit-culture-startup-personal-loan-cloud-singapore-application-form-automation/"&gt;Singaporean Personal Loan Startup Helps to Fill up Tedious Application Loans for You&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 05:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: The battle of Fintech is over, the battle of TechFin is about to begin -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/03/29/the-battle-of-fintech-is-over-the-battle-of-techfin-is-about-to-begin/</link><description>Jack Ma famously called Alibaba and their tech giant peer group &amp;#8211; TechFins, declaring their intention to sneak into financial services. Banks were too focused on their battle with Fintechs then, that they perhaps were blindsided by the rise of TechFins. The first quarter of 2019 has been eventful, with major headlines from big tech [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 05:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: Vietnam’s FinTech Investment Landscape – In-Depth Review -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://gomedici.com/vietnam-fintech-investment-landscape-in-depth-review/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/vietnam-fintech-investment-landscape-in-depth-review.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;Over the next few weeks, MEDICI brings you a series of articles exploring FinTech in the ASEAN region. The articles, each focused on a different ASEAN country, provide comprehensive insights into the FinTech investment landscape in the region. ASEAN in Figures ASEAN (the Association of Southeast Asian Nations) is the third-largest Asian region. It is home to more than 630 million people and one-fourth of the population lives in urban areas. ASEAN has an annual growth rate of 4.7% and USD 119.97 billion in FDIs; it is also one of the fastest-growing regions as well as the seventh-largest economy globally. Its population is young and educated with a literacy rate of over 80%, phone-savvy with more than 0.5 phones per person, and enjoys a low-to-mid unemployment rate of 0.5%–6.9%. ASEAN members also have an average to a high life expectancy of 69–82.7 years, and a gender parity of 49.9% males...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 16:47:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: TymeBank’s AI-Powered Chatbot Key to Low-Cost Digital Strategy -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/03/tymebanks-ai-powered-chatbot-key-to-low-cost-digital-strategy/</link><description>Digital bank TymeBank and conversational banking technology provider Finn AI have teamed up to bring a low-cost, AI-powered experience to underserved consumers as well as small and micro businesses in emerging markets. TymeBank, which was awarded the first full banking license in South Africa in about two decades, signed up over 100,000 customers within the [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Guardian technology: 'Bias deep inside the code': the problem with AI 'ethics' in Silicon Valley -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/28/big-tech-ai-ethics-boards-prejudice</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As algorithms play a growing role in criminal justice, education and more, tech advisory boards and academic programs mirror real-world inequality&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Stanford &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/press-releases/2019/03/18/stanford-institute-human-centered-artificial-intelligence/"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; a new artificial intelligence institute, the university said the “designers of AI must be broadly representative of humanity” and unveiled 120 faculty and tech leaders partnering on the initiative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some were quick to notice that not a single member of this “representative” group appeared to be &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/chadloder/status/1108588849503109120"&gt;black&lt;/a&gt;. The backlash was &lt;a href="https://qz.com/1578617/stanfords-new-diverse-ai-institute-is-overwhelmingly-white-and-male/"&gt;swift&lt;/a&gt;, sparking discussion on the severe lack of diversity across the AI field. But the problems surrounding representation extend far beyond exclusion and prejudice in academia.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/28/big-tech-ai-ethics-boards-prejudice"&gt;Continue reading...&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 05:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: What I learned using GPT-2 to write a novel -  Puntaje: 2800</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/what-i-learned-using-gpt-2-to-write-a-novel-b74a6294c813?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The story&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;On February the 14th 2019 Open AI posted their peculiar love-letter to the AI community. They shared a 21-minute long blog talking about their new language model named GPT-2, examples of the text it had generated, and a slight warning. The blog ends with a series of possible policy implications and a release strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“…we expect that safety and security concerns will reduce our traditional publishing in the future, while increasing the importance of sharing safety, policy, and standards research” &lt;a href="https://openai.com/charter/"&gt;OpenAI Charter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;While we have grown accustomed to OpenAI sharing their full code bases alongside announcements, OpenAI is committed to making AI safe. On this occasion, releasing the full code was deemed unsafe, citing concerns around impersonation, misleading news, fake content, and spam/phishing attacks. As a compromise, OpenAI shared a small model with us. While less impressive than the full GPT-2 model, it did give us something to test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So that’s exactly what I did! Last week, I set up the small model of GPT-2 on my laptop to run a few experiments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, for a bit of fun, I thought I’d test its skill at creative writing. I didn’t hold great expectations with only the small model to hand, but I thought I could learn something about the capabilities of the model, and perhaps start a few interesting conversations about technology while I was at it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I joined a popular online writing forum with an account named GPT2 and wrote a short disclaimer, which said;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;** This is computer generated text created using the OpenAI GPT-2 ‘small model’. The full model is not currently available to the public due to safety concerns (e.g. fake news and impersonation). I am not affiliated with OpenAI. Click this link to find out more &amp;gt;&amp;gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://openai.com/blog/better-language-models/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://openai.com/blog/better-language-models/&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; **&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The setup seemed perfect. I had a ready-made prompt to feed into GPT-2, and the model’s output is the exact length expected for submissions. I could even get feedback from other users on the quality of the submission. I chose a few specific blurbs and fed them into GPT-2 as a prompt, running the model multiple times before it created a plausible output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I pasted the story into the platform with my disclaimer at the top, excited to see what sort of questions I would receive from the community. I hit enter, and within seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;‘You have been banned.’&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was confused. I had been abundantly transparent about my use of computer-generated text and had not attempted to submit a large number of posts, just one. This was where I learned my first lesson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lesson 1 — Being transparent might not always be enough&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had made a strong conscious effort to be as transparent as possible. I didn’t want to deceive anyone into believing this was anything other than computer generated text. Far from it, I wanted people to know it was created by GPT-2 to engage them in a conversation around AI safety. I naively thought I would avoid a negative response through my honesty, but that was not enough for this community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I messaged the moderators. This is the reply I received;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*1X47eLIwp7myWkDmjkviow.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Please note, I have redacted any references to the specific forum out of respect for their community. They do not want to inspire copy-cats, and hopefully, this blog will make it apparent that I don’t either.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is how the conversation began but know that it ended happily!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lesson 2 — It’s not GPT-2 that’s the risk, it’s how we use it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shortly after the release of GPT-2 I saw two primary reactions to the limited release. There were parts of the mainstream media dusting off their favourite terminator photos, while some people in the AI community took the opinion that it was a marketing ploy — because any technology too dangerous to release must be very impressive indeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I only had access to the severely limited ‘small model’ of GPT-2. You need only use it for a few minutes to know just how far it is from being a terminator style risk, yet it still highlighted the need for thought through release strategy. Poor implementations of technology can have a negative impact on public sentiment, and in this instance, it was my choice of forum and application of the technology that raised the alarm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lesson 3 — Authenticity matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s possible that GPT-2 could write a charming story, but it won’t hold the same place in our hearts if it’s not both charming and authentic. Max Tegmark makes this point in Life 3.0, suggesting that AI could create new drugs or virtual experiences for us in a world where there are no jobs left for humans. These drugs could allow us to feel the same kind of achievement that we would get from winning a Nobel prize. But it’d be artificial. Tegmark argues that no matter how real it feels, or how addictive the adrenaline rush is, knowing that you’ve not actually put in the groundwork and knowing that you’ve effectively cheated your way to that achievement will mean it’s never the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Let’s say it produces great work”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For whatever reason, people desire the ‘real product’ even if it’s functionally worse in every way than an artificial version. Some people insist on putting ivory keytops on a piano because it’s the real thing — even though they go yellow, break easily and rely on a material harmful to animals. The plastic alternative is stronger and longer lasting, but it’s not the real thing. As the message (from the forum) says, even if ‘it produces great work’, possibly something functionally better than any story a human could have written, you don’t have the authentic product of ‘real people, who put time and effort into writing things.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lesson 4 — We don’t just care about the story — we care about the story behind the story&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The message also highlights two things — a human submission takes effort and creativity to produce, and that matters, even if the actual output is functionally no better than computer generated text. I think I agree. I have always found that a great book means so much more to me when I discover the story behind that — the tale of the writers own conscious experience that led them to create the work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fahrenheit 451&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ray Bradbury’s magnum opus, Fahrenheit 451 is a brilliant book in itself, but it was made a little bit more special to me by the story behind its creation. Bradbury had a young child when the novel was conceived and couldn’t find a quiet place at home to write. He happened across an underground room full of typewriters hired at 10c an hour. Bradbury wrote the whole book in that room, surrounded by others, typing things he knew nothing about. Nine days and $9.80 later, we had Fahrenheit 451.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vulfpeck — Sleepify&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t only apply to generated text. I recently spent far too much money importing a vinyl copy of Vulfpeck’s ‘Sleepify’ album. A record with 10 evenly spaced tracks, with completely smooth grooves. Why? It’s just pure silence! While this is an awful record based on its musical merit, and even the most basic music generation algorithm could have created something better, I love it for its story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The band Vulfpeck put this album on Spotify in 2014 and asked their fans to play it overnight while they slept. After about 2 months the album was pulled from Spotify, but not before the band made a little over $20,000 in royalty payments, which they used to run the’ Sleepify Tour’ entirely for free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As an aside, I think an AI like GPT-2 could also do a great job of creating a charming back-story behind the story. To the earlier point though, if it didn’t actually happen and if there wasn’t conscious human effort involved it lacks authenticity. As soon as I know that, it won’t mean the same thing to me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lesson 5 — Sometimes it’s about the writing process, not about being read&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*zUx_c-gjZqwTld7D6P0r1Q.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;My second response from the moderators&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing that came out of my conversation with the moderators that I’d not even considered was that it’s not all about the people reading the content, sometimes there’s more pleasure and personal development to be gained from writing, and that’s something the forum actively wanted to promote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Netflix’s new show ‘After Life’, (no real spoilers!) the main character, Tony, works for a local newspaper. Throughout the series, Tony points fun at the newspaper, from the mundane selection of stories that their town has to report on to the man delivering their papers, who it turns out just dumps them in a skip nearby. Nobody actually reads the paper, and Tony takes that to mean their work is meaningless up until the very end of the series. Tony realises that it doesn’t matter who reads the paper, or if anyone reads it at all. What’s important instead is being in the paper. Everyone should have the chance to have their story heard, no matter how mundane it might sound to others. If it makes them feel special and part of something bigger, even just for a moment, then it’s doing good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been writing for a few years now, and aside from the 18 blogs I now have on Medium, I have a vast amount of half-written thoughts, mostly garbage, and an ever-growing list of concepts that I’d like to expand on one day. Sometimes my writing is part of a bigger mission, to communicate around the uses, safety and societal impact of AI to a wide audience, and at those times I do care that my writing is read, and even better commented on and discussed. At other times, I use it as a tool to get my thoughts in order — to know the narrative and message behind a presentation that I need to make or a proposal that I need to submit. Sometimes, I write just because it’s fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If AI is capable of writing faster and better than humans, and it very much seems like it can (no doubt within some narrowing parameters)- it doesn’t mean that we can’t keep writing for these reasons. AI might capture the mindshare of readers, but I can still write for pleasure even if nobody is reading. However, I think it’ll mean people write a whole lot less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I began writing because I was asked to for work. It was a chore at the start, difficult, time-consuming and something I’d only apply myself to because there was a real and definite need. Gradually it became easier, until suddenly I found myself enjoying it. If it weren’t for that concrete demand years ago, I don’t know if I ever would have begun, and if I’d be here now writing for pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not a conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/600/1*BXQ9AeaV9JtOSbrUcKxSkg.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Not a flamethrower either&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that language models like GPT-2 can have a positive impact on society. OpenAI has identified a handful of examples, like better speech recognition systems, more capable dialogue agents, writing assistants and unsupervised translation between languages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this will be possible though unless we get the release strategy right, and have robust safety processes and policy to support it. Creative writing might not be the right application, so we need to ensure we identify the applications that society can agree are good uses of these language models. Codifying these applications that we approve and those that we want to protect in policy will help others to make the right decisions. Good communication will ensure that people understand what’s being used, why, and keep them onside. Robust security will prevent nefarious parties from circumventing policy and best practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note that these lessons are anecdotal, derived from a single interaction. No sound policy is based on anecdotal evidence, but rather academic research, drawing in a wide range of opinions with an unbiased methodology before boiling down values into concrete rules for everyone to follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story is just beginning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/454/1*YBmWdUPqr5JlRWfLNWye5Q.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Thankfully, we parted on good terms&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/700/1*MqyjtyN3EYRQ4WVmUm1z2Q.gif" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Credit: Ben Barry / OpenAI&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=b74a6294c813" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/what-i-learned-using-gpt-2-to-write-a-novel-b74a6294c813"&gt;What I learned using GPT-2 to write a novel&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 21:38:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>aljazeera: Killer robots: Scientists concerned over ethics of military AI -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/03/killer-robots-scientists-concerned-ethics-military-ai-190329140107653.html</link><description>Google employees rebelled last year, signing a petition saying Google should not be in the business of war.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: MoviePass Challenger Sinemia Said It Cancelled 3 Pct Of Accounts Due To Fraud -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/security-and-risk/2019/sinemia-movie-accounts/</link><description>Sinemia, the movie subscription service in direct competition with MoviePass, surprised customers by cancelling a number of accounts, according to a report by TechCrunch. “Sinemia is a FinTech company in the entertainment industry. Just like any other FinTech company, Sinemia  also faces its own challenges of fraud,” the company said. “After conducting a detailed fraud […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Top fintech stories this week – 29 March 2019 -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/top-fintech-stories-this-week-29-march-2019/</link><description>Catch up on FinTech Futures' top five fintech stories of the week - all in one place!</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 08:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Blockchain Gaming Startup Announces Global Licensing Agreement With Formula One -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-gaming-startup-announces-global-licensing-agreement-with-formula-one</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80NGE0ZGM5YjA1MWFjNmFkN2U4MjcwZWM5OTcwYTY4Ny5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockchain startup Animoca Brands reveals global licensing agreement with Formula 1® to publish a blockchain game based on the world-renowned racing series&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Facebook’s Blockchain Hiring Spree Continues With 5 New Job Postings -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/facebooks-blockchain-hiring-spree-continues-with-5-new-postings</link><description>Social media behemoth Facebook is advertising for five more blockchain-related positions – adding to the 20 posted by the company in recent weeks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : 7 Malware Families Ready to Ruin Your IoT's Day -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/iot/7-malware-families-ready-to-ruin-your-iots-day/d/d-id/1334246?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>This latest list of Internet of Things miscreants doesn't limit itself to botnets, like Mirai.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 13:00:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: CNA commits to a fully transmedia future to remain relevant in changing media landscape -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/singapore/cna-commits-to-a-fully-transmedia-future-to-remain-relevant-11393570</link><description>Technology, such as Augmented Reality and Artificial Intelligence, is increasingly being tapped to help deliver the news, says Mediacorp chairman Niam Chiam Meng on CNA's 20th anniversary.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 20:56:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Mt. Gox CEO Decides to Appeal Conviction on Manipulating Financial Records -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mt-gox-ceo-decides-to-appeal-conviction-on-manipulating-financial-records</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8zZGZkY2YyNmM2NzY0YjczOThiODcwOGNhNDAzZjJkMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Karpeles, former CEO of now-defunct Mt. Gox crypto exchange, has appealed his conviction on charges of manipulating data&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC technology: Worries about A.I. technology making fake news are a 'little overhyped,' says Salesforce scientist -  Puntaje: 500.0</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/29/salesforce-chief-scientist-richard-socher-on-challenges-future-of-ai.html</link><description>The worries over artificial intelligence&amp;#039;s ability to create disinformation may be overblown, according to one expert.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: UAE’s digital bank Liv launches Kasisto’s AI chatbot -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/uaes-digital-bank-liv-launches-kasistos-ai-chatbot/</link><description>The conversational AI is called Olivia.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Bitwise Asset Management report Claims 95% of Bitcoin Trading Volumes are Fake, Overstating True Size of the Market -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/30/bitwise-asset-management-report-claims-95-of-bitcoin-trading-volumes-are-fake-overstating-true-size-of-the-market/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/30/bitwise-asset-management-report-claims-95-of-bitcoin-trading-volumes-are-fake-overstating-true-size-of-the-market/"&gt;Bitwise Asset Management report Claims 95% of Bitcoin Trading Volumes are Fake, Overstating True Size of the Market&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-150x150.png" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-150x150.png 150w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-300x300.png 300w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-768x768.png 768w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-696x696.png 696w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-420x420.png 420w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-840x840.png 840w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA.png 900w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" data-attachment-id="32345" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/30/bitwise-asset-management-report-claims-95-of-bitcoin-trading-volumes-are-fake-overstating-true-size-of-the-market/1_d0lamhwy1epe6il-9ns6oa/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA.png" data-orig-size="900,900" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA-300x300.png" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/1_d0LAMHWy1EpE6il-9nS6oA.png" /&gt;A recent analysis by Bitwise Asset Management, the leading provider of cryptoasset index and beta funds, has recently claimed that 95 percent of Bitcoin’s reported trading volume is fake. The online version of their claim found here is part of their ETF submission to the SEC here &amp;#8211; and states that widespread stats on sites [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/30/bitwise-asset-management-report-claims-95-of-bitcoin-trading-volumes-are-fake-overstating-true-size-of-the-market/"&gt;Bitwise Asset Management report Claims 95% of Bitcoin Trading Volumes are Fake, Overstating True Size of the Market&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 23:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Why is Python Used for Machine Learning? -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/why-is-python-used-for-machine-learning-773aaaadd0ea?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*hLnluojxspNir60RyS8wuQ.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might have heard about the python which is the topmost programming language of the computers. It is a high-level programming language which is having dynamic semantics. As it, language is very easy and readable, so it reduces the cost of program maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Python is considered to be the simplest programming language of all, its usage is also ranked in the topmost place. In regard to this, a few seconds are needed to spend at the below-given graph:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/0*2AFO4ey0_Qp8nf5V" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the major advantages of its being easy is that it is very easy to interface with other languages as well particularly with C and C++. So let’s spend our little time to know what is the impact of using&lt;strong&gt; Python for machine learning.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a look below:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FesmzYhuFnds%3Ffeature%3Doembed&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DesmzYhuFnds&amp;amp;image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FesmzYhuFnds%2Fhqdefault.jpg&amp;amp;key=a19fcc184b9711e1b4764040d3dc5c07&amp;amp;type=text%2Fhtml&amp;amp;schema=youtube" width="854" height="480" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/f75e2226e309ed615490fe00e506261c/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/f75e2226e309ed615490fe00e506261c/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Why python holds an important position in Machine learning projects?&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Machine learning is basically an application of Artificial intelligence which enables computers and software to learn and envision outcomes automatically without the interference of human being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;what basically the work of Machine learning engineer. Machine learning engineer has to assemble, arrange and understand the data in order to develop the data into intelligent algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, according to the above-said statement that what actually the task of the Machine learning engineer, the Python language is recommended for the Machine learning projects as it is easy to understand in comparison to other languages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/0*Jp1-WqdIeMggqYJ2" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Python is preferred for Machine learning projects because its syntax structure is little easy to understand and its data handling capacity is just amazing. According to the &lt;a href="https://research.hackerrank.com/developer-skills/2018/"&gt;Hackerrank Stat 2018&lt;/a&gt; developer survey “JavaScript may be the most in-demand language by employers, but Python wins the heart of developers across all ages, according to our Love-Hate index.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;The immense selection of libraries and frameworks&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of, the main reasons for which Python is used for machine Learning is that it is having a large number of frameworks which makes coding easier and helps in saving development time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A little need to discuss some of the libraries and frameworks of Python which are really helpful for Machine learning. For scientific computation, there is Numpy, for advanced computation, there is SciPy, for data mining and data analysis, there is SciKit- learn. These libraries are working for frameworks such as TensorFlow, CNTK, and Apache Spark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is one framework of Python which is particularly written for &lt;strong&gt;Machine learning&lt;/strong&gt; and that is PyTorch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*CNCZzM9hYwh-vnMP" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Comprehensibility&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it is proved that Python is the most high-level language as it easy to understand and process. It is concise and is having the readable code and hence is also beneficial for the learning &lt;a href="https://www.pixelcrayons.com/hire-software-developers"&gt;custom software developers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Python is beneficial for use in Machine learning as ML algorithms are quite complex to solve and understand. And as Python is considered to be the simplest language, so the developer need not focus much on the coding part in order to understand and he can easily focus on the solving the complex projects based on Machine learning&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Python is having a simple syntax structure, it is considered easier in comparison to other languages. So, in the existence of this fact, the developers are allowed to test the complex algorithms very quickly without spending much time on implementing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Plenty of support&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Python which is considered to be the topmost programming language is being supported by various resources and good quality documentation. As python is supported by various types of high-quality resources, it also supports the developers while various stages of development by providing advice and assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Flexibility&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another advantage of using this language for ML projects is that it is having flexibility as one can go for any one option like either for OOPs approach or scripting. It helps in linking different data altogether. Apart from this, it helps the various developer, particularly who are struggling to check the majority code in IDE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Popularity&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it is already known that Python is well known as the topmost programming language as it is having easy to understand syntax structure. For developers, it is very easy to keep command over it, it means easily understandable for the developers. So, it could be said that it is easy to search for Python developers for ML projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Wrapping up&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the above-discussed information, it has become clear that why Python is used for the processing of Machine learning projects. As Machine learning is having complex algorithms, so, its issues could only be solved with the easy approach of Python language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Python is considered to be the simplest language which could easily be understood, so, it is the only option which can win over the complex tasks of the ML projects. Because by using this, &lt;a href="https://www.pixelcrayons.com/hire-python-developers-in-india"&gt;python developers in India&lt;/a&gt; will focus more on the complex projects instead of focusing on the code language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=773aaaadd0ea" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/why-is-python-used-for-machine-learning-773aaaadd0ea"&gt;Why is Python Used for Machine Learning?&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 21:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: IOHK Founder Charles Hoskinson Says Crypto Industry Needs More Interoperability -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/iohk-founder-charles-hoskinson-says-crypto-industry-needs-more-interoperability</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy82ZmU0MGI3YzY0MjAyMzlkNmU4MTg0NmZlOTgzNjg1MC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;IOHK founder Charles Hoskinson has argued that the cryptocurrency industry needs a “WiFi or Bluetooth moment”&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Android Malware Targets Users of 32 Crypto Apps, Including Coinbase, BitPay -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/android-malware-targets-users-of-32-crypto-apps-including-coinbase-bitpay</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80OWExYTM2NTViMzFjY2RiMjU5M2ViMGRhYTY5OTNiZi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;New strain of Trojan malware for Android phones is targeting global users of top crypto and bank apps&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Bahrain aiming to roll-out commercial 5G by June -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/telecom/bahrain-5g-june/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_762531937-1-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_762531937-1-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_762531937-1-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;The Minister of Transportation and Telecommunications, Kamal bin Ahmed Mohammed has announced that preparations for the rollout of 5G networks in the Kingdom of Bahrain are complete and anticipates that Bahrain will be one of the first countries globally to provide commercial 5G services by June 2019, pending availability of consumer handsets and equipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the regulatory hurdles to full 5G implementation have been resolved, with the licensing and spectrum allocation set to be finalised by mid-April by the Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA). Mobile operators in the Kingdom have already begun rolling out the necessary network infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bahrain’s state of readiness is a testament to the leadership of the Government of the Kingdom of Bahrain in enabling the implementation of cutting-edge technology and promoting innovation, and the continuous support of all stakeholders including the TRA and the national Spectrum Strategy &amp;amp; Coordination Committee (SSCC), all of which serves to highlight the Kingdom’s continued role as a regional leader in telecommunications and ICT,” said the Minister.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This announcement positions Bahrain as one of the globe’s leading 5G-ready countries and increases its attractiveness as a destination for companies trialling next-generation technologies such as autonomous vehicles and virtual/augmented reality products as the Kingdom continues to encourage investment in world-class telecommunications infrastructure and services. These products and services will also be ably supported by the National Broadband Network (NBN) which will offer ubiquitous high-speed fibre-based products to operators and consumers throughout the Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Successful commercial trials for 5G technology in the Kingdom of Bahrain were held in June 2018 and all the operators are preparing to provide commercial 5G services which will be ready to go when consumer handsets become available. The products and services will be in line with the 3GPP standards issued in 2018 and will predominantly utilise bandwidth in the C-Band spectrum (3GHz) and will allow Bahraini companies to tap into the global 5G services market, which is anticipated to grow from an estimated 60 billion USD in 2020 to an estimated 125 billion USD in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kingdom of Bahrain has consistently ranked high in global ICT indices, being ranked first in the Arab region in the ITU’s ICT Development Index (IDI) for the last five years, and ranked 4thglobally in the UN’s Telecommunications Infrastructure Index (TII) of the E-Government Development Index (EGDI) in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One major benefit of 5G technology is enabling higher volume of data transmission at higher speeds (lower latencies). This in turn enables the development and implementation of technologies such as autonomous driving vehicles, which can require up to 100Gb of data per second to operate. Research and development into other technologies such as AI open up a massive potential market for Bahrain. Furthermore, 5G can potentially support interactive technologies like virtual reality which need high bandwidth to send and receive large amounts of data with very low latency, helping enable the growth of some IoT applications and delivering improved video streaming and high-end gaming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our leadership in 5G reflects Bahrain’s appetite for innovation and sends a signal to the world that we can be a test-bed for some of the most transformative technologies. There were a lot of hurdles along the way – ensuring spectrum availability as soon as possible was a big challenge, but overcoming these obstacles exemplifies the support and cooperation amongst all stakeholders in Bahrain and demonstrates how Bahrain can move quickly, deliver enormous progress against an accelerated timeframe, and be a partner to technology leaders,” said the Minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/telecom/bahrain-5g-june/"&gt;Bahrain aiming to roll-out commercial 5G by June&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 08:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Digital Asset Journey - From crypto currency to corporate digital asset ecosystems -  Puntaje: 2300</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16909/digital-asset-journey---from-crypto-currency-to-corporate-digital-asset-ecosystems?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>2019 marks a special year for digital assets. On January 3, 2019, the world celebrated the 10th anni...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 11:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>