<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:25:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cointelegraph: Report: China Leading World in Blockchain Projects -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-china-leading-world-in-blockchain-projects</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85ZWU0ZWJkNGE2ZjdmZWE1NTQyNWMzYzc1NTEyMDI0Zi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a recent report, China is leading the world in the number of blockchain projects under development&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 03:10:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: PayPal joins Cambridge Blockchain funding round -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77893/paypal-joins-cambridge-blockchain-funding-round?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Cambridge Blockchain, Inc. a digital identity enterprise software provider, announced today that Pay...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 19:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: First blockchain Thai-Myanmar money transfer service to launch -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/first-blockchain-thai-myanmar-money-transfer-service-to-launch/</link><description>Designed to meet the needs of migrant workers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 11:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: PayPal Invests in Digital Identity-Focused Blockchain Startup in Apparent First -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/paypal-invests-in-digital-identity-focused-blockchain-startup-in-apparent-first</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81NGUzOTdjYzU4YmI5MTJiMGVmOTkzY2EyNzdlMjA2Yi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an apparent first, PayPal has made an investment in a blockchain startup — one that focuses on giving users more control over their digital identities&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:29:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: PayPal Makes Its First-Ever Investment in a Blockchain Startup -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/paypal-makes-its-first-ever-investment-in-a-blockchain-startup</link><description>Online payments giant PayPal has taken a stake in Cambridge Blockchain – its first investment in the blockchain space.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IBM Blockchain Blog: Does Hyperledger Fabric perform at scale? -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain/2019/04/does-hyperledger-fabric-perform-at-scale/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Yes. Yes it does! Quite often, clients ask us, “do channels scale?” Or, “I heard Hyperledger Fabric can only scale to N nodes, is this true?” They claim that they have read or heard information suggesting that Fabric and the channel model of privacy does not scale horizontally. When I ask where they got this [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain/2019/04/does-hyperledger-fabric-perform-at-scale/"&gt;Does Hyperledger Fabric perform at scale?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain"&gt;Blockchain Pulse: IBM Blockchain Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Berlin-based Brickblock Tokenizes Property in Europe in Private STO -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/berlin-based-brickblock-tokenizes-property-in-europe-in-private-sto/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/berlin-based-brickblock-tokenizes-property-in-europe-in-private-sto/"&gt;Berlin-based Brickblock Tokenizes Property in Europe in Private STO&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/BrickBlock-Photo-150x150.png" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="32360" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/berlin-based-brickblock-tokenizes-property-in-europe-in-private-sto/brickblock-photo/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/BrickBlock-Photo.png" data-orig-size="801,400" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="BrickBlock-Photo" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/BrickBlock-Photo-300x150.png" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/BrickBlock-Photo.png" /&gt;Berlin-based Brickblock is claiming they have done the first transaction in the European Union for fractionalized ownership tokens &amp;#8211; in which real estate shares are registered as digital tokens on the blockchain and entitle token holders to the economic benefits of the underlying real estate asset (e.g. dividends from rent, interest, principal distributions). The token [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/berlin-based-brickblock-tokenizes-property-in-europe-in-private-sto/"&gt;Berlin-based Brickblock Tokenizes Property in Europe in Private STO&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:08:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Coursera &amp; INSEAD launch Blockchain Specialization in the Middle East -  Puntaje: 1800</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/coursera-insead-blockchain-middle-east/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1221141247-1-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1221141247-1-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1221141247-1-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Coursera, the world’s leading online learning platform, has announced they are partnering with INSEAD, one of the world’s top business schools, to launch ‘Blockchain Revolution for the Enterprise,’ a new Specialization taught by Don Tapscott, adjunct professor at INSEAD and co-founder of the Blockchain Research Institute (BRI). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With content derived from the BRI’s multi-million-dollar research program, the four-course Specialization, available in the Middle East and around the globe, is designed to introduce business professionals to the world of blockchain, focusing on how to strategically leverage the technology to create scalable business opportunities. Tapscott is one of the world’s leading authorities on blockchain and the role technology plays in business and society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Blockchain is reshaping the business world and creating new opportunities across a variety of industries. It is helping revolutionize business processes, drive efficiencies, and even lower costs, so it’s critical that both technical developers and business professionals understand blockchain and its applications,” said Dil Sidhu, Chief Content Officer at Coursera. “We’re thrilled to collaborate with a top institution like INSEAD and leading blockchain authority Don Tapscott to help professionals make informed, strategic decisions about how to use blockchain to transform their business.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With blockchain spending in the Middle East and Africa poised to reach $307 million in 2021, acquiring blockchain skills will be key to helping the UAE emerge as a knowledge-powered economy," said Leah Belsky, Vice President of Enterprise at Coursera. "In line with Dubai's 'Blockchain Strategy', which aims to promote efficiency around government services and fuel economic development, our new ‘Blockchain Revolution for the Enterprise’ Specialization will help business leaders in the region gain the critical skills needed to innovate.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Educating leaders is one of the keys to accelerating the widespread adoption of blockchain,” said Don Tapscott. “Working with INSEAD and Coursera, we’ve been able to develop the world’s definitive online course for blockchain in business. This will be invaluable to learners around the world.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With no programming background necessary, Blockchain Revolution for the Enterprise enables mid-career and senior business professionals to: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Understand a high-level view of blockchain and how they can position themselves within this ecosystem&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Critically evaluate various claims, applications, use-cases, and implementation challenges of blockchain technology using seven design principles  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Produce a Blockchain Opportunity Analysis to assess the feasibility of a blockchain application within their own industry or organization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Blockchain, a technology predicted to disrupt many industries, is being viewed both as a threat and an opportunity,” said Peter Zemsky, Deputy Dean and Dean of Innovation at INSEAD. “It is important for INSEAD to lead the way to offer a universally accessible learning program to help demystify this technology and to prepare future leaders for this transformation.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The courses in the Blockchain Revolution for the Enterprise Specialization are now available online and kick off with the ‘Introduction to blockchain technologies’ course. Upon completion of the four-course program, learners will receive a certificate that they can share with potential employers and their professional network. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As blockchain presents another wave of global technological disruption, Coursera offers flexible, affordable ways for learners to keep up. Coursera will continue to provide an accessible pathway that empowers learners with skills that can transform their careers and their businesses. In the future, Coursera and INSEAD plan to launch a number of vertical-focused Specializations that adapt blockchain content for specific application in industries like healthcare, finance, and supply chain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/coursera-insead-blockchain-middle-east/"&gt;Coursera &amp;#038; INSEAD launch Blockchain Specialization in the Middle East&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 08:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Universal Faucet Integration: Polkadot -  Puntaje: 2400</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/universal-faucet-integration-polkadot-bdd9e25f8cb1?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/0*AkTNDy1ZzOuID1El" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;By: Jesse Abramowitz &lt;br&gt;Blockchain Developer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has been a while since I had been truly excited about a new blockchain. This is not to say applications. I think the applications on the blockchain are crushing it and there are some truly amazing products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Platforms themselves…other than Ethereum have not excited me. In my mind they either sacrifice decentralization for scalability or copy Ethereum’s road map and call themselves a 3rd generation blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One current way to scale blockchains is horizontally. This means to create more blockchains that can burden the load. For this to truly work seamlessly users must be able to walk in between those blockchains as easily as they switch websites on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also can see further issues with horizontal scaling. It is the difficulty, not to create a blockchain, that is actually really easy with the tools we have today. However, to truly decentralize, bridge and secure a chain is a vastly more complex situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You need to balance incentives and convince both users and network maintainers to hop on board whatever you are building. Once that is complete then you can actually build whatever application you had in mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polkadot offers a fascinating solution to this. They do scale vertically with a higher TPS than Ethereum but they also offer a horizontal scaling solution. Polkadot was built with Substrate. Substrate is a bunch of node modules that allow you to build your own blockchain fairly fast and customize it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href="https://www.parity.io/substrate-has-arrived/"&gt;core substrate modules&lt;/a&gt; you are connected to Polkadot. As well, you can borrow from Polkadot’s consensus security. Thus, if I now want to build my own chain I do not have to worry about the bridge or the security.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can customize and deploy a specific chain for a specific use case. We have seen this model pop up with Ethereum and some other really cool projects. For example, Burner wallet is all the rage and for good reason. It allows you to spend DAI by bridging over to the PoA network. Thus the burdens of gas are reduced astronomically. With Polkadot the creation of specific blockchains for this use purpose will have a lot of friction removed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, not only does Polkadot excite me, it left me staring up at my bed unable to sleep imagining a world with as many blockchains as websites communicating with each other. After spending a few hours deploying my own demo parachain, I knew I wanted to get my hands wet with Polkadot itself, so it’s been added to our &lt;a href="https://faucets.blockxlabs.com/?utm_source=Medium&amp;amp;utm_campaign=PolkaDot"&gt;Universal Faucet&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Blockchain&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://poc-3.polkadot.io"&gt;Polkadot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Tokens&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chain: Alexander&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;DOTs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why this Blockchain?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;They didn’t have a faucet yet and it will be an amazing chain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I love anything by &lt;a href="http://poc-3.polkadot.io"&gt;Parity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Getting coins&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href="https://matrix.to/#/!fOOzymDEHiIIUtmlBE:matrix.org?via=matrix.org&amp;amp;via=matrix.parity.io&amp;amp;via=status.im"&gt;community&lt;/a&gt; was super nice, after we demoed what we built people were tripping over themselves to send us more DOTs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Sending a Transaction&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This wasn’t bad at all, the &lt;a href="https://polkadot.js.org/ui/ui-identicon/#usage-examples"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; was pretty decent. I personally had an issue with some older packages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The JS &lt;a href="https://www.npmjs.com/package/@polkadot/api"&gt;package&lt;/a&gt; are getting updated quite frequently, the blockchain is new not even mainnet so constant updates are a good thing, makes it a tad bit challenging trying to use it though&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;iframe src="" width="0" height="0" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/media/7eaec0170358cb483332116cc7fee411/href"&gt;https://medium.com/media/7eaec0170358cb483332116cc7fee411/href&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Technical notes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Endpoint we were using was a websocket which was really cool. Should make updates from the network easier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We had to force a disconnection from the websocket after we send a transaction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;pre&gt;if (provider.isConnected()) provider.disconnect()&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;— -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jesse Abramowitz is a Blockchain Developer at BlockX Labs. He has worked on multiple DApps, projects, and Blockchain Networks. Currently, he is also a professor at George Brown College in Toronto. He is always looking to help, teach and build on the blockchain. You can reach him at: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:jesse@blockxlabs.com"&gt;&lt;em&gt;jesse@blockxlabs.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.blockxlabs.com/?utm_source=Medium&amp;amp;utm_campaign=MIT"&gt;BlockX Labs&lt;/a&gt; specializes in building developer tools and solutions for blockchain ecosystems.We aim to sift through the noise to bring some sense and clarity into the Blockchain space. Our accomplishments include &lt;a href="https://getaiwa.com/?utm_source=Medium&amp;amp;utm_campaign=MIT"&gt;AIWA&lt;/a&gt; — a wallet and DApp interaction tool for the Aion Network, and &lt;a href="https://faucets.blockxlabs.com/?utm_source=Medium&amp;amp;utm_campaign=MIT"&gt;Universal Faucet&lt;/a&gt; — a test token faucet for Ethereum, Aion, and Tron.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Us on Twitter: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BlockxLabs"&gt;@BlockXLabs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: BlockX Labs is a recipient of a Web3 Foundation Grant to build Enzyme — a dApp wallet for the Polkadot Network. This was announced on Wednesday March 29, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=bdd9e25f8cb1" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/universal-faucet-integration-polkadot-bdd9e25f8cb1"&gt;Universal Faucet Integration: Polkadot&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 18:29:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Logistics Company Partners With Blockchain-Based ‘ShipChain’ To Bring Cutting-Edge Tech to Supply Ch -  Puntaje: 4000</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/logistics-company-partners-with-blockchain-based-shipchain-to-bring-cutting-edge-tech-to-supply-ch-ae8a852e8757?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;h3&gt;Logistics Company Partners With Blockchain-Based ‘ShipChain’ To Bring Cutting-Edge Tech to Supply Chain&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*-FAsKyP8exRJFE2uNpneJQ.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the technology space, many companies (and their competitors) call themselves “blockchain solutions.” But, there’s one issue with the majority of these associations — the word “Blockchain” has simply been inserted for marketing purposes and nothing more. More often than not, companies are not implementing “true” blockchain technology, because these systems themselves aren’t completely decentralized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Visibility to the Supply Chain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest advantages that blockchain technology can and has already begin to bring to the world is the added visibility to the supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://shipchain.io/"&gt;Shipchain&lt;/a&gt;, the blockchain-based end-to-end logistics startup announced the integration of its platform with Scandinavian logistics company, &lt;a href="http://www.scanlog.se/en/"&gt;Scanlog&lt;/a&gt;, to help with the track-and-trace of Scanlog’s freight moving across the company’s logistics network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With this integration, Shipchain is able to help monitor Scanlog’s trucks — from the pickup point to the destination, all with the assistance of smart contract technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spoke with ShipChain’s CEO, John Monarch about the recent announcement and how this helps benefit the supply chain space as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*ROsF8ZV9Ty9QhugFZMCZSw.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;ShipChain CEO, John Monarch&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew Rossow: &lt;/strong&gt;In your opinion, why do you feel that ‘track-and-trace’ is necessary?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Monarch: &lt;/strong&gt;It’s monumental to adding visibility to the supply chain. As the industry currently stands, a shipment must pass through several different hands before it reaches the end consumer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AR: &lt;/strong&gt;For someone who may not be familiar with this process, can you walk us through it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JM: &lt;/strong&gt;It typically starts its journey in a manufacturing facility, is then transported to the port via truck, travels overseas on a shipping vessel, and then again by truck until it is reaches its final destination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The package is passing through so many different facilities and processes that it can be hard to keep track of its whereabouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AR: &lt;/strong&gt;So, what’s the issue?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JM:&lt;/strong&gt; The lack of transparency becomes an issue as goods are stolen or unaccounted for every single day. Without the added visibility that the Blockchain brings, it is extremely difficult to place accountability when things do go wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Monarch,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;every year, billions of dollars worth of goods disappear without a trace and are completely unaccounted for. “&lt;em&gt;Track and trace allows you to pinpoint exactly where they go missing in the supply chain, who was handling them most recently, and when they were last accounted for&lt;/em&gt;,” Monarch emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While minimizing chances for fraud and theft, it also “&lt;em&gt;boosts overall efficiency because less time is spent trying to locate shipments&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tackling The Supply Chain From End-End&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*_drpeNs9Xvco2AycD9JRSA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;With companies like &lt;em&gt;Walmart &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;em&gt;HP&lt;/em&gt; utilizing the Blockchain to help improve track-and-trace procedures, specifically pertaining to food traceability, the question becomes how other contenders are able to stand on equal ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;We are taking a holistic approach to solving the most pressing issues in shipping and logistics and doing so without asking you to hand your data over to us&lt;/em&gt;,” Monarch told me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are other companies, in the space using blockchain, but only ShipChain is working on the entire supply chain from end-to-end&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company told me that we are currently at a crossroads between technology of today and one of the oldest trades in the world — moving items. One one hand, Shipchain competes with classic solutions — from paper trails to supply chain control towers, but on the other, they have blockchain solutions that promise to do away with the “old way” of doing things and revolutionize the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AR:&lt;/strong&gt; What have you observed from your competition or others in the industry when it comes to this technology?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JM: &lt;/strong&gt;The emergence of private blockchains. Unlike us, many of our competitors who claim to be “blockchain solutions” are not truly implementing blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What I mean by that is there is a large number of “private blockchains.” As you know, private blockchains are not decentralized — someone or some entity owns them. In many ways, it is very similar to a cloud-based solution. By joining a private blockchain, you are essentially giving your data to the owners of the said blockchain. Since they now own that data, they can tamper with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We believe that to truly reap the benefits of the Blockchain, you must join a public chain like the one ShipChain is building upon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AR: &lt;/strong&gt;Why do “public blockchains” provide more flexibility than that of “private blockchains?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JM:&lt;/strong&gt; Private chains will only further fragment the industry because they may not have the ability to interact or communicate with other Blockchains. This limits the ability of all companies to use the same platform, essentially defeating the core mission of blockchain technology to streamline and make things more effective and transparent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public blockchains, on the other hand, are decentralized. They have no owner and they are extremely difficult to hack or tamper with. In truth, putting your data on a public blockchain means increased security through distributed consensus and validation. As the industry slowly transitions to a public blockchain, players will be able to rely on the technology itself for security, thereby increasing trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ShipChain will install its GPS-enabled cellular devices, known as &lt;em&gt;Axle Gateways&lt;/em&gt;, into the main cab of multiple Scanlog-associated participant trucks in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Axle Gateway&lt;/em&gt; is a device that drivers can attach to various jobs through the ShipChain Portal. The device allows shipments that are being carried out in real-time to be automatically synced with the tracking data and Ethereum blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;It will post encrypted GPS-data to the Scanlog on-site storage location and will generate a unique signature of data that will be posted to the Blockchain&lt;/em&gt;,” Monarch pointed out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company then grants Scanlog access to the ShipChain Mobile app that in turn allows Scanlog to attach photos and other relevant information to specific shipments along the way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;Our primary objective here is to increase visibility in Scanlog’s supply chain, thereby bringing peace of the mind to the company and its clients&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shipchain ended our conversation by stating that this partnership can help benefit other areas across the supply chain starting with &lt;em&gt;pharmaceuticals&lt;/em&gt; and continuing on to &lt;em&gt;food, agriculture, &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;em&gt;farming&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;Any issues with drugs or medical devices can have disastrous implications for patients and their families, so visibility in this space is extremely critical. The Blockchain helps to ensure that all pharmaceuticals are legitimate and maintained at the right temperature and under the right storage conditions&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=ae8a852e8757" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/logistics-company-partners-with-blockchain-based-shipchain-to-bring-cutting-edge-tech-to-supply-ch-ae8a852e8757"&gt;Logistics Company Partners With Blockchain-Based ‘ShipChain’ To Bring Cutting-Edge Tech to Supply Ch&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 17:56:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: How to Launch (or not launch) a Mainnet/Testnet? -  Puntaje: 21000</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/how-to-launch-or-not-launch-a-mainnet-testnet-f857a82b91ad?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*2RdNExLGOajHS96Y.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the most anticipated events in a crypto project roadmap are the testnet and mainnet launch. These are some critical milestones for both the projects as well as for the investors. Once a project reaches the testnet phase, it just gives out the message that the platform will be around for a long-term and shows good development in terms of progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From an investor’s perspective, this gives the project more legitimacy and more confidence to invest in the project. From a token value perspective, in the past, all major mainnet launches have seen a surge in token price which ranged to a healthy 25%- 30% in the current market and even more than 100% in the good old bull market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;So what’s exactly is Testnet and Mainnet?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/960/0*aWKEPLBmP3fQp_uu.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Testnet and Mainnet launches are simply the first steps to show the project is making substantial progress. When a project is launched as an ICO, the native token will be launched mostly as an ERC20, NEO, XLM etc based token which will be running on the respective blockchain. Once the project has successfully tested a stable product, it the natural course to launch its own mainnet for the journey ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Launching of its independent blockchain happens in two-phase. The first step is the testnet launch. As the name suggests, a &lt;strong&gt;testnet&lt;/strong&gt; is like a prototype of the proposed end product(in this case “mainnet”) for developers to experiment and test-run without risking breaking the main blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;In simple terms, a Testnet is the network used to test all the functionality of the mainnet before it is launched for widescale use.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the team is satisfied with the performance of testnet, all the changes are incorporated and the &lt;strong&gt;mainnet &lt;/strong&gt;is rolled out and will be made available for the public to use. Once the blockchain is deemed to be stable various exchanges and wallets start the process of token swaps and will be providing the users with the new tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Past stories: The Good and the Bad.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The EOS Mainnet nightmare&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/proxy/1*shlCiE6c7KGW_jinthx8Hg.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;EOS is backed by Block.one which raised &lt;a href="https://www.ccn.com/eos-ico-approaches-4-billion-after-year-long-crowdsale/"&gt;$4 billion&lt;/a&gt; for the project via an ICO that ran for almost a year. The EOS project is, we can say, reasonably young in the blockchain space which aims to radically improve on what is on the market today by bringing together positive elements of both the Bitcoin and Ethereum platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The major focus EOS platform is to eventually allow for industrial-scale applications, through the elimination of transaction fees and an ability to process tens of thousands of transactions per second; in contrast, to Ethereum that can currently handle around 15 transactions per second and Bitcoin with seven transactions a second, only.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EOS mainnet launch was one of the most awaited events for the year of 2018. The mainnet was scheduled to be launched on June 2018. Just a couple of days before the launch, Block.one’s email account was&lt;a href="https://ambcrypto.com/millions-worth-eos-token-stolen-from-investors-block-one-becomes-online-scam-victim/"&gt; hacked&lt;/a&gt; and hackers started to send the phishing email offering free EOS tokens. The link given in the mail was routed to an EOS styled website, asked the users to enter their private key to unlock their wallets to get the free tokens. Then you know what could have happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just around a week before the mainnet launch, Chinese internet security firm, Qihoo360 &lt;a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/chinese-report-epic-vulnerabilities-discovered-in-eos-blockchain-patched-same-day"&gt;found several vulnerabilities in the EOS network&lt;/a&gt; and they reported this to Block.one. These loopholes could have allowed hackers to remote control EOS nodes and attack any cryptocurrency built on top of its blockchain. Unsurprisingly Block.One asked Qihoo360 not to report the bugs to the public as they claimed to have resolved it on the same day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suddenly Block.one came up with a bug bounty program against their earlier communications of&lt;em&gt; “all is well”&lt;/em&gt;. This gave a doubt that EOS seemed to have misinformed their community about vulnerabilities getting fixed in time for the mainnet launch. This also confirmed that the testnet was not appropriately tested which ultimately lead to these kinds of issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/eosio/calling-all-devs-the-eosio-bug-bounty-program-is-live-7219c625a444"&gt;Calling all Devs: The EOSIO Bug Bounty Program is Live&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within 48 hrs of its launch, it was reported that EOS mainnet was &lt;a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/eos-mainnet-experiences-freeze-two-days-after-launch"&gt;experiencing a freeze&lt;/a&gt;. Irrespective of having such massive funding and resources, these setbacks from EOS was surprising to the crypto community, and all these instances proved &lt;em&gt;how not to launch a mainnet&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aelf Testnet — Showing the way.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/0*PXHCyeLP6zcqVtSW.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based out of Singapore, Aelf is a decentralised platform for cloud computing blockchain network, that is trying to develop the operating system exclusively for blockchains. As per the team “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;aelf is planning to be the “Linux system&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;” of the Blockchain, enabling organisations to build their own systems with any consensus mechanism desired on the blockchain. It is a decentralised, self-evolving cloud computing network also capable of cross-chain interaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aelf was recently in the news for initiating the &lt;strong&gt;Aelf Innovation Alliance.&lt;/strong&gt; The main aim behind the initiative is to accelerate blockchain adaptation among the enterprises. Besides Aelf other members of the Innovation Alliance includes Michael Arrington( creator of TechCrunch), Signum Capital(Singapore-based digital fund), FBG Capital (an Asian blockchain hedge fund), Roland Berger(Strategy consultancy company based out of Germany) and Huobi labs( blockchain incubation wing of Huobi). You can read more about the Innovation Alliance &lt;a href="https://medium.com/aelfblockchain/aelf-announced-the-inauguration-of-the-innovation-alliance-38c178f7a69"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/proxy/1*IAqv5ZQ3K5IB5hbWM10aOw.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aelf testnet was officially launched on June 30, 2018. It went on to clock an incredible achievement of 14,968 TPS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/aelfblockchain/aelf-testnet-results-explained-2efd00240837"&gt;Aelf Testnet Results Explained&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aelf’s testnet functionalities offered were&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;💠&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; Multi-node P2P communication&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;💠 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Smart contract&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;💠 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Parallel processing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;💠 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cluster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;💠 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Basic DPOS consensus&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike EOS, Aelf went ahead and made all codes are available on &lt;a href="https://github.com/AElfProject/AElf/wiki"&gt;GitHub &lt;/a&gt;and created a guide to welcome all developers to recreate and improve the testnet. With the support of this documentation, a developer can learn and apply&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to build a local test environment&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to write a contract, publish a contract, execute a contract;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Test data executed in parallel operation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the mainnet launch, the team has planned to implement cross-chain interaction, complete the network economic system, peripheral tools and improve the developer system as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also was keeping the community posted about its progress via its weekly reports on development progress updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/aelfblockchain/development-progress-update-mar-17th-55b96f3a953b"&gt;Development Progress Update (Mar 17th)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike EOS which created a bounty once the flaw was discovered, Aelf went ahead with a developer bounty to improve the testnet and upcoming mainnet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All these were done as part of the collective initiative to pool in more brains and make the testnet foolproof. Aelf has made it quite clear on various occasions that they have followed closely the mainnet launches of projects like EOS, learned where it went wrong and have improved on the launch process to reduce the errors and issues that these projects have suffered. All these are done keeping in mind that they will be having a successful launch and the mainnet will be able to fully support large-scale commercial use helping adaptation of blockchain at an enterprise level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moving a project from a whitepaper to having its own blockchain is no small feat. Since we are in the earlier stage of crypto, these kinds of small setback are bound to happen. What matters is how the new and upcoming projects learn from these setbacks and iterate their process to have a smooth and successful product launch in future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am a community member of Aelf and am passionate about the blockchain. I will not receive any payments for the same as well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Always keep in mind that trading digital assets involves significant risk and can result in the loss of your invested capital. You should take into consideration your level of experience, investment objectives and seek independent financial advice if necessary.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=f857a82b91ad" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/how-to-launch-or-not-launch-a-mainnet-testnet-f857a82b91ad"&gt;How to Launch (or not launch) a Mainnet/Testnet?&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 18:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: A16z-Backed TrustToken Launches Stablecoin Pegged to UK Pound -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/a16z-backed-trusttoken-launches-stablecoin-pegged-to-uk-pound</link><description>Cryptocurrency startup TrustToken has launched its second stablecoin – and this time it's a token pegged 1:1 to the British pound.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Time Magazine business: Bitcoin’s Value Suddenly Surged, But Nobody’s Really Sure Why -  Puntaje: 250.0</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/time/business/~3/Aof2lqu544c/</link><description>The spike came after months of calm in the cryptocurrency world</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Why Binance, the World’s Biggest Crypto Exchange, Is Enthusiastic About Stablecoins -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-binance-the-worlds-biggest-crypto-exchange-is-enthusiastic-about-stablecoins</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yM2U4Mjg0ZWZlOTYzMmU1MDRlNTZjYWNmOTJkMzMzNC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binance, the world’s biggest crypto exchange, is throwing its weight behind stablecoins amid growing speculation that it could trigger mainstream adoption. #SPONSORED&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 13:55:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: BTC Hits $4,800 for the First Time in 2019, Top Crypto Markets See Double Digit Growth -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-hits-4-800-for-the-first-time-in-2019-top-crypto-markets-see-double-digit-growth</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yNGE1NDZjNjBlNmNiNGRiNjQ4ZWQ3OTA4MWZiNjkxZS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin peaked at $4,800 for the first time in 2019 today, while other top coins are all solidly in the green amid significant market growth&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: QuadrigaCX Crypto Exchange Could Soon Be Placed in Bankruptcy -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/quadrigacx-crypto-exchange-could-soon-be-placed-in-bankruptcy</link><description>EY, the court-appointed monitor for QuadrigaCX, is looking to move the exchange into bankruptcy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Bitcoin soars 20%, mystery buyer seen as catalyst -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/bitcoin-soars-20-mystery-buyer-seen-as-catalyst-11404994</link><description>Bitcoin burst to its highest level in almost five months on Tuesday (Apr 2), sending smaller cryptocurrencies up, with analysts ascribing the move to a major order by an anonymous buyer that triggered a frenzy of computer-driven trading.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 19:24:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Bitcoin soars to highest level in 5 months, thanks to mystery buyer -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/international/bitcoin-soars-to-highest-level-in-5-months-thanks-to-mystery-buyer-119040201331_1.html</link><description>Bitcoin surged to near $20,000 in late 2017, the peak of a bubble driven by retail investors that pushed cryptocurrencies onto the agenda of mainstream financial firms</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 23:47:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bitcoin’s Price Rises Above Major Moving Averages In First Since 2018 -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bitcoins-price-rises-above-major-moving-averages-in-first-since-2018</link><description>Bitcoin is now trading above its 50, 100 and 200 day moving averages for the first time in nearly 15 months after the cryptocurrency breached $5,000 during Tuesday's trading session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Malta: Financial Regulator Approves First 14 Crypto Assets Agents -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/malta-financial-regulator-approves-first-14-crypto-assets-agents</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yN2YzZGVkZmIyNjBkYWE0NjUzNGM3OWEwMDM2OWZlYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Malta Financial Services Authority approves first 14 crypto assets agents five months after its Virtual Financial Assets Act came into effect&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:43:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Puerto Rico Sees New Crypto Bank Accept First Client Deposit -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/puerto-rico-sees-new-crypto-bank-accept-first-client-deposit</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80NTBkMjI3ODRkYWE1ZTRkZDU5Y2ZhMGYyZDU3ZGFlOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banking subsidiary of San Juan Mercantile Exchange begins operating following license acquisition&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:27:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>The New York Times Business: Amid Bitcoin Uncertainty, ‘the Smart Money Knows That Crypto Is Not Ready’ -  Puntaje: 875.0</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/02/technology/cryptocurrency-bust-wall-street.html?partner=rss&amp;emc=rss</link><description>Paul Chou, a former Goldman Sachs employee, set up LedgerX, a crytocurrency exchange in Manhattan, to cater to big finance companies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: A New Bank for Crypto Traders Has Opened in Puerto Rico -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/a-new-bank-for-crypto-traders-has-opened-in-puerto-rico</link><description>A new Puerto Rico-based financial institution catering to traders of cryptocurrency has opened for business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Crypto lenders push no-tax perk of leveraging bitcoin for cash -  Puntaje: 2100</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/articles/crypto-lenders-push-no-tax-perk-of-leveraging-bitcoin-for-cash</link><description>Since last fall, when the value of digital money plummeted, lenders have been pushing people who have paper profits to leverage them into cash by borrowing against their cryptocurrencies. And the fact that there's no tax bill on the transactions is a big selling point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Digital Currency Group Data Reveals Turbulent Crypto Investment Landscape -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-currency-group-data-reveals-turbulent-crypto-investment-landscape</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8zMjc5YjczNTdlODgxOTlmMzMwYzU0YzU0MmVjZWNiYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;DCG’s newly-released investment data provides a window into venture capital injections in crypto&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:28:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: The Bitcoin rush seems to be on- FOMO caution advised -  Puntaje: 6600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/the-bitcoin-rush-seems-to-be-on-fomo-caution-advised/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_663195304_optimized-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_663195304_optimized-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_663195304_optimized-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Why did Bitcoin (BTC) rise 20% in value in half an hour is anyone’s guess. But it did today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BTC skidded through three key resistance levels at $4,200, $4,420 and  $4,567 on the way to $5000+.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;many analysts predict could go to as high as $5,500 in the upcoming days, according to CCN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should the FOMO people rush to buy before BTC rises to $10k?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not necessarily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The Bitcoin market and crypto market, in general, continues to be small relative to the rest of the markets -- and emotional,” Jehan Chu, managing partner at blockchain investment and advisory firm Kenetic Capital told Bloomberg.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s still very much subject to waves of enthusiasm. I don’t think today is anything special, other than a temporary enthusiasm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it is exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Say hello to BTC @ $5000&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After hovering around $4,000 for days (even perhaps months), BTC reached a high of $5,106 on Bitfinex – a new all-time high for 2019, according to the Dailyhodl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trading volume has also skyrocketed for BTC, up 125% from $289.5 to $655.2 million on the Real 10 Volumes index over the past week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the last 3 months, BTC swung between $3,217 and $4,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethereum is trading at over $150, up 6.06%. XRP is trading at $0.3323, up 6.77%. Litecoin is trading at $67.42, up 11.17%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crypto hedge fund Tetras Capital outlined bullish reasons why the crypto marketing is suddenly on the move, including ongoing US quantitative easing, baby boomers retiring, the upcoming US election and the Bitcoin halving set to happen in May of 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fundstrat co-founder and head of research Tom Lee said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“... definitely a number of macro factors acting as tailwinds for BTC. Several of which were headwinds in 2018.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Source: Fundstrat, Bloomberg, Coinmarketcap, BitMEX&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sudden jump&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The price of BTC shot up 17% within 30 minutes on Tuesday,  reports Coindesk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Bitcoin’s market capitalization has also risen significantly, up $5.1 billion on the day to $78.8 billion, its highest since Nov. 22, 2018,” said Coindesk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bitcoin price recorded a massive surge from $4,200 to nearly $4,800 within minutes, demonstrating a 20% gain in a short time frame, according to CCN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Earlier this week, economist and global markets analyst Alex Krüger said that a price movement of bitcoin above the $4,200 level will mark the end of the bear trend beginning January 2018, lasting 16 months,” said CCN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BTC wait &amp;amp; see?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BTC has lead a surge in virtual currencies and ended 3 months of calm in the $160 billion market, according to Bloomberg&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Traders struggled to pinpoint a reason for the rally, which briefly lifted Bitcoin above $5,000 and increased the value of digital assets tracked by CoinMarketCap.com by about $17 billion in less than an hour, says Bloomberg.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“While sudden swings in Bitcoin are nothing new, price action in the virtual currency has been relatively subdued this year as investors weighed the prospects for more mainstream adoption after last year’s 74% crash.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big buy or sell orders in Bitcoin can often lead to outsized moves while trend-following individual investors can also exacerbate volatility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s FOMO vs WNC (wait &amp;amp; see). Which side are you on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/the-bitcoin-rush-seems-to-be-on-fomo-caution-advised/"&gt;The Bitcoin rush seems to be on- FOMO caution advised&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 08:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Naked Security: Government spyware hidden in Google Play store apps -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2019/04/02/government-spyware-hidden-in-google-play-store-apps/</link><description>The malware, dubbed Exodus, records and steals all manner of data and leaves phones vulnerable to further hacking and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 13:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Krebs on Security: Canadian Police Raid ‘Orcus RAT’ Author -  Puntaje: 500.0</title><link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2019/04/canadian-police-raid-orcus-rat-author/</link><description>Canadian police last week raided the residence of a Toronto software developer responsible for authoring and selling “Orcus RAT,” a software product that’s been marketed on underground forums and used in countless malware attacks since its creation in 2015. Its author maintains Orcus is a legitimate Remote Administration Tool that is merely being abused, but security experts say it includes multiple features more typically seen in malware known as a Remote Access Trojan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Analyzing AZORult malware using NSA Ghidra suite -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83211/breaking-news/azorult-nsa-ghidra.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Cybaze-Yoroi ZLAB malware researchers decided to use the NSA Ghidra suite in a real case study, the analysis of the AZORult malware. Introduction One of the most expected moments in the infosec community during the last few months was, with no doubt, the Ghidra public release. On the 5th of March, at the RSA conference, [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83211/breaking-news/azorult-nsa-ghidra.html"&gt;Analyzing AZORult malware using NSA Ghidra suite&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC technology: Network security market shows its highest growth in more than 6 years: BofA -  Puntaje: 1000.0</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/02/network-security-market-showing-highest-growth-since-2012.html</link><description>Companies are increasing spending on more traditional cybersecurity methods, spurring growth in the market for network security.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: The Rise of The Gig Economy: How Electronic Payments Can Help Pt. 2 -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16959/the-rise-of-the-gig-economy-how-electronic-payments-can-help-pt-2?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>In part 1 of our series on The Rise of the Gig Economy, we showed you how on-demand workers, short-t...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Jet Airways grounds 15 more planes due to non-payment of rentals to lessors -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/jet-airways-grounds-15-more-planes-due-to-non-payment-of-rentals-to-lessors-119040201033_1.html</link><description>Last week, Jet Airways had informed the government it has 35 aircraft in operations</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 20:28:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: New Fintech Unicorn Bill.com Teams with Mastercard to Offer Virtual Card -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/04/bill-com-latest-fintech-unicorn-after-88-million-round/</link><description>Bill.com, a business payments and software platform firm, today announced an $88 million funding round led by Franklin Templeton that makes it the latest fintech unicorn. The Palo Alto, Calif.-based firm also announced plans to offer Mastercard virtual cards as part of the Bill.com automated accounts payable solution for small and midsize businesses. The company [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Coinbase Expands Into Cross-Border Payments -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-expands-into-cross-border-payments</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8wMmU0ZTljMTY3NWQ4OWIxYjA5NWY4MGUxNDczZWRhZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major American cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has expanded into cross-border payments&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:20:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Pakistan’s Central Bank Aims to Issue Its Own Digital Currency by 2025 -  Puntaje: 1100</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pakistans-central-bank-aims-to-issue-its-own-digital-currency-by-2025</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80NWE0MjY3Y2YyNTZlMjU4NDc2MWVhOGE0MTJkZDQxZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jameel Ahmad, the deputy governor of the State Bank of Pakistan, declared that the institution aims to issue a digital currency by 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:50:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Pakistan Central Bank Eyes Digital Currency Launch by 2025 -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/pakistan-central-bank-eyes-digital-currency-launch-by-2025</link><description>The State Bank of Pakistan, the country’s central bank, is reportedly considering launching a digital currency as part of a modernization drive.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: DLT ready to drive widespread disruption in cross-border payments -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33622/dlt-ready-to-drive-widespread-disruption-in-cross-border-payments?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The cross-border payments industry is "ripe for disruption', with distributed ledger technologies le...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Open Banking Transformation and Disruption - the expectation of Open Banking in 2019 -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/featurearticle/2387/open-banking-transformation-and-disruption---the-expectation-of-open-banking-in-2019?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Join this latest webinar from Finextra in association with Equinix on 02 May 2019 at 15:00 UK time a...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Ensemble Capital chooses Numerix Oneview Asset Management -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77887/ensemble-capital-chooses-numerix-oneview-asset-management?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Ensemble Capital, the absolute return global AI fund based in Singapore, is live with Numerix’s Onev...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Google’s anti-trans controversy is the latest case of big tech overcorrecting to the right -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/cm8AeA15Ohc/</link><description>Google just smoothed over one spat with the LGBT community, but it&amp;#8217;s already well into the next one. Last week, in an effort to monitor the ethical development of artificial intelligence and presumably to assuage public concern, Google launched an eight person advisory group dedicated to the task. Controversially, Google included Heritage Foundation President Kay [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Morris Garages demonstrates connectivity features of upcoming MG Hector SUV -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/automobile/morris-garages-demonstrates-connectivity-features-of-upcoming-mg-hector-suv-119040200686_1.html</link><description>MG hector will come equipped with on-board internet connectivity, AI-powered voice assist and a host of pre-loaded apps stacked in a 10.4-inch touchscreen infotainment system</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:57:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Tencent Co-Founder Backs Singaporean Fintech Startup to the Tune of SG$2.7 Mil -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29852/remittance/koku-singapore-remittance-fx-tencent/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Koku is a foreign exchange fintech that is based in Singapore. And it just raised US$2 million (approximately SG$2.7 million) in a Pre-Series A funding round led by Jason Zeng, co-founder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29852/remittance/koku-singapore-remittance-fx-tencent/"&gt;Tencent Co-Founder Backs Singaporean Fintech Startup to the Tune of SG$2.7 Mil&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 04:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Tinkoff Bank builds supercomputer -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77888/tinkoff-bank-builds-supercomputer?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Tinkoff Group built its own supercomputer in line with its AI First strategy and ambition to develop...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Blend seeks to deepen bank ties with account opening product -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/blend-seeks-to-deepen-bank-ties-with-account-opening-product</link><description>The loan origination fintech is offering the product in a stand-alone format and as part of the workflow for its mortgage and home equity loan products.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 17:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Singapore’s Investment Management Association Announces a New Chairperson -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29889/roboadvisor/singapores-investment-management-association-announces-a-new-chairman/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Investment Management Association of Singapore (IMAS) today announced that it has appointed Susan Soh, CEO Singapore, Schroders, as its new Chair of the IMAS Executive Committee. The IMAS Executive&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29889/roboadvisor/singapores-investment-management-association-announces-a-new-chairman/"&gt;Singapore&amp;#8217;s Investment Management Association Announces a New Chairperson&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 11:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: Movers and Shakers: Notable March Hires in Fintech and Banking -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/04/movers-and-shakers-notable-march-hires-in-fintech-and-banking/</link><description>Goldman Sachs recently announced plans to hire more women and people of color. The bank wants to increase its representation in entry-level analysts and associates in the Americas to 50% for women, 11% for black employees and 14% for Latino employees, based on an email to employees from CEO David Solomon, President John Waldron and [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: South Africa's TymeBank picks Finn AI for digital financial fitness coach -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33626/south-africas-tymebank-picks-finn-ai-for-digital-financial-fitness-coach?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>South African digital lender TymeBank has enlisted the help of artificial intelligence-powered conve...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Top IoT, AI and Robotics Books -  Puntaje: 6000</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/22282/iot/top-iot-ai-and-robotics-books/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The proliferation of Internet of Things (IoT) technology across consumer products, enterprises and public service fueled by artificial intelligence, machine learning and big data is often said to bring about&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/22282/iot/top-iot-ai-and-robotics-books/"&gt;Top IoT, AI and Robotics Books&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 08:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IBM Banking Industry: Succeeding in the future of payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.ibm.com/blogs/insights-on-business/banking/succeeding-in-the-future-of-payments/</link><description>Embracing the future in the age of instant gratification The payments industry is at an inflection point. Customers increasingly demand new payment options like real-time payments and P2P payments, underpinned by security and trust. The costs of running payments operations, complying with a myriad of regulations and enforcing payments standards are increasing. Exposure to operational [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: A Primer for Fintech’s Biggest Event this Spring -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://finovate.com/a-primer-for-fintechs-biggest-event-this-spring/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In just over a month we&amp;#8217;ll be on the ground in San Francisco making last minute preparations for one of the year&amp;#8217;s biggest events in the fintech sector, FinovateSpring. The main event will take place May 8 through 10 at the Hilton San Francisco Union Square. This year, there is an option to add to &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/a-primer-for-fintechs-biggest-event-this-spring/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/a-primer-for-fintechs-biggest-event-this-spring/"&gt;A Primer for Fintech&amp;#8217;s Biggest Event this Spring&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Address the FinovateSpring audience by taking part in FinTech Futures supplement -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/address-the-finovatespring-audience-by-taking-part-in-fintech-futures-supplement/</link><description>Deliver a strong message to the fintech community!</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Big Tech: Intel Capital throws £89m at cloud gaming, AI, communications -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/bit-tech/all/~3/BzNn15pNASI/</link><description>Plus a company promising cheaper chips.&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/bit-tech/all/~4/BzNn15pNASI" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Exchange Volumes May Be Fake, But Bitcoin’s Value Is Real -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/exchange-volumes-may-be-fake-but-bitcoins-value-is-real</link><description>More than a critique of price manipulation rife across bitcoin markets, the Bitwise report shows cryptocurrencies' potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 04:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Ernst &amp; Young Argues That Crypto Exchange QuadrigaCX Should Be Placed in Bankruptcy -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ernst-young-argues-that-crypto-exchange-quadrigacx-should-be-placed-in-bankruptcy</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jNjNmNGRiMGU5YzdiMzlhY2U1MjYyN2NjZDUxMDMwNC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ernst &amp; Young has argued that the now-defunct Canadian crypto exchange QuadrigaCX should be placed in bankruptcy rather than undergo a restructuring process&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 20:05:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: BC Group Unveils Insured Custody Offering for Asia-Based Crypto Investors -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bc-group-unveils-insured-custody-offering-for-asia-based-crypto-investors</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83MzE0YzUyODhkMWY3MTdlOGE1YTE3OTE5NDE0ODkyYi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latest crypto custody offering debuts from Hong Kong’s BC Group&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:44:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: How Crypto Is Taxed in the US: A Taxpayer’s Dilemma -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-crypto-is-taxed-in-the-us-a-taxpayers-dilemma</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81NThmYmNmZTBjMzdiMjEwYTk2N2M2ODllMDhiNjJmZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facing the deadline to report their taxes by April 15, 2019, United States individual taxpayers may wonder what their U.S. tax reporting obligations are for crypto&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:10:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Alcatraz AI is building Face ID for corporate badges -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/ehOinirb5dY/</link><description>Meet Alcatraz AI, a startup that wants to replace all the bade readers in your office with a Face ID-like camera system. Alcatraz has integrated multiple sensors to identify faces and unlock doors effortlessly. If you think about it, it’s weird that fingerprint sensors took off on mobile but everybody is still using plastic badges [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Major Swiss Stock Exchange SIX Lists XRP Exchange Traded Product -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/major-swiss-stock-exchange-six-lists-xrp-exchange-traded-product</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83YzhmMTY1OTIyMTRkODNhZGM3NzlkZWI0NjNlYTYyYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Ripple-based Exchange Traded Product dubbed Amun Ripple XRP (AXRP) has been listed on major Swiss stock exchange SIX&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 11:05:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Computer systems in the City of Albany hit in Ransomware Attack -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83187/cyber-crime/city-albany-ransomware-attack.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Another ransomware attack made the headlines, this time the victim is the City of Albany, its computer systems were infected with the malware. Computer systems in the City of Albany, New York, were infected with ransomware over the weekend that disrupted some municipal computers. According to Albany Mayor Kathy Sheehan, no personal information belonging to [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83187/cyber-crime/city-albany-ransomware-attack.html"&gt;Computer systems in the City of Albany hit in Ransomware Attack&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 07:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: XRP Exchange-Traded Product Goes Live on Swiss SIX Exchange -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/xrp-exchange-traded-product-goes-live-on-swiss-six-exchange</link><description>An exchange-traded product (ETP) tracking the price of the XRP cryptocurrency has gone live on Switzerland’s primary stock exchange SIX.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 07:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Threatpost: Mobile-First Phishing Kit Targets Verizon Customers -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://threatpost.com/mobile-phishing-targets-verizon/143366/</link><description>The kit's authors demonstrate a knowledge of Verizon's infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: BREAKING: new update about DDoS’er Linux/DDoSMan ELF malware based on Elknot -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83157/malware/new-linux-ddosman-threat-emerged-from-an-evolution-of-the-older-elknot.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The popular expert unixfreaxjp analyzed a new China ELF DDoS&amp;#8217;er malware tracked as &amp;#8220;Linux/DDoSMan&amp;#8221; that evolves from the Elknot malware to deliver new ELF bot. Non-Technical-Premise “This report is meant for incident response or Linux forensics purpose, TO HELP admin &amp;#38; IR folks”, with this the very beginning sentence starts the new analysis of one [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83157/malware/new-linux-ddosman-threat-emerged-from-an-evolution-of-the-older-elknot.html"&gt;BREAKING: new update about DDoS&amp;#8217;er Linux/DDoSMan ELF malware based on Elknot&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 08:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: ARTEÏA launches Token Sale for P2P Art Market Blockchain Platform -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/arteia-launches-a-p2p-blockchain-platform-for-art-market/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/arteia-launches-a-p2p-blockchain-platform-for-art-market/"&gt;ARTEÏA launches Token Sale for P2P Art Market Blockchain Platform&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/arteia2-150x150.png" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="32358" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/arteia-launches-a-p2p-blockchain-platform-for-art-market/arteia2/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/arteia2.png" data-orig-size="1818,784" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="arteia2" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/arteia2-300x129.png" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/arteia2-1024x442.png" /&gt;Blockchain company Arteïa has announced the launch of its Initial Coin Offering (ICO) and is offering the first comprehensive, advanced technology platform set to empower art collectors by linking a collection management system to a matching platform supported by a provenance tracker. &amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;ve raised €3 million already since the creation of the company to develop [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/02/arteia-launches-a-p2p-blockchain-platform-for-art-market/"&gt;ARTEÏA launches Token Sale for P2P Art Market Blockchain Platform&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 08:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: 10 FinTech Startups in Mexico Worth Your Attention -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://gomedici.com/10-fintech-startups-mexico-worth-your-attention/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/10-fintech-startups-mexico-worth-your-attention.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;Since the start of 2018, Mexico’s financial regulators have adopted a progressive approach towards financial inclusion and policymakers are looking at FinTech startups &amp;amp;amp; banks to help them. In January 2019, Mexico unveiled new measures to boost financial inclusion and promote new payments platforms for mobile devices. In 2018 alone, over 130 FinTechs were founded in Mexico. Overall, Payments &amp;amp;amp; Remittances, Lending, and Enterprise Financial Management are the hottest segments in terms of the number of startups. Here is a list of 10 well-funded FinTech startups in Mexico: PayClip was founded in 2012 and has raised $42.3 million in total funding. PayClip enables merchants to accept payments on their smartphone or tablet using the Clip card reader. The company offers a portable card reader that fits into the headphone socket of smartphones and tablets. PayClip was formerly known as BlitzPay, Inc. Konfio was founded in 2013 and has raised $43...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 15:49:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: UAE workforce optimistic about AI inclusion at workplace -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/it-2/uae-workforce-optimistic-about-ai-inclusion-at-workplace/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1063998056_optimized-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1063998056_optimized-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_1063998056_optimized-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;A UAE survey by Citrix shines a light on the optimism of local workforce has when it comes to AI and robotics in the workplace, with 45% indicating a positive outcome within the next 5 years and 55% indicating both positive and negative effects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked about the biggest benefit of AI within the workplace, 47% said it will help them perform very complex tasks, while nearly 35% of workers said AI and robotics will help them become free from the most repetitive tasks, while&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is evident that the UAE workforce believes the outlook of AI and robotics within the workplace is a positive one. This is a green light for technology companies to continue to adapt and evolve our solutions that will aid in this transformation,” said Ali Kaddoura, UAE Country Manager at Citrix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across the UAE, Dubai and the youngest generation of workers showed more enthusiasm when it comes to the positive impact of integrating AI and robot at the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence is also a source of concern with 50% of the respondents fearing its propagation will lead to a loss of jobs. Despite this worry, a mere 2.8% of workers said AI and robots will negatively affect their jobs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, AI is not seen as a panacea. While nearly 30% of knowledge workers wish to be equipped with superhuman intelligence as a superpower, they primarily wish for developing their creativity at work. This is the number one skill (44%) respondents would like to acquire within the next five years and the number one soft skill companies need the most in 2019 according to LinkedIn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The rise of AI and robotics in the workplace will allow creativity to become increasingly important as it is precisely one of the skills machines can’t automate. The Citrix survey makes clear that UAE workers are as excited as we are for the emerging use of AI and robotics within the workplace. As the workplace becomes more and more intelligent, people and organizations can unlock innovation, engage customers, and be productive. Citrix is here to help develop the technology workers need to drive business forward,” said Kaddoura.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Citrix survey, carried about by Onepoll, includes responses from over 500 working professionals across all seven emirates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/it-2/uae-workforce-optimistic-about-ai-inclusion-at-workplace/"&gt;UAE workforce optimistic about AI inclusion at workplace&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : Privacy &amp; Regulatory Considerations in Enterprise Blockchain -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/privacy-and-regulatory-considerations-in-enterprise-blockchain-/a/d-id/1334277?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>People who understand information governance, privacy, and security should be active participants on the distributed ledger technology implementation team to ensure success.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:30:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: When the Price of Bitcoin Rises -  Puntaje: 2400</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/when-the-price-of-bitcoin-rises-1f2fd052beac?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*WaBINFcwlQ8u6liYlLGxrg.png" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is a very new technology, even though the concept that it brings to life is decades old. The double spending problem has been solved; this means that it is possible to use a digital certificate to stand in the place of money and be sure that no one else can spend that certificate other than you as long as you hold it. This is an unprecedented paradigm shift, the implications of which are not yet fully understood, and for which the tools do not yet exist to fully take advantage of this new idea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This new technology requires some new thinking when it comes to developing businesses that are built upon it. In the same way that the pioneer providers of email did not correctly understand the service they were selling for many years, new and correct thinking about Bitcoin is needed, and will emerge, so that it reaches its full potential and becomes ubiquitous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/728/1*To2c6CVvqYgoVz9yg2B-tA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The original Hotmail Interface&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hotmail used familiar technologies (the browser, email) to create a better way of accessing and delivering email; the idea of using an email client like Outlook Express has been superseded by web interfaces and email ‘in the cloud’ that provides many advantages over a dedicated client with your mail in your own local storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin, which will transform the way you transfer money, needs to be understood on its own terms, and not just as an online form of money. Thinking about Bitcoin as money is as absurd as thinking about email as another form of sending letters by post; one not only replaces the other but it profoundly changes the way people send and consume messages. It is not a simple substitution or one dimensional improvement of an existing idea or service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I have explained previously, &lt;a href="http://irdial.com/blogdial/?p=3135"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin is not money&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Bitcoin is &lt;a href="http://irdial.com/blogdial/?p=3166"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a protocol&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. If you treat it in this way, with the correct assumptions, you can start the process of putting Bitcoin in a proper context, allowing you to make rational suggestions about the sort of services that might be profitable based on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/571/1*HYfcq-NmVEFAfaQukvUzDA.png" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Every part of Bitcoin is text. It is always text, and never at any point ceases to be text. This is a fact, and as text, it is protected under the free speech provisions of the constitutions of civilized nations with guaranteed, irrevocable rights.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Bitcoin is a protocol and not money, then setting up currency exchanges that mimic real world money, stock and commodity exchanges to trade in is not the sole means of discovering its price. You would not set up an email exchange to discover the value of email services, and the same thing applies to Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Staying with this train of thought, when you type in an email on your Gmail account, you are inputting your ‘letter’. You press send, it goes through your ISP, over the internets, into the ISP of your recipient and then it is outputted on your recipient’s machine. The same is true of Bitcoin; you input money on one end through a service and then send the Bitcoin to your recipient, without an intermediary to handle the transfer. Once Bitcoin does its job of moving your &lt;a href="http://www.weusecoins.com/globe-Bitcoin/"&gt;value across the globe&lt;/a&gt; to its recipient it needs to be ‘read out’, i.e. turned &lt;em&gt;back into money&lt;/em&gt;, in the same way that your letter is displayed to its recipient in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the email scenario, once the transfer happens and the email you have received conveys its information to you, it has no use other than to be a record of the information that was sent (accounting), and you archive that information. Bitcoin does this accounting on the block chain for you, and a good service built on it will store extended transaction details for you locally, but what you need to have as the recipient of Bitcoin is &lt;em&gt;services &lt;/em&gt;or &lt;em&gt;goods &lt;/em&gt;not Bitcoin itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin’s true nature is as an instant way to pay (despite not being money) anywhere in the world. It is not an investment, and holding onto it in the hopes that it will become valuable is like holding on to an email or a PDF in the hopes it will become valuable in the future; it doesn’t make any sense. Of course, you &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; hold onto Bitcoin and watch its value go up, and its value &lt;em&gt;will &lt;/em&gt;go up, but you need to have guts to weather the violent waves of selling and buying as the transition to an all Bitcoin economy gets under way. Remember also that businesses that have a need to store Bitcoin need to be concerned about its value if their models are open-ended and are exposed to the market. “Closed Circuit Bitcoin” models have control over everything and never need to worry about prices at exchanges. They can do all their business moving an unlimited amount of fiat with just a few Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the fact that you can’t double spend them and each one is unique, Bitcoins have no inherent value, unlike a book or any physical object. They cannot appreciate in value. Mistaken thinking about Bitcoin has spread because &lt;em&gt;it behaves like money&lt;/em&gt;, due to the fact it cannot be double spent. Misrepresentation of Bitcoin’s true nature has masked Bitcoin’s dual nature of being digital and not double-spendable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/640/1*AJ7a1SivFZAWl83KivqRXQ.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Razzles. They start as a candy, and then end as a gum. Before you chew them, which are they? A candy, or a gum?&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is digital, with all the qualities of information that make information non scarce. It sits in a new place that oscillates between the goods of the physical world and the infinitely abundant digital world of information, belonging exclusively to the digital world but having the characteristics of both. This is why it has been widely misunderstood and why a new approach is needed to design businesses around it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this goes some way to explain why the price of buying Bitcoins at the exchanges &lt;strong&gt;doesn’t matter for the consumer. &lt;/strong&gt;If the cost of buying a Bitcoin goes to 1¢ This doesn’t change the amount of money that comes out at the other end of a transfer. As long as you redeem your Bitcoin immediately after the transfer into either goods or currency, the same value comes out at the other end no matter what you paid for the Bitcoin when you started the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think about it this way. Let us suppose that you want to send a long text file to another person. You can either send it as it is, or you can compress it with zip. The size of a document file when it is zipped can be &lt;a href="http://file-compression-software-review.toptenreviews.com/file-compression-software-compression-test.html"&gt;up to 87% smaller&lt;/a&gt; than the original. When we transpose this idea to Bitcoin, the compression ratio is the price of Bitcoin at an exchange. If a Bitcoin is $100, and you want to buy something from someone in India for $100 you need to buy 1 Bitcoin to get that $100 to India. If the price of Bitcoin is 1¢ then you need 10,000 Bitcoin to send $100 dollars to India. These would be expressed as compression ratios of 1:1 and 10,000:1, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same $100 value is sent to India, whether you use 10,000 or 1 Bitcoin.The price of Bitcoins &lt;em&gt;is irrelevant to the value that is being transmitted&lt;/em&gt;, in the same way that zip files do not ‘care’ what is inside them; Bitcoin and zip are dumb protocols that do a job. As long as the value of Bitcoins does not go to zero, it will have the same utility as if the value were very ‘high’.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearing all of this in mind, it’s clear that &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@beautyon_/azteco-bitcoin-for-the-masses-fc17f8ca1df0"&gt;new services to facilitate the rapid, frictionless conversion into&lt;/a&gt; and out of Bitcoin are needed to allow it to function in a manner that is true to its nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current business models of exchanges are not addressing Bitcoin’s nature correctly. They are using the Twentieth Century model of stock, commodity and currency exchanges and superimposing this onto Bitcoin. Interfacing with these exchanges is non-trivial, and for the ordinary user, a daunting prospect. In some cases, you have to wait up to seven days to receive a transfer of your fiat currency after it has been cashed out of your account from Bitcoins. Whilst this is not a fault of the exchanges, it represents a very real impediment to Bitcoin acting in its nature and providing its complete value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine this: you receive an email from across the world, and are notified of the fact by being displayed the subject line in your browser. You then &lt;em&gt;apply &lt;/em&gt;to your ISP to have this email delivered to you, and you have to wait seven days for it to arrive in your physical mail box.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/450/1*eXMvyss76on3zAD1hsX_Ig.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The very idea is completely absurd, and yet, this is exactly what is happening with Bitcoin, for no technical reason whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is clear that there needs to be a re-think of the services that are growing around Bitcoin, along with a re-think of what the true nature of Bitcoin is. Rethinking services is a normal part of entrepreneurialism and we should expect business models to fail and early entrants to fall by the wayside as the ceaseless iterations and pivoting progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearing all of this in mind, focussing on the price of Bitcoin at exchanges using a business model that is inappropriate for this new software simply is not rational; its like putting a methane-breathing canary in a mine full of oxygen breathing humans as a detector. The bird dies even though nothing is wrong with the air; the miners rush to evacuate, leaving the exposed gold seams behind, thinking that they are all about to be wiped out, when all is actually fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/736/1*VwFksGcOdGffKLr5Jevo2w.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Day traders speculating on Bitcoin from home cause the price to oscillate. It’s an artificial signal that has nothing to do with demand for Bitcoin and its circulation as an economic tool to facilitate commerce.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin, and the ideas behind it are here to stay. As the number of people downloading the client and using it increases, like Hotmail, it will eventually reach critical mass and then spread exponentially through the internet. When that happens, the correct business models will spontaneously emerge, as they will become obvious, in the same way that Hotmail, Gmail, Facebook, cellular phones and instant messaging seem like second nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the future, I imagine that very few people will speculate on the value of Bitcoin, because even though that might be possible, and even profitable, there will be more money to be made in providing easy-to-use Bitcoin services that take full advantages of what Bitcoin is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing is for sure: speed will be of the essence in any future Bitcoin business model. The startups that provide instant satisfaction on both ends of the transaction are the ones that are going to succeed. Even though the volatility of the price of Bitcoin is bound to stabilise, since it has no use in and of itself, getting back to money or goods instantly will be a sought after characteristic of any business built on Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The needs of Bitcoin businesses provide many challenges in terms of performance, security and new thinking. Out of these challenges will come new practices and software that we can only just imagine as they come over the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, when there is no more fiat, and &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/bitcoin-adoption-and-conway-s-game-of-life-54ca71db7b88"&gt;the chaotic transition zone between fiat and Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt; has been abolished, then everything will be priced in Bitcoin, and there will be no volatility, because no one uses anything other than Bitcoin to buy or sell. If you know any chemistry, this will be like a reaction’s reagents reaching equilibrium. You can shake it and stir it all you like; the reaction is over, and you’re left with the inert reaction products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now, compared to the amount of fiat in the world, Bitcoin can expand and contract very rapidly over a large range, because it is small in volume. It can expand to what for many is an unimaginably high price, and then shrink down again. As it gets bigger and accumulates more mass (its price expressed in fiat), these fluctuations will become smaller and smaller. Through all of this, Bitcoin remains exactly the same; it is its users that are publishing numbers as a signal to react upon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you like the content and feel so obliged to send some love via BTC donations you can do so at the address below:↴&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/200/0*QoOh0IUIWgzJijdR" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.blockchain.com/btc/address/3PCqP6ajCfUXiyyZC4f2z4gVXu3dz698YX"&gt;3PCqP6ajCfUXiyyZC4f2z4gVXu3dz698YX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=1f2fd052beac" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/when-the-price-of-bitcoin-rises-1f2fd052beac"&gt;When the Price of Bitcoin Rises&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>