<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:12:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tech Crunch: Enterprise blockchain startup Offchain Labs scores $3.7M seed round -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/TdXIimB8kac/</link><description>Two of the issues limiting blockchain adoption in the enterprise has been lack of scalability and privacy. Offchain Labs, a startup that spun out of research at Princeton, wants to help create more scalable smart contracts while shifting part of the process off of the public blockchain to increase privacy. Today, the company announced a [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: PayPal invests in potential collaboration with Cambridge Blockchain -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/paypal-invests-in-potential-collaboration-with-cambridge-blockchain/</link><description>The funding is an extension of the firm's Series A round.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: How Blockchain May Help the Cobalt in Smartphones and Electric Cars Be Ethically Sourced -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-blockchain-may-help-the-cobalt-in-smartphones-and-electric-cars-be-ethically-sourced</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lYTRmNWIzYTNhZWU4N2I5OTZhNTRjODFlNzg5YTdiMC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smartphones and electric cars rely on natural resources, but they are not always ethically sourced. A blockchain-driven mining project is vowing to change this #SPONSORED&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Former Obama Tech Officer Raises $3.7 Million for Blockchain SaaS Startup -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/former-obama-tech-officer-raises-3-7-million-for-blockchain-saas-startup</link><description>Led by former Obama White House Deputy CTO Ed Felton, Offchain Labs is the latest startup vying for enterprise clients.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Chinese Regulator Approves First 197 Blockchain Firms, Including Tencent, Alibaba, Baidu -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/chinese-regulator-approves-first-197-blockchain-firms-including-tencent-alibaba-baidu</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8yNzY0NmViZTYzODYwNzI1MmY2N2IyMzUyNmM3NDA0OS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first list of blockchain service providers registered in China — 197 companies long —  has been released by China’s cyberspace administration&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 11:48:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Minersinc Brings To India The Best Of World Cinema, Curates 200+ Critically Acclaimed Titles For Cinema Enthusiasts -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/03/minersinc-brings-to-india-the-best-of-world-cinema-curates-200-critically-acclaimed-titles-for-cinema-enthusiasts/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/03/minersinc-brings-to-india-the-best-of-world-cinema-curates-200-critically-acclaimed-titles-for-cinema-enthusiasts/"&gt;Minersinc Brings To India The Best Of World Cinema, Curates 200+ Critically Acclaimed Titles For Cinema Enthusiasts&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/minerinc2-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="32366" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/03/minersinc-brings-to-india-the-best-of-world-cinema-curates-200-critically-acclaimed-titles-for-cinema-enthusiasts/minerinc2/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/minerinc2.jpg" data-orig-size="1400,425" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="minerinc2" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/minerinc2-300x91.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/minerinc2-1024x311.jpg" /&gt;India’s first blockchain powered entertainment ecosystem MinersINC,, is about to launch its curated VOD service called ‘myNK’ which features an eclectic collection of films, documentaries and series. While India is undoubtedly a vast and film-crazy nation, the country’s cinephiles have been increasingly seeking out films from beyond just Hollywood and Bollywood. Wendy Bernfeld MD of [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/04/03/minersinc-brings-to-india-the-best-of-world-cinema-curates-200-critically-acclaimed-titles-for-cinema-enthusiasts/"&gt;Minersinc Brings To India The Best Of World Cinema, Curates 200+ Critically Acclaimed Titles For Cinema Enthusiasts&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 12:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: 61% of Major Global Digital Firms Invest in Blockchain, Report Finds -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/61-of-major-global-digital-firms-invest-in-blockchain-report-finds</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8wNTg0ZDAzM2M2NDI2ZTYwM2QwOTRmMzE1ZWY0NGVkNi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;61 percent of high-profile digital companies worldwide are investing in blockchain, according to a new Okta report&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:15:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Cybersecurity, Blockchain Firm WISeKey Acquires Interest in Data Infrastructure Firm -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cybersecurity-blockchain-firm-wisekey-acquires-interest-in-data-infrastructure-firm</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jYTE5ZWI0YzlmNTYyNTIwNGZkZTgyYTA3MTc4ZmFlYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Switzerland-based blockchain, IoT and cybersecurity firm WISeKey has acquired a 22% interest in U.S. data infrastructure firm Tarmin through a multi-million USD transaction&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 11:05:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Business: 'Anybody's guess': Bitcoin's sudden surge leaves experts baffled -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/markets/anybody-s-guess-bitcoin-s-sudden-surge-leaves-experts-baffled-20190403-p51a5m.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_business</link><description>After three months of relative calm, cryptocurrencies have sprung back to life, leaving traders scratching their heads.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 05:43:51 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: 3 Reasons Bitcon’s Price Suddenly Surged Back to $5K -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/these-3-factors-were-likely-behind-bitcoins-price-surge-to-5k</link><description>The cryptocurrency market sprang back to life with bitcoin's surge to 4.5-month highs yesterday. But why?</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 11:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC technology: Major cryptocurrencies are soaring after bitcoin made its first big jump in months -  Puntaje: 375.0</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/03/other-major-cryptocurrencies-move-following-bitcoins-jump.html</link><description>Hot on the heels of bitcoin surging to multi-month highs, other major cryptocurrencies are also posting strong moves upward.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Andreessen Horowitz Shifts Business Model From VC To RIA -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/cryptocurrency/2019/andreessen-horowitz-business-model-vc-ria/</link><description>Andreessen Horowitz has revealed that it is transitioning from being a venture capital (VC) firm to a registered investment advisor (RIA). The firm filed last month to become an RIA so that it can have more flexibility in its investments, particularly in the area of cryptocurrencies, said Margit Wennmachers, an operating partner at the firm, according to […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Bitcoin Trading Losing Its Luster Among Wall Street Heavy Hitters -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/blockchain/bitcoin/2019/bitcoin-trading-wall-street/</link><description>In the wake of the crash in bitcoin last year, institutional players that had big plans for the cryptocurrency market are reigning in those efforts. According to a report in The New York Times citing sources who requested anonymity, the likes of Goldman Sachs, the New York Stock Exchange and the Chicago Board of Options Exchange are […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 11:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Crypto exchange Liquid says it is now valued at over $1 billion following new investment -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/qbU0VtHZCQc/</link><description>Crypto has a new unicorn after exchange Liquid announced today it has raised capital from investors at a valuation of more than $1 billion as it goes after expansion opportunities. The company said the capital will be put to work expanding into new markets and offering new services, including &amp;#8212; potentially &amp;#8212; a platform for [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japan: Crypto Trading Platform Liquid Hits Unicorn Status With Over $1 Billion Valuation -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japan-crypto-trading-platform-liquid-hits-unicorn-status-with-over-1-billion-valuation</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9hNTE4ZTk5MzVhMjczNDFhNGFiZGE5OTY3M2I1YTIxOS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese crypto trading platform Liquid has hit unicorn status with the first close of an ongoing Series C funding that puts the company valuation at over $1 billion&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:11:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Liquid.com Closes Funding Round Valuing Crypto Firm at ‘Over $1 Billion’ -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/liquid-com-closes-funding-round-valuing-crypto-firm-at-over-1-billion</link><description>Crypto trading platform Liquid.com has been backed by Bitmain and IDG Capital in a funding round it says makes it the latest crypto unicorn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Market Rally Continues With Bitcoin Above $4,900, Tech Stocks Bounce Back -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-market-rally-continues-with-bitcoin-above-4-900-tech-stocks-bounce-back</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xY2VjZjVjY2UwYzUyYTZiMDRkYjNiYjIyMGFhM2Y1Ni5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of the top-20 cryptocurrencies continue seeing solid gains, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average slumped for the first time in four sessions today&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 01:35:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackernoon: Why Unveiling Fake Volume is Essential for Market Growth -  Puntaje: 12800</title><link>https://hackernoon.com/why-unveiling-fake-volume-is-essential-for-market-growth-f20279b1ad8b?source=rss----3a8144eabfe3---4</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The market is under fire the last few days as the general public have finally realized that a major chunk of liquidity on exchanges does not actually exist. This has been taken as a negative for cryptocurrency growth and adoption, but I guess someone forgot to tell Bitcoin’s price action!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a primer, Bitwise Asset Management gave a presentation to the SEC where they showed the officials how crypto volume is manipulated. While I don’t agree with their investment philosophy or financial products, Bitwise’ presentation was perfectly summed up and contained useful data that everybody needs to see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe this is being perceived incorrectly. Maybe this is actually excellent for cryptocurrencies. Most of the world sees cryptocurrency as ‘fake internet money’. That perception is likely to worsen in the short term due to reports like these — given those people are even paying attention. But what does this mean for long term developments?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A brief look into how volume was faked reveals a manipulation tactic called ‘wash trading’. Wash trading is a known evil, especially in crypto. It is when a single account or entity simultaneously issues buy and sell orders on an exchange. They sell their cryptocurrency (minor market downturn occurs) and then buy it back (at the lower price; creates a tiny surge). This volume shouldn’t be considered as it doesn’t represent real demand, supply, or trading. It is simply selling and buying back crypto at the same time in order to create the illusion of liquidity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/593/0*rDNMCSEGOywcNaRw" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Transparency — Practice what you Preach&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everybody involved with blockchain or distributed technology uses the narrative of transparency and blocking corruption as their main talking points. How can we advocate transparency when our markets aren’t transparent? We should be more concerned with portraying the technology and markets for what they really are — not what we want them to be. This is likely to be a revelation for cryptocurrency trading and institutional investments. Most institutions have a tiny presence in the market but nothing meaningful. Certain institutions may use it as a neat little platform for them to manipulate liquidity and rake in some profits. But for meaningful capital inflow to Bitcoin and its peers, we need to see the market for what it really is and work toward strengthening it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s very likely Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, and all the other huge banks and corporations are aware of the fake liquidity in cryptocurrency. For them, the ​maturity of the market trumps technological development. They’re more interested in their return on investment than how it can fundamentally change the world. But let’s be honest, so are most cryptocurrency investors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up till now, the industry has unfortunately been extremely hypocritical. Crypto enthusiasts call out the banking cartel for their lack of transparency when crypto markets themselves don’t have any. Of course, when we talk of transparency, it is with regard to transactions and networks. So the added transparency to the financial market side of crypto will be a huge boost to credibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/768/0*zuPTBiz9ANU4f7G6" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Long Term Effects&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than focusing on the present, we should look at the long term effects of this event. This revelation means the entire industry will now overcome ‘fake volume’. Now that the problem is not just known but also publicized, we will see many solutions come forward. The first of those is the analytics firm Messari. Messari has decided to release a ‘Top 10’ index that shows true volume on the top 10 exchanges. Many such solutions will emerge to give a more pragmatic view of​ the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Influential people like Vitalik Buterin and Jackson Palmer (amongst others) have openly spoken of the negatives of the market. Their vision is to put their time and effort into the technology as the markets are far too young. Vitalik has gone as far as to tell people to only invest a fraction of their capital in cryptocurrency and to be prepared to lose even that as the markets are hyper-volatile and anything can happen. His sentiments honestly echo the truth. A high allocation to cryptocurrency is the reason why most cryptocurrency hedge funds are failing. Inexperienced and hyperactive fund managers jump from public equities and private investment straight into cryptocurrency because they made 10x holding some Bitcoin and can explain what a blockchain does. The dynamics are far more complicated. The fundamentals of cryptocurrency are not comparable to the fundamentals of traditional investments. Bitcoin doesn’t have an operating margin, a business model that can be tweaked at your will, or potential for cost reduction. The closest thing to fundamentals in crypto boils down to two things: the news and sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The basic outcome I see is net positive. We lose some short term credibility, but we gain long term traction in the right direction. It is impossible to please everyone, so we might as well take the ethical route. This ethical route also turns out to be the best option for the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why Didn’t This Come Out Sooner?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be overly blunt, nobody cared. Yes, we knew that this was happening, but we didn’t know the extent. The volume surges that seem normal on the outside were actually wash trades. It takes a certain amount of studying volume profiles as well as buy &amp;amp; sell walls to understand what is normal and what is manipulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the volatility in Bitcoin is from unsuspecting retail traders who think they’ve found their golden duck, they enter trades based on where volume is going and it zooms the opposite direction. This happens nearly every time we see Bitcoin rocket upwards (its succeeded by a large move downward). But other than speaking about the manipulation, nobody viewed this as a serious issue as long as they were able to ride the wave and lock in a significant amount of gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most traders were sure $6000 was the limit to downside. This came from the ‘mining fallacy’ that stated miners wouldn’t let Bitcoin fall below a profitable level. This is completely untrue as stocks continuously fall below issued capital amounts or intrinsic value. Gold has also fallen below the cost of mining, so what makes people think Bitcoin is immune from this? If anything, it makes Bitcoin more susceptible given the rampant manipulation that everyone claims to know exists. A quick study of previous bull runs and their ensuing corrections show us more often than not, Bitcoin hits the peak of the previous bull-run. In this case, that level is around $950. You might think it’s a crazy thing to call for, but if you rule it out, you close your mind to the infinite possibilities that could occur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only recently people started to legitimately care about the manipulation and volume busts as they lost a fortune when Bitcoin price halved ($6000-$3000). But if a large entity like Bitwise didn’t publish a formal report, these people still wouldn’t have cared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I often call the current banking system ‘the banking cartel’ given their close ties and interdependent actions. But in all honesty, there is a ‘whale cartel’ in Bitcoin that controls the market. This can only be overcome by achieving a high level of real liquidity and volume to shrink the amount of control these whales have in the market. I specify Bitcoin in general because we don’t know if other altcoins have the same kind of whale movement. Altcoins so far have merely tracked Bitcoin price sentiment, so it may just be a case of replication over manipulation. As Andreas Antonopolous said,​ “Bitcoin adoption is low because it’s volatile; Bitcoin volatility is high because of low adoption”. It is essentially a paradox that will require a significant growth driver. This growth driver is likely to be a force external to the Bitcoin network as we have seen in Venezuela.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transparency is key going forward. We require more and more transparency in order to live by the doctrines we advocate. This may be a short term trough for Bitcoin, but this will help us grow organically rather than through fake volume and controlled price movements. Bitcoin is most certainly not dead. With each hack, the Bitcoin network gains more resilience. Once this feature is replicated in the market, nobody with half a brain will be able to call Bitcoin an immature market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Sources&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://staging.busy.org/exit?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sec.gov%2Fcomments%2Fsr-nysearca-2019-01%2Fsrnysearca201901-5164833-183434.pdf"&gt;Bitwise and NYSE Arca Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Images — OMC and CoinDesk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- AB&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=f20279b1ad8b" width="1" height="1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com/why-unveiling-fake-volume-is-essential-for-market-growth-f20279b1ad8b"&gt;Why Unveiling Fake Volume is Essential for Market Growth&lt;/a&gt; was originally published in &lt;a href="https://hackernoon.com"&gt;Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt; on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wired security: Hacker Eva Galperin Has a Plan to Eradicate Stalkerware -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/eva-galperin-stalkerware-kaspersky-antivirus</link><description>Galperin has already convinced Kaspersky to flag domestic abuse spyware as malware. She expects more to follow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Naked Security: 2m credit cards ripped off from restaurant chain, sold on the dark web -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2019/04/03/2m-credit-cards-ripped-off-from-restaurant-chain-sold-on-the-dark-web/</link><description>PoS malware affected some Buca di Beppo, Earl of Sandwich, Planet Hollywood, Chicken Guy!, Mixology and Tequila Taqueria locations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The New York Times Most shared: Woman From China Carrying Malware Arrested After Entering Mar-a-Lago -  Puntaje: 375.0</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/02/us/mar-a-lago-zhang-chinese-secret-service.html?partner=rss&amp;emc=rss</link><description>Mar-a-Lago, President Trump’s club in Palm Beach, Fla.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 03:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: Insurers Take The Guesswork Out Of Small Business Cyber Insurance -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2019/sayata-smb-cyber-insurance/</link><description>The threat of a small business cyberattack has introduced a conundrum for the rising InsurTech market. The demand for cyber insurance is on the rise, with the sector expected to reach a $7.5 billion valuation by the end of the decade, with small businesses a rising customer demographic. Yet those small companies remain one of […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: Crooks use hidden directories of compromised HTTPS sites to deliver malware -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83249/cyber-crime/https-sites-deliver-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Attackers Store Malware in Hidden Directories of Compromised HTTPS Sites Security experts at Zscaler discovered that threat actors are using hidden “well-known” directories of HTTPS sites to store and deliver malicious payloads. Crooks are utilizing hidden “well-known” directories of HTTPS sites running WordPress and Joomla websites to store and serve malicious payloads. Hacked websites were [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/83249/cyber-crime/https-sites-deliver-malware.html"&gt;Crooks use hidden directories of compromised HTTPS sites to deliver malware&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 06:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The New York Times Business: There Are Probably Cameras on Your Flight, but Relax, They’re Not On (Yet) -  Puntaje: 1000.0</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/02/business/airlines-cameras-privacy.html?partner=rss&amp;emc=rss</link><description>Vitaly Kamluk, a cybersecurity and malware expert, stirred attention on Twitter in February, including from two senators, after querying Singapore Airlines about what looked like a camera in the seat back.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 03:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Sandinavia's Evry turns to ACI Worldwide to strengthen card and mobile payment processes -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77898/sandinavias-evry-turns-to-aci-worldwide-to-strengthen-card-and-mobile-payment-processes?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>ACI Worldwide (NASDAQ: ACIW), a leading global provider of real-time electronic payment and banking...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Bill.com raises $88m for business payments push -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/bill-com-raises-88m-for-business-payments-push/</link><description>Led by Franklin Templeton with participation from Mastercard, Fidelity Investments Canada, among others.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 12:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Jet Airways defers March salary payment to its 16,000 employees -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/companies/jet-airways-defers-march-salary-payment-to-its-16-000-employees-119040300875_1.html</link><description>Earlier, the airline had been delaying the salaries of its pilots, engineers and senior staff since August who have not been paid since January</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 18:06:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Celo Raises $30 Million for Stablecoin-Based Smartphone Payment Plans -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/celo-raises-30-million-for-stablecoin-based-smartphone-payment-plans</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lZDg3ZjcxNzBhOTExYTZlNDRiNjVlNWJhNmY2YzBjZS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Startup Celo has raised $30 million, with plans to let unbanked send funds internationally using a stablecoin&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:14:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker News: In-Depth Analysis of JS Sniffers Uncovers New Families of Credit Card-Skimming Code -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~3/JW9uuneJoCE/js-sniffers-credit-card-hacking.html</link><description>In a world that's growing increasingly digital, Magecart attacks have emerged as a key cybersecurity threat to e-commerce sites.

Magecart, which is in the news a lot lately, is an umbrella term given to 12 different cyber criminal groups that are specialized in secretly implanting a special piece of code on compromised e-commerce sites with an intent to steal payment card details of their&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/TheHackersNews/~4/JW9uuneJoCE" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 03:18:53 PDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Nimiq Acquires 9.9% Stake in Germany's WEG AG to Become Bank's Third Crypto Firm Owner -  Puntaje: 2100</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nimiq-acquires-99-stake-in-germanys-weg-ag-to-become-banks-third-crypto-firm-owner</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8zYjkxYWQyOGNjZjZlZjM3ZjQ5ZTFhNTMwMzVmZTBhZS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Browser-based blockchain payments system Nimiq acquired a 9.9 percent stake in Germany’s WEG Bank AG, joining existing shareholders TokenPay and the Litecoin Foundation&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: All Shops in Changi Airport Will Accept E-Wallet Payments Very Soon -  Puntaje: 2900</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29902/mobilepayments/changi-airport-qr-e-wallet-payment-mobile-paynow-alipay-grabpay/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The various merchants in Changi were probably already on their way towards accepting QR wallet payments one way or another, but a recent agreement may help speed up that process. Changi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29902/mobilepayments/changi-airport-qr-e-wallet-payment-mobile-paynow-alipay-grabpay/"&gt;All Shops in Changi Airport Will Accept E-Wallet Payments Very Soon&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 03:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Effective Implementation of PSD2 and Open Banking Propositions -  Puntaje: 1400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16966/effective-implementation-of-psd2-and-open-banking-propositions?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The target for Open Banking access has fallen way short of legislators’ expectations, with over 40%...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 14:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: European Commission sets up fintech innovation forum -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33630/european-commission-sets-up-fintech-innovation-forum?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The European Commission has launched a European Forum for Innovation Facilitators (EFIF), to improve...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: OpenGamma raises $10M in a growth funding round led by Dawn Capital -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Jg2SRysc2PM/</link><description>Over ten years ago, OpenGamma emerged as one of London&amp;#8217;s new breed of FinTech startups, launching an open source analytics and risk management platform for the financial services industry. Its open architecture allowed financial services firms to develop analytics applications aimed at traders and risk managers. This open-source approach was designed to disrupt the proprietary [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: To license or not to license – are we asking the question? -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/04/03/to-license-or-not-to-license-are-we-asking-the-question/</link><description>In 2017, SME challenger bank OakNorth first came to the attention of Daily Fintech readers in a post from Bernard titled ‘Can challenger banks break the massive bank concentration in the UK?’. Since then the bank has achieved some significant milestones, many of which have come to light in the press in the past few [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 06:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: With this New ATM by NCR, You Only Need to Wave Your Hand to Get Cash -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29877/fintech/ncr-kelpie-atm/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;American banking solution vendor NCR Corporation showcased its latest range of self service banking solution recently at Money 20/20. One of the machines in particular caught our attention. Dubbed concept&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29877/fintech/ncr-kelpie-atm/"&gt;With this New ATM by NCR, You Only Need to Wave Your Hand to Get Cash&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 07:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: Traversing Indonesia’s FinTech Landscape – Investment Perspective -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://gomedici.com/traversing-indonesia-fintech-landscape-investment-perspective/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/traversing-indonesia-fintech-landscape-investment-perspective.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;Over the next few weeks, MEDICI brings you a series of articles exploring FinTech in the ASEAN region. The articles, each focused on a different ASEAN country, provide comprehensive insights into the FinTech investment landscape in the region. ASEAN in Figures ASEAN (the Association of Southeast Asian Nations) is the third-largest Asian region. It is home to more than 630 million people and one-fourth of the population lives in urban areas. ASEAN has an annual growth rate of 4.7% and USD 119.97 billion in FDI; it is also one of the fastest-growing regions as well as the seventh-largest economy globally. Its population is young and educated with a literacy rate of over 80%, phone-savvy with more than 0.5 phones per person, and enjoys a low-to-mid unemployment rate of 0.5%–6.9%. ASEAN members also have an average to a high life expectancy of 69–82.7 years, and a gender parity of 49.9% males...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 14:49:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Onfido, which verifies IDs using AI, nabs $50M from SoftBank, Salesforce, Microsoft and more -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/lqBIPHMF7b0/</link><description>Security breaches, where malicious hackers obtain snippets of information that then get used to impersonate individuals in order to gain access to individuals&amp;#8217; and businesses&amp;#8217; sensitive financial and other private information, have become par for the course in the world of digital services. More than 2.7 billion records were  breached in a single incident this year [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 12:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Tinkoff builds most powerful supercomputer in financial sector -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/tinkoff-builds-most-powerful-supercomputer-in-financial-sector/</link><description>Offers much faster solution to machine learning and AI-related tasks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 11:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Saxo Bank: What does Q2 hold for Europe? -  Puntaje: 3600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/economy/saxo-bank-what-does-q2-hold-for-europe/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_318496325-1-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_318496325-1-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/shutterstock_318496325-1-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Saxo Bank, the online trading and investment specialist, has published today its Q2 2019 Quarterly Outlook for global markets, including trading ideas covering equities, FX, currencies, commodities, and bonds, as well as a range of central macro themes impacting client portfolios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The euro could struggle to rally until a path towards EMU deepening opens up”, says Steen Jakobsen, Chief Economist and CIO, Saxo Bank. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The gulf between European valuations and their US counterparts remains high with Europe trading at a massive discount. Part of this lies with the composition of business – Europe has less technology firms and more privately-owned companies. In fact, the most truly successful companies in Europe remain in private hands, and for good reason as they refuse to cave to short-term, quarterly earnings report-centred strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The view from the outside is that Europe is a perennial basket case. This is an easy conclusion to reach if you don’t understand Europe’s history, its vested interests, the peace dividend and the need for government to sell the naive illusion of fiscal self-rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We firmly believe that any macro change has to come from a breakdown or a crisis, and as such we see 2019 and 2020 as key years for Europe’s evolution. We foresee populist parties getting 20% if not 25% of the popular vote in May’s European parliament elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The most important, factor, though is the collapse of German growth. We see a risk of recession there by Q4 even without a trade spat with the US. Germany, with its very successful “industry 3.0” model, is being left behind. Underinvestment in the technology sector leaves it unprepared as “industry 4.0” rolls in, and its internet speed ranking is just one of many symptoms. Germany needs to catch up in terms of digitalisation, in terms of programmes for working women, with new airports and more overall infrastructure spending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The lapse of Germany will reopen the Franco-German “hotline” as well as making the debt issue a pan-European issue, and not one of Germany versus the PIIGS, or austerity versus free spending. Investors long convinced by talk of basket cases would be unwise to count out Europe. It is, after all, perfectly positioned to benefit from automation, AI, digitalisation and a capital market that is cheap by any standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Q2 will see the noise increase; the “basket case” narrative will be spread far and wide and the EUR, led by the ECB, will probably test 1.05 if not 1.03 versus the dollar. The next 12 months, however, will be 2000 all over again.“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Against this uncertain backdrop, Saxo’s main trading ideas and themes for Q2 include: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equities – the great divergence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The depressing reality is that European companies have had negative real growth in operating earnings as the region lacks a strong technology sector that capitalises on the digital age. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter Garnry, Head of Equity Strategy, said: “We remain defensive on equities until there is evidence of a turning point as contracting economies with below-trend activity have historically delivered negative equity returns. Within Europe, this macro environment is typically bad for Europe’s cyclical equity markets such as Germany, Italy, the Netherlands, Norway and France. The equity markets that usually do relatively well in a poor economic environment are Denmark, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland and the UK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One of Europe’s biggest problems remains the banking sector. The total return on Europe’s banking sector is zero since January 2003; in real terms, it’s -28.5% over a 15-year period. This is an ugly parallel to Japan’s zombie banks after its meltdown in the 1990s. Europe has also agreed to implement costly banking regulations, driving up costs on an already weak sector. It has been 10 years since Lehman Brothers’ bankruptcy and Europe’s banking sector has still not healed; this will continue to be an anchor constraining growth and equity returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FX – Europe has most to lose and most to gain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Europe is in a potential lose-lose situation as we await the outcome of the US-China trade negotiations. The friendlier the deal, the more likely that China could shift some of its import demand away from Europe and towards the US. With or without a friendly deal, risks point to ongoing de-globalization and a growth slowdown that would be double trouble for the European Union, the world’s largest trade surplus economic bloc. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Europe stumbles towards recession later this year or early next year, the old existential questions will inevitably rise once more to dog the EU political and financial landscape. In short, Saxo believes that Europe deserves a considerable portion of our attention as Q2 will inevitably prove an important pivot point for the EU. Either we see escalating signs of further dysfunction or a more determined shift by EU governments to get ahead of the risks of rising populism and the unworkable fiscal/European Central Bank foundation of the EMU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Hardy, Head of FX Strategy, said: “Our least favourite currencies in a weakening global growth environment are the commodity dollar currencies, where housing bubbles are in various stages of unwinding, inevitably impacting the credit and therefore growth outlooks. Our longer-term bullish call on commodities should eventually offset downside risks, but these risks will prevail until central bank policy in these countries looks like it does for the rest of the DM – i.e. more or less ZIRP and central bank balance sheet expansion to clean up the private credit mess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Growth risks remain a concern for emerging markets, but we think China provides a backdrop of stability as it seeks to maintain a stable currency and attract capital inflows to deepen its capital markets and accommodate its transition to becoming a deficit country (a key step in shifting the CNY to an eventual reserve asset). The JPY could do well during bouts of risk deleveraging this year, but the Japanese government is perhaps the most ready to switch on the fiscal stimulus, with the Bank of Japan happy to cooperate as it seeks to avoid yen volatility.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commodities power ahead&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The commodity sector delivered a surprisingly strong return during the first quarter of 2019 with the Bloomberg Commodity Index trading higher by 9%. This remarkable development relates to the fact that the rise was led by growth-dependent commodities such as energy (+17%) and industrial metals (+12.5%). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markets, including commodities, began the year on the defensive with growth concerns and US Federal Reserve-led liquidity tightening raising concerns about the prospects for 2019. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The year, however, was only a few weeks old before global policy panic set in. In early January, the Fed hit the pause button before abandoning it at the end of the quarter while calling a halt to further quantitative tightening. The Bank of Japan and the European Central Bank followed suit with their own measures, while in China the government stepped in with various initiatives to stabilise the economy as the chance of a trade deal between Washington and Beijing helped sentiment further. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ole Hansen, Head of Commodity Strategy, “The dramatic recent turnaround at the Fed is seen as bullish for gold as the return to a dovish stance highlights the risk of a gold-supportive recession within the next 12 months. The second quarter, however, may not yet provide the spark gold needs to break strong resistance between $1,360/oz and $1,380/oz. Into the second half, however, a formidable challenge could be seen amid support from a weaker dollar, stable to lower bond yields and concerns about global stocks’ ability to forge higher amid raised growth concerns.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Macro – You can’t fight gravity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has been a huge shift in the global macro backdrop over the last six months and it has huge structural significance for both Asia and the world as a whole. The crux of the matter is that central bankers, led by the Federal Reserve and European Central Bank, have unequivocally failed to attain escape velocity from quantitative easing. The gravitational pull of addiction to lose money has led to pampered stock and bond markets, as well as some remarkable events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saxo believes that we shouldn’t be surprised about escaping this QE world, particularly given debt levels are now north of $250 trillion as compared to $175 trillion before the financial crisis. The bank does feel though that the speed with which we have been pulled back in, was surprising. The implication is now that, until a “great debt reset” (read: haircuts, restructuring and a debt jubilee) that could still be five to ten years away, it’s back to QE for life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay Van-Petersen, Global Macro Strategist, “Taking the world back to looser monetary policy and lower yields will be bullish for bonds and equities. Expect new cyclical lows in bond yields for example, and as we have long mentioned, Australian 10-years are already taking out the 1.81% lows. Structurally speaking, I also expect a much weaker USD over the course of the year. The world needs a weaker USD to flourish and what the world needs, it tends to eventually get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s also worth noting that while we are not far from all-time highs in US equity indices, we have already seen new all-time highs in certain stocks, Shanghai at around 3,100 is still around 40% lower than its 2015 high of 5,180. We also have huge China equity inclusions in the MSCI EM index coming that will take us from 5% to 20% (in +5% increments slated for May, August and November. The bounce in Chinese equities is likely telling us that, for now at least, we’ve seen the worst in the underlying Chinese economy and could be in for some positive surprises, particularly in Q2’19 growth data.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonds – Why sovereign bonds are Q2’s investor favourites&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first quarter of 2019 saw a U-turn in central bank policy. With data pointing to a global slowdown, policymakers do not wish to take chances. Saxo believes that is why we have seen the Federal Reserve stall its rate hike plans, the European Central Bank commit to whatever support measures are needed and the People’s Bank of China push stimulus in the form of fiscal policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Althea Spinozzi, Bonds Specialist, added: “We believe that this global policy panic will play in favour of global sovereigns. Credit spreads will also be supported, but investors should remember that dovish central bank policies may prolong the late-cycle period. They will not, however, be sufficient to entirely avoid the recession we believe is coming in Q4’19 or early 2020. This means that while credit valuations will be supported for longer, credit risk will remain very high; in this context, investors should stay cautious and avoid picking up unnecessary risk, especially in the high-yield and emerging market spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The global policy panic sparked by the December selloffs has seen the Fed turn away from quantitative tightening and its own rate hike schedule. A dovish Fed is good news for bond investors even amid muted economic growth. Treasuries will gain from the unconditional support even though if it is now clear that recession is coming.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Macro – A reality check for the euro area&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Large declines in core European industrial production data can be observed, especially in Germany, which accounts for one-third of European industrial activity. This slowdown came as a shock for many policymakers, but Saxo feels that it was predictable. Over recent quarters, leading indicators - notably credit impulse - led us to warn clients and investors against the risk of lower growth in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As economic data will continue to disappoint in the coming months, Saxo believes that a new consensus for looser fiscal policy will emerge in European countries in H2’19. An accumulation of negative German data could be the perfect trigger to set off expansionary fiscal policy in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christopher Dembik, Head of Macroeconomic Analysis, said: “We see growing risks to growth in the periphery of the euro area and expect that Germany will experience disappointing growth this year. The outcome is likely to be more fiscal expansion after the EU parliamentary elections and further monetary stimulus in a tricky period for the ECB as it will be looking for its next president.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Macro – Debt financed spending versus rising populism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Trump and the China-US trade war to Brexit and the gilets jaunes, the threats of this regime shift are evident. The tectonic plates are shifting, even if we are yet to feel the consequences of the extremist versions of these movements, like a hard Brexit. After a 30-year spate of deregulation and laissez-faire economics, this new paradigm will create a different business and investment environment and the implications will be far-reaching, creating fresh headwinds and therefore risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eleanor Creagh, Market Strategist, commented: “As the backlash intensifies, so will the battleground, making it increasingly difficult to price risk and determine the policy response against a complicated and polarising backdrop. Aside from reactive or palliative redistribution policies, any response that will bring real improvement and tackle the misfortunes of those caught on the wrong side of globalisation seems a long way off. The current new political era is the result of decades of societal shifts and the solution could itself take decades to work though.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click here to access Saxo Bank’s full Q2 2019 outlook, with more in-depth pieces from our analysts and strategists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/economy/saxo-bank-what-does-q2-hold-for-europe/"&gt;Saxo Bank: What does Q2 hold for Europe?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Changi Airport taps Liquid Group for roll out of integrated QR payment and marketing platform -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77897/changi-airport-taps-liquid-group-for-roll-out-of-integrated-qr-payment-and-marketing-platform?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Liquid Group is pleased to announce today that it has entered into an agreement with Changi Airport...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BusinessLine Money &amp; Banking: Paytm Payments Bank to offer risk-free insurance, mutual fund by June: MD -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/money-and-banking/paytm-payments-bank-to-offer-risk-free-insurance-mutual-fund-by-june-md/article26721960.ece</link><description>Paytm Payments Bank is planning to launch risk-free insurance and mutual fund products by June this year, the company’s MD and CEO Satish Kumar Gupt</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 17:31:21 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Paytm Payments Bank to offer risk-free insurance, MF products by June: MD -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/finance/paytm-payments-bank-to-offer-risk-free-insurance-mf-products-by-june-md-119040300783_1.html</link><description>The Paytm Payments Bank has 4.4 crore savings bank accounts with a deposit of over Rs 400 crore</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 17:11:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: 5-Star Swiss Hotel Set to Accept Bitcoin Payments -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/5-star-swiss-hotel-set-to-accept-bitcoin-payments</link><description>The Dolder Grand, a five-star hotel in Switzerland, will start accepting bitcoin payments from next month.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 04:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Nationwide and Jaywing explore “explainable” AI driven application scoring -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/04/nationwide-and-jaywing-explore-explainable-ai-driven-application-scoring/</link><description>The building society was impressed by Jaywing’s transparent model.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Biotech Company-Turned-Mining Firm Riot Blockchain Reports 2018 Net Loss of $58 Million -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/biotech-company-turned-mining-firm-riot-blockchain-reports-2018-net-loss-of-58-million</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85NTRhYTNkMjkxZTczNjY2Y2U1ZTExMjVhM2YwMzU3Zi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biotech company-turned-mining firm Riot Blockchain reported a 2018 net loss of about $58 million, with revenue through mining of $7.3 million&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: US Blockchain Firm Partners with Sustainable Construction Firm to Design Data Centers -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-blockchain-firm-partners-with-sustainable-construction-firm-to-design-data-centers</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lNzg3N2Y3Njg3YWE0ZjFjZTMzMWY4YzE5MmNiYmVlYS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. blockchain startup BHCV partnered with SG Blocks to develop data centers made of used shipping containers&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 02:13:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: Chinese Woman Cuffed at Mar-a-Lago With Malware on USB -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/chinese-woman-arrested-maralago-1-1/</link><description>Woman with two passports was told to seek out Trump family member</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Smart Dubai Endorses Blockchain Platform From Major Local Telecoms Operator -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/smart-dubai-endorses-blockchain-platform-from-major-local-telecoms-operator</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lMjYyMDZkM2YxNmNmM2NkNGU1NzEwYmVhNDg2MDU1Ny5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dubai’s digital transformation Smart Dubai has endorsed du’s Blockchain-Platform-as-a-Service&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 11:17:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Jamaica Stock Exchange to Pilot Bitcoin and Ether Trading -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/jamaica-stock-exchange-to-pilot-bitcoin-and-ether-trading</link><description>The Jamaica Stock Exchange is soon to trial bitcoin and ether trades with help from Canadian fintech firm Blockstation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Bitcoin at 4-month high as cryptocurrency market suddenly springs to life -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/markets/bitcoin-at-4-month-high-as-cryptocurrency-market-suddenly-springs-to-life-119040300176_1.html</link><description>The cryptocurrency briefly topped $5,000 and the value of digital assets tracked by CoinMarketCap.com jumped by about $17 billion in less than an hour</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:29:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: INATBA: EU seeking ways for widespread adoption of Blockchain, and what this means for the industry -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16964/inatba-eu-seeking-ways-for-widespread-adoption-of-blockchain-and-what-this-means-for-the-industry?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The past few days have seen a surge in the value of Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies in general. The bul...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:35:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: Run.AI raises $13M for its distributed machine learning platform -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/1BrR9eX0Y9Q/</link><description>Tel Aviv&amp;#8217;s Run.AI, a startup that is building a new virtualization and acceleration platform for deep learning, is coming out of stealth today. As a part of this announcement, the company also announced that it has now raised a total of $13 million. This includes a $3 million seed round from TLV Partners and a [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: System Audit with help of Artificial Intelligence in Banking -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16965/system-audit-with-help-of-artificial-intelligence-in-banking?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Across the globe, banks are facing major issue with digital banking, cyber security, regulatory audi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:39:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: A16z, Polychain Invest $25 Million in Crypto Payments Startup Celo -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/a16z-polychain-invest-25-million-into-crypto-payments-startup-celo</link><description>Mobile-friendly cryptocurrency payments startup Celo has raised millions from A16z and Polychain in a private token sale.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>