<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:25:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cointelegraph: Overstock CEO Praises tZERO Blockchain Platform in Q4 Earnings Report -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/overstock-ceo-praises-tzero-blockchain-platform-in-q4-earnings-report</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81MjY1OTVjMGU5Mzg0MjNiOTI3ZmViNDAxYzBkODYzZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q4 earnings need improvement, Overstock CEO says while championing blockchain offering&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Italian asset manager AcomeA successfully tests direct to consumer distribution using blockchain -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77685/italian-asset-manager-acomea-successfully-tests-direct-to-consumer-distribution-using-blockchain?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>AcomeA SGR, a leading Italian asset management company, has successfully completed an investment fun...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Australia Announces National Blockchain Roadmap and Further Boost to Government Funding -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-announces-national-blockchain-roadmap-and-further-boost-to-government-funding</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy84OTYwM2Q0ZWJjZGIyODVhMTA1NDU5NGY2ZWM5OWNjZi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia has unveiled a national blockchain strategy and roadmap, with a boost of AU$100,000 in further funding from the federal government&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Australian Government to Help Fund Trade Mission to CoinDesk Consensus -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/australian-government-to-help-fund-trade-mission-to-coindesk-consensus</link><description>Australia’s government has committed AU$100,000 to support blockchain firms joining Austrade's mission to CoinDesk Consensus in May.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: Lightning Network is the Bitcoin story that matters in 2019 -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/03/18/lightning-network-is-the-bitcoin-story-that-matters-in-2019/</link><description>For general background, please go to this chapter of The Blockchain Economy digital book. If Lightning Network works, Bitcoin will become more than a store of value. It will also become a currency for regular use. If not, Bitcoin may be relegated to the dustbin of history. A lot of Altcoins will decline in value [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 06:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Editorial: The Rumours of ICOs’​ Death Have Been Greatly Exaggerated -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/18/editorial-the-rumours-of-icos%e2%80%8b-death-have-been-greatly-exaggerated/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/18/editorial-the-rumours-of-icos%e2%80%8b-death-have-been-greatly-exaggerated/"&gt;Editorial: The Rumours of ICOs&amp;#8217;​ Death Have Been Greatly Exaggerated&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/twain2-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="32234" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/18/editorial-the-rumours-of-icos%e2%80%8b-death-have-been-greatly-exaggerated/twain2/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/twain2.jpg" data-orig-size="1920,1080" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="twain2" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/twain2-300x169.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/twain2-1024x576.jpg" /&gt;“The reports of my death are greatly exaggerated.”  So said Mark Twain. Allegedly. There was some irony in his declaration. As there is in my headline. Crypto Winter has been hard on all of us. However, I would like to share some of my thoughts which may give you some ideas of where we came from, where we [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/18/editorial-the-rumours-of-icos%e2%80%8b-death-have-been-greatly-exaggerated/"&gt;Editorial: The Rumours of ICOs&amp;#8217;​ Death Have Been Greatly Exaggerated&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IBM Blockchain Blog: Exploring blockchain as the foundation for next gen apps on Web 3.0 -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain/2019/03/exploring-blockchain-as-the-foundation-for-next-gen-apps-on-web-3-0/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Web 3.0 is the collection of next gen web applications which use emerging technologies such as blockchain, AI, IoT, augmented and virtual reality (AR/VR) as part of their core technology stack. These emerging technologies will shape the interactions users will have in this next generation of the web. The internet took us from zero to [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain/2019/03/exploring-blockchain-as-the-foundation-for-next-gen-apps-on-web-3-0/"&gt;Exploring blockchain as the foundation for next gen apps on Web 3.0&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ibm.com/blogs/blockchain"&gt;Blockchain Pulse: IBM Blockchain Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, Litecoin, EOS, Bitcoin Cash, Binance Coin, Stellar, Tron, Cardano: Price Analysis, March 18 -  Puntaje: 2600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-ripple-litecoin-eos-bitcoin-cash-binance-coin-stellar-tron-cardano-price-analysis-march-18</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jMzE3OTU4MmM2NmFjZjk5NDZkZWIxMmViNDAwZmU5My5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As larger traditional players have recognized the power of blockchain, how have the markets responded?&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: Will Increased Decentralization Give Bitcoin its Second Life? -  Puntaje: 4800</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/18/will-increased-decentralization-give-bitcoin-its-second-life/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/18/will-increased-decentralization-give-bitcoin-its-second-life/"&gt;Will Increased Decentralization Give Bitcoin its Second Life?&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/staffwriter/"&gt;Staff Writer&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/bitcoin-2868703_960_720-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="26102" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2018/02/26/high-street-crypto-payments-within-two-years-report/bitcoin-2868703_960_720/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/bitcoin-2868703_960_720.jpg" data-orig-size="960,635" data-comments-opened="1" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;2.5&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;NIKON D7000&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;50&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;160&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0.01&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="bitcoin-2868703_960_720" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/bitcoin-2868703_960_720-300x198.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/bitcoin-2868703_960_720.jpg" /&gt;Adrian Thomson, Global VP of Marketing at Sapphire It’s no secret that the cryptocurrency industry is an unpredictable landscape. With consistent lows and highs taking the value of digital currencies to opposing extremes, the sector is not without its volatility. For instance, in 2017, Bitcoin hit an all-time high reaching a value of over $17,000 [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/18/will-increased-decentralization-give-bitcoin-its-second-life/"&gt;Will Increased Decentralization Give Bitcoin its Second Life?&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/staffwriter/"&gt;Staff Writer&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Winklevoss Twins: Crypto Heralds Something Greater Than Facebook -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/winklevoss-twins-crypto-heralds-something-greater-than-facebook</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9iNmI1MWEyMmQyNmZjMDIxNDlmZGQ4MGEyZDM1YzFjOC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Winklevoss twins say that while Facebook’s crypto project is “really positive” for the industry, ultimately crypto will usher in something greater than the social networking era&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Bitcoin Cash Grows as Major Oil Futures Show Mixed Movements -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-cash-grows-as-major-oil-futures-show-mixed-movements</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81ZDQyMzkyNzU4NmQ4NjA3YTg2YjRlMDUwNzBiYmU1My5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Cash sees gains as most of the top cryptocurrencies and Bitcoin are reporting slight to noteworthy losses on the day&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Banking Startup Launching Visa Card That Lets You Spend 7 Cryptos -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/banking-startup-launching-visa-card-that-lets-you-spend-7-cryptos</link><description>Banking startup 2gether is launching a prepaid Visa debit card that allows eurozone-based users to spend cryptocurrencies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Israeli Bank Policy Should Not Have Shut Down Bitcoin Mining Firm’s Account, Court Rules -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/israeli-bank-policy-should-not-have-shut-down-bitcoin-mining-firms-account-court-rules</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9jOGQ3YjFmZTg2YmE2OWM2MGVkZTdiMzM1MjM3ZjI5OC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin deposits and banks remain a gray area in Israel after a court rules banks can refuse to accept deposits from crypto trades&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Citi Has Scrapped Its Plan for a JPM Coin-Like Bank-Backed Cryptocurrency -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/citi-scraps-its-plan-for-a-jpm-coin-like-bank-backed-cryptocurrency</link><description>Several years back Citi tested a bank-backed cryptocurrency similar to JPMCoin. The lesson it learned? It's easier to rely on SWIFT.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Exclusive: “Stablecoins will be a key feature of 2019” -  Puntaje: 27000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/exclusive-stablecoins-will-be-a-key-feature-of-2019/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1227211036-min-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1227211036-min-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1227211036-min-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;New investors who trade in cryptocurrencies are also taking up investments in other assets such as stocks, commodities, and forex, according to the latest data revealed by global multi-asset investment platform eToro. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About 11 percent of people, globally, who traded in cryptocurrencies on the eToro platform since 2017, went on to diversify their investments. In the GCC and Arab region, the findings are quite similar. Close to 9 percent of crypto traders in the region invested in other assets, with 2.7 percent of this 9 percent investing in commodities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Global trends show the cryptocurrency market expanding from a valuation of $574.3 million in 2017 to $6.7 billion in 2025 at a compound annual growth rate of 31.3 percent, according to Transparency Market Research. AMEinfo spoke to George Naddaf, Regional Manager, Middle East, at eToro about the growth of cryptocurrency in the GCC region, major trends, important disruptions, and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[caption id="attachment_1381356" align="aligncenter" width="1024"] George Naddaf, Regional Manager of the Middle East at eToro[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: How is crypto-trading picking up in the GCC region? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Naddaf: The Middle East is an incredibly diverse region, which means that interest in cryptoassets is growing as the technology that powers it – blockchain – is increasingly embraced by the region’s leaders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai has led the way in supporting blockchain technology, with His Highness Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the Crown Prince of Dubai and the Chairman of Dubai Future Foundation, establishing a blockchain strategy with a goal of securing all government documents on blockchain by 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, some cities will move faster than others in adopting cryptoassets as certain local economies are still heavily reliant on cash and are moving at different speeds to adopt digital forms of payment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equally, crypto trading has been highly appreciated among investors in the Arabic World where they believe in the longevity of this asset class - especially as cryptoassets and the networks behind them become more organized and regulated. Investors in the Arabic Region are diversifying the crypto portfolio by being able to trade the 14 crypto assets eToro offers them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: How has the investment in crypto opened up opportunities to bring in new investors to other asset classes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Naddaf: Crypto has the power to act as a gateway to long-term investing for people who are new to the market. As we have seen for eToro, the variety of assets available means that people may have come to the platform to initially trade crypto, but could then choose to diversify into other investment types - all in one place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trading in crypto has given new investors a degree of market understanding and experience. It’s enabled them to become familiar with the tools and knowledge needed to make their own investment choices, which can be applied to any asset class they might become interested in. Technical analysis and fundamentals tools are presented in a simple and transparent way on the eToro platform. Users can also take advantage of the knowledge shared between traders on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: What is the crypto industry doing to better engage with consumers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Naddaf: For bitcoin and other cryptos to succeed their rate of adoption has to be faster than email. We, therefore, need to see more user-friendly applications. That is where the industry needs to focus its efforts. If we achieve this in the next 24-36 months, then mass adoption will arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Focusing on the first crypto - Bitcoin - it has managed to ride the wave of volatility and has started to address questions regarding scalability. Its price, although volatile at times, will fall in line with other assets as its utility increases and speculation reduces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first ever Bitcoin transaction took place just eight years ago and today we are already seeing it begin to meet the requirements of everyday money. Given the speed of adoption, we could see bitcoin on the high street within the decade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking beyond crypto as a payment method, blockchain technology has driven an explosion in financial innovation. It offers the potential to upend everything we think we know about financial systems and assets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regulations also have a role to play and we believe that appropriate regulation will help encourage the mass adoption of crypto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: What are the major trends and disruptions likely to impact crypto trading in the coming months?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Naddaf: Last year was a rollercoaster year for crypto assets as the market was balancing itself off the back of highs seen in 2017. However, eToro holds a positive outlook for the year ahead: from increased institutional interest to more regulatory certainty in the market, the infrastructure that traditional markets rely on has grown stronger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s safe to say that the cryptoasset space has seen incredible growth and all signs are pointing towards 2019 being the year that we see a greater level of integration between crypto and traditional markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that the rise of stablecoins will be a key feature of 2019. One of the key obstacles that cryptoassets need to overcome for mainstream adoption is price stability. Stablecoins largely eliminate this hurdle, creating a more user-friendly way to interact with the blockchain. It is well known that eToro is working on the launch of its exchange. Our own suite of stablecoins will form part of the evolving range of tokens listed on the exchange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: Bitcoin is still stuck under the key resistance level of $4000-$4,200. What will BTC need to break past this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Naddaf: $4000 - $4200 remains a key area of resistance on Bitcoin. The price has reached this area on numerous occasions this year and sold off. For the price to potentially break through this level, a significant catalyst, or set of catalysts, is needed to encourage new 'investors' to buy into it. A couple of potential ones that I can point out are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 	major retailers starting to accept BTC, which will potentially come with viable scaling solutions such as Lightning Network&lt;br /&gt;
 	SEC approval of crypto ETP products - such as VanEck SolidX ETF&lt;br /&gt;
 	Intercontinental Exchange’s launch of crypto exchange - BAKKT&lt;br /&gt;
 	regulatory approval of exchange tokens such as Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: What are the challenges preventing blockchain payment methods from becoming mainstream? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Naddaf: The first ever Bitcoin transaction took place just eight years ago and today we are already seeing it begin to meet the requirements of everyday money. Given the speed of adoption, we believe that we could see bitcoin on the high street within the decade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, many challenges remain such as scalability, regulation, energy usage, awareness etc. but we believe that in time these can and will be overcome.  We must remember that crypto assets are still in their infancy and are, rightly so, developing under close scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the greatest challenges is understanding. The Venn diagram between the individuals who understand what is being developed and the ones that write about them simply have very little overlap. We need to change this. We need to work together. The industry knows there are only a handful of cryptocurrencies. Ethereum, for example, is not a currency. It is like saying my Nectar points are money, or my shares on Facebook are money. Other tokens, crypto assets or cryptocurrencies as you refer to them are not currencies, but they can be converted to a currency such as Bitcoin. Just as when gold was used as money, we didn’t have every element within the periodic table used as money we will not have 1.5million cryptocurrencies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we had critiqued the Internet as we do crypto assets, we would not have experienced the changes we have in the last three decades. It wasn’t scalable, we all knew Internet addresses were limited in number. It wasn’t possible to send files larger than 1Mb over email. I couldn’t watch a video. Every time I tried to read something, ‘The Internet went down’. It was pretty useless, but a few people continued to dream and delivered possibly one of the greatest innovations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: How are initiatives like eToro helping in the development of new investors?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Naddaf: eToro was founded in 2007 with the vision of opening up the global markets for everyone to trade and invest in a simple and transparent way. We wanted the eToro to become a community where people could share their ideas. We built the platform as a social network for traders and investors, where they can execute trades, but also see what others are doing and talk to each other. We invented copy trading, or at least brought it to the masses, and 'copy' remains a key feature of our multi-asset platform today. Around half of our clients use it, both in terms of following others or investing in our growing range of CopyPortfolios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that investors are looking for three things: 1) access to the assets they want, 2) knowledge and insight, and 3) someone to make the process easy.  Unlike traditional fund managers, eToro offers all three and at a price point which makes investing accessible to everyone.  Joining eToro gives investors of all types of access to the assets they want today from commodities and stocks, through to crypto assets.  They also benefit from being part of a global community of more than 10 million registered users who share their investment strategies and insights and anyone can follow the approaches of those who have been the most successful. It is simple and easy to set up an account, then buy, hold and sell assets. For those new to investing, the community aspect of eToro’s platform and the educational resources introduce users to the risk profiles of the different asset classes and the types of returns to expect. Our community is alive 24/7 to answer questions and share insight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/exclusive-stablecoins-will-be-a-key-feature-of-2019/"&gt;Exclusive: &amp;#8220;Stablecoins will be a key feature of 2019&amp;#8221;&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC business: Desperate to get through to execs, some cybersecurity vendors are resorting to lies and blackmail -  Puntaje: 375.0</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/18/heres-how-cybersecurity-vendors-drive-the-hacking-news-cycle.html</link><description>Aggressive sales tactics can make it harder for overworked cybersecurity execs to find and stop real threats.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: French Cybersecurity Agency Grants Security Certificate to Ledger Nano S Hardware Wallet -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/french-cybersecurity-agency-grants-security-certificate-to-ledger-nano-s-hardware-wallet</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9mOGMxZTJjMDc5YzFlNWYzMjU0NGQ4OTNhMWIzODc3Yy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ledger Nano S from French crypto hardware wallet firm Ledger has received a First Level Security Certificate from France’s national cybersecurity agency&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BankNews.com: Consumers Are on Board with Increased Mobile Security -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.banknews.com/blog/consumers-are-on-board-with-increased-mobile-security/</link><description>With mobile transacting such as peer-to-peer payments, m-commerce purchases and bill pay on the rise, a recent survey from Atlanta-based Entersekt, a mobile-first fintech provider, focused on uncovering where security and authentication fall on the spectrum of concern for today&amp;#8217;s mobile-driven consumers. Survey findings show that a strong majority of U.S. adults value additional security [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:05:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Business: Digital wallet payments surge on Apple Pay: CBA -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/banking-and-finance/digital-wallet-payments-surge-on-apple-pay-cba-20190315-p514ms.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_business</link><description>Commonwealth Bank says the number of digital wallet transactions has nearly tripled since it launched Apple Pay earlier this year.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:05:00 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Innovations drive 5G push into rural networks -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/telecom/innovations-drive-5g-push-into-rural-networks/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1221123064-min-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1221123064-min-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1221123064-min-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;by Amrit Heer, Head of Business Development, EME, Parallel Wireless&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The telecom operators in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) countries face dual challenges of low telecom penetration and lower Average Revenue Per User (ARPU) in the rural areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to GSMA Mobile Economy report 2018, the subscriber base in the MENA region is still at just 62 percent while only 36 percent of the population uses the internet. Further, mobile monthly ARPU in the region remains stagnant at around $7, one-third of the average ARPU in the OECD countries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Typically, low ARPU in the rural areas dissuades telcos from expanding the network in the rural and remote areas. Further, the region’s overdependence on older generation technologies (over 90 percent of users are still on 2G and 3G networks) means that the service providers are inherently reluctant to expand in yet-to-be connected areas. They are not ready to invest in the older generation of technology knowing that it will be obsolete soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, since the return on investment is spread over a more extended period, so the telcos are unable to justify investment in newer technologies, like 5G, for providing connectivity in rural or remote areas. Many also believe that rural areas do not require high-speed connectivity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first glance, 5G seems to be an urban and futuristic technology. 5G is the latest generation of communication technology that promises ultra-high internet speed, low latency with better coverage. Virtual reality, augmented reality, autonomous cars, and remote surgery is just some of the use cases of this new technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the technology promises many innovative use cases for rural regions as well. For poverty-stricken regions like North Africa, 5G can revolutionize the way governments in the region deliver essential services like education, health, and security to the remotest areas. The technology also enables service providers to offer many innovative use cases like remote surgery, which is especially beneficial for rural areas. The availability of high-speed and cost-effective mobile broadband promises to open up new avenues of economic and social growth for the rural areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An innovative technology approach can enable the rural community to benefit from high-speed mobile broadband. The British Government’s ongoing 5G RuralFirst project is a case in point. The initiative explores new network deployment strategies for rural areas and promises to provide new business models for the rural community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5G RuralFirst shows the way&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently being tested in three locations – North Scotland in the Orkney Islands, and Harper Adams and Somerset in rural England – the 5G RuralFirst project seeks to demonstrate that advancements in technology can be leveraged to cost-effectively provide high-speed connectivity in low-ARPU regions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project uses a novel approach for network deployment. Instead of using the traditional method of adding a new layer for new technology, 5G RuralFirst uses Parallel Wireless’ All G approach to show that telecom operators can deploy all generation networks (2G, 3G, 4G, and 5G) on the same telecom infrastructure efficiently and cost-effectively. This software-enabled approach allows the service provider to move to a new generation of technology by just easily upgrading the software. This way it becomes easier to deploy, maintain and manage the networks. It also adds much-needed simplicity, agility and flexibility to the networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 5G RuralFirst initiative provides a new and more effective model for efficiently deploying rural networks. It is exploring how new 5G technologies can allow new business models to create new networks and demonstrate end-to-end use case, utilizing super-fast enhanced mobile broadband, ultra-low latency communications and support the massive Internet of Things (IoT) connectivity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project also demonstrates how software-based architecture can help in reducing maintenance cost and enabling new business cases. A software-based network can provide the best networks with operational simplicity and business agility needed to excel in the new digital economy regardless of where someone lives, be it rural or urban or even a busy urban environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The success and findings of this project can pave the way for more such trials, possibly, in the MENA region too. It is a significant attempt at busting the myth that areas, where telecom operators have not expanded their coverage, need to start with the primary 2G network before they can think of 3G or 4G, let alone 5G. With the 5G RuralFirst approach, the service providers can think of providing the best-possible connectivity in the rural areas, which will allow the remote areas to use connectivity for overall social and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/telecom/innovations-drive-5g-push-into-rural-networks/"&gt;Innovations drive 5G push into rural networks&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 07:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Boost Capital embraces Open Banking to power small biz financing -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77692/boost-capital-embraces-open-banking-to-power-small-biz-financing?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Boost Capital, a leading provider of small business financing, today announced the launch of Open Ba...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Standard Chartered builds Fintech Bridge to matchmake with startups -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33546/standard-chartered-builds-fintech-bridge-to-matchmake-with-startups?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The innovation arm of Standard Chartered is building a 'fintech bridge' to connect startups to relev...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: PayPal in Argentina; Temenos Backs African Challenger Bank -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://finovate.com/paypal-in-argentina-temenos-backs-african-challenger-bank/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Finovate Global is our weekly look at fintech innovation in developing economies in Asia, Africa, the Middle East, Latin America, and Central and Eastern Europe. Latin America and the Caribbean PayPal invests $750 million in Argentina-based e-commerce company MercadoLibre. First Data to acquire Brazilian electronic funds transfer (EFT) solution provider Software Express. NCR, Bluefin, and Powertranz &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/paypal-in-argentina-temenos-backs-african-challenger-bank/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/paypal-in-argentina-temenos-backs-african-challenger-bank/"&gt;PayPal in Argentina; Temenos Backs African Challenger Bank&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The New York Times Business: Bits: The Week in Tech: How Much Regulation Is Too Much? -  Puntaje: 500.0</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/15/technology/tech-regulation-antitrust.html?partner=rss&amp;emc=rss</link><description>A screen demonstrating facial recognition using artificial intelligence at the CES tech conference in Las Vegas this year.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 03:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: FIS in $43 billion deal for Worldpay as fintech consolidation ramps up -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/news/fis-in-43-billion-deal-for-worldpay-as-fintech-consolidation-ramps-up</link><description>The financial services technology company FIS has agreed to buy Worldpay. The deal is valued at $43 billion and will allow FIS to counter the transaction processing scale Fiserv received when it acquired First Data this year. The merger price is based on a $34 billion bid plus $9 billion of Worldpay's debt.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 11:32:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Exclusive: The fantastic business and journey of drones in our lives -  Puntaje: 3200</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/travel/exclusive-the-fantastic-business-and-journey-of-drones-in-our-lives/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/aziz-drones-150x150-1463558122.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;With the number of delivery drones in the global eCommerce industry alone expected to increase to 2.2 million units by 2025, there will be a surge in the demand for drone servicing, repair, and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Faster deliveries, reduced road traffic, access to remote areas, accurate deliveries, and greater convenience make drones an attractive proposition for last-mile delivery,” said Joe Praveen Vijayakumar, Mobility Consulting Vice President at Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, in reference to drone research the company conducted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Acknowledging the vast application scope of the technology, drone delivery companies are collaborating with drone software platform companies to develop advanced artificial intelligence and autonomous flight capabilities. There is also considerable potential to partner with companies developing next-generation rotors and propellers that can muzzle sound."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AMeinfo interviewed Joe Praveen Vijayakumar, also Senior Industry Analyst, Mobility Practice, at Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We asked about this trend, and his answers below paint a robust picture of the technology that looks sure to have a safe landing in our future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: What is the volume of drone orders by 2025 for e-commerce delivery alone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Delivery drones will predominantly be used to deliver small parcels which will weigh about 2Kgs or less. Presently, about 85% of all parcels delivered in e-commerce weigh about 2kgs or less. So the potential market is huge for drone deliveries in e-commerce. We estimate that globally, about 2.2 million delivery drones will be required by 2025, to support parcel deliveries in the e-commerce industry alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: What size/type/price drones are best suited for the ecommerce industry?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Companies are trying out different types of drones to figure out which drones will be best suited. The drones available in the market at the moment can be classified into two broad categories, namely fixed wing and multirotor drones. Both have their pros and cons. Fixed wing drones do not possess VTOL (vertical take-off) capabilities as multirotor drones. Fixed wing drones are more durable and are more fuel efficient. On the other hand, the hovering capability of multirotor drones allows them to make precise deliveries. Recently we have witnessed the emergence of Transitional drones, which are essential fixed drones with rotors. They combine the advantages of VTOL, along with the aerodynamic advantages of a fixed winged drone design. We believe transitional drones will play a key role in the drone delivery landscape of the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: Where will these land for people living in towers (60th floor for example)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Yes, you will need to have drone landing pads in high rises. Some real estate companies have already started incorporating drone landing pads in their new projects. Trumark Urban, a real estate developer has incorporated a Drone Landing Pad in its project titled TEN 50 in downtown Los Angeles. This is the first residential high rise to have a drone landing pad in the US. Residents of the 25 storey tower can place orders on their smartphone and have their packages delivered to the delivery pad in the building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: What are some of the results of Drone delivery trials in terms of speed, safety, accuracy, AI, others..?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Drone delivery trials are happening across several countries across the globe. One of the prominent ones is the one happening in Iceland. Flytrex has partnered with Iceland based online retailer to drone deliver goods to customers living along one route in the city Reykjavik. Deliveries that earlier used to take 25 minutes to reach the customer by road will be delivered in under 5 minutes using drones. Apart from savings on time and easing traffic congestion, the drone program is expected to cut delivery cost by 60%. Now, AHA and Flytrex are working to expand the service to 13 additional routes in the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: What are the industry sectors, besides eCommerce, best suited for drones?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Our research focused specifically on Drones for deliveries. Apart from drone deliveries in e-commerce, you will see their adoption in industries such as Military (Delivery of supplies to battlefields), Hospitals, Oil&amp;amp; Gas, Construction, Manufacturing, Shipping, Postal/Courier and Food Delivery. Delivery drones will also be used in humanitarian scenarios to deliver aids to people stuck in disaster-struck areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; AME: What is the role of AI with drones in e-commerce but also in construction, surveys, mining, or any main sector they are employed in?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- An AI-powered drone will work autonomously with minimal human intervention, thereby reducing mishaps caused due to human error&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- AI will enable drones to understand their mistakes when they commit one and learn from them, resulting in progressively improved service over a period of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Drone companies have access to huge volumes of data generated by drones while on their missions. Driven by AI; this data can be used by drones to make informed decisions to enhance drone services in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: Will AI allow drones to talk to each other, and what would they say? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Yes, the drones will communicate with each other, primarily to ensure that they do not stray into each other’s path and avoid a collision. Data pertaining to evolving weather conditions on different routes can also be shared real-time among drones in flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: Does autonomous for drones mean that no human will be engaged remotely or directly?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Even with autonomous drones, we predict that operations will commence with a human command and control centre to monitor the drones in flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: Is Drone noise part of regulatory compliance? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Yes, it is. A swarm of delivery drones flying overhead populated areas is likely to make considerable noise which can disturb the inhabitants. Hence companies are working to develop propulsion systems which will reduce the noise emitted from drones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: How is space around cities partitioned to allow for Drone-Specific areas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Governments, regulatory authorities and drone companies are working towards developing an effective geofencing mechanism that will allow drones to be operated on a large scale in urban areas in the future&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: How catastrophic are instances when these spaces are violated, or when interference takes place with amateurs not bound by rules Drone operators abide by?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Yes, it can be catastrophic. That’s why there are companies who specialize in identifying intrusive drones. Dedrone, a US-based company has developed a system that can detect drone activity in given airspace and employ Artificial Intelligence to determine if the incoming drone is hostile or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DroneShield has developed a multi-sensor system that can detect intrusive drones. A combination of radar, acoustic, and radio frequency sensors are used.  Camera and thermal sensors allow for visual confirmation upon which an alert is sent in the form of SMS and e-mail to the buildings security system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: What if drones start falling on people's heads due to bad maintenance, strong wind, malfunctions, empty batteries, etc.. What is the industry doing as a contingency?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Yes, the participants in the industry are working towards developing contingency measures for these safety-related scenarios. For Eg.  ParaZero, a start-up, has developed a safety solution called ‘SafeAir’. This system comprises an automatic pyrotechnic parachute system, which will launch a parachute within a fraction of second on sensing a malfunction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon has filed a patent application for an airbag system that will be inflated when the package is about to be dropped off for delivery. The airbag will cushion the impact when the package falls to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME: What is the fly-time range of most commercial drones?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Multicopter, electric drones presently have an approximate range between 8 km and 45 km and can be used for short-range deliveries. Winged hybrid propulsion models of drones achieve a range more than 100 km and could be used for intercity deliveries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AME:  What ground infrastructure is needed (battery refuelling for example) to allow for seamless operation of commercial drones? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANS: Ground infrastructure will be required to support charging which can increase the range of missions that a delivery drone can undertake. Several companies are developing innovative charging solutions. US-based Asylon has developed the ‘DroneHome’, which is a weatherproof rugged box. It is a charging box which houses 12 batteries. When a drone with a depleted battery lands on the box, a robotic arm automatically removes the depleted battery and loads a new battery on to the drone. The drone can continue with its mission, while the depleted battery is placed inside the DroneHome to charge.  Skysense, a Germany based company has developed a portable charging pad with conductive tiles on the surface on which drones can land and automatically charge their batteries. These devices can be installed along the routes with high drone traffic and can be used to increase the range of the drones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/travel/exclusive-the-fantastic-business-and-journey-of-drones-in-our-lives/"&gt;Exclusive: The fantastic business and journey of drones in our lives&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 08:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Cobots – How to live with them, work with them &amp; love them -  Puntaje: 4200</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/cobots-ai-future/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_687084607-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_687084607-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_687084607-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;(Words by Chris Pope, VP Innovation, ServiceNow)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The renaissance we are currently experiencing in Artificial Intelligence (AI), and all forms of Machine Learning (ML), has given rise to widespread discussion on how business will run in the immediate future. As the impact of AI starts to be applied to real-world use cases, we will inevitably need to get used to some new terminology. One of the technology industry’s new favourites is the notion of the ‘cobot’, short for collaborative-robot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cobots come in many forms. Some will be purely software-based helper robots that we might think of as sophisticated extensions of chatbots or virtual assistants. Some will more physically manifest themselves as robot arms, exoskeletons or some other form of intelligently programmed machinery. Some will be a super-smart mix of both.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Chris Pope, VP Innovation, ServiceNow)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your intelligent new office buddy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can think of cobots as your new office buddies and people—I do mean all of us―are going to have to get used to working alongside intelligent machines, in close proximity, very soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cobot brains are composed of software-based virtual services that form the synapses of ‘thought’—we know its processing and data analytics really―that they run on. Like a Tamagotchi, they do need feeding and watering, but only in the form of software updates, exposure to new datasets and patches for security provisioning and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who find the notion of cobots unnerving should perhaps stand back and consider the fact that machines have already been looking after us in close proximity for years. Your desktop machine, tablet and smartphone are all using AI to power the spam filter algorithms that assess every email you get for its potential threat value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it helps you warm up to the concept, think of cobots as just one step further than a spam filter. But instead of just protecting you from a potential virus, cobots will be able to intuitively manage your work schedule, actions and business decisions, to create a better employee experience all round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As DXC Technology’s Marc Wilkinson writes in Wired:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For businesses, the promise of AI is that [intelligent assistants] will be embedded across all aspects of the organization. Such agents will analyse data, discover patterns over time and then make decisions based on predictive analysis. The outcome? The application of AI on this level will make businesses not only more efficient, but also more profitable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behavioral responsibility&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As shiny and fabulous as all this sounds, there is a responsibility factor to bear in mind here. As we start to feed data into cobot brains, we need to be able to reflect a consciousness of and appreciation for society’s acceptable behavioral norms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means that cobots will need to be able to assess the risk factor in terms of the judgements they give to any individual worker based on that person’s skills, background and other competencies. To do this effectively, we will need to be able to assess and measure individual workers’ skills in an even more granular and mathematical way before we start to engineer more automation of this kind into our lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cobots will also need to appreciate cultural, ethical and behavioral norms for the global culture that they are applied in depending on location—and this is of course a subject in and of itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cobots and global digital workflows&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the cobots start to take over the mundane tasks in our world, we must consider how people will now coexist in the new world of automated controls that drive digital workflows and how we actually implement these devices―be they software-based, hardware-based or both—in the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some argue that we will now need to be able to measure an individual’s rank or score in terms of workplace competency. If we accept this methodology, then it could arguably help us find the engineering point at which we can apply cobot technology to an individual’s role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a cobot as your new office buddy, we can start to think about the workplace itself from a different perspective. We’re all used to open plan office seating layouts these days, but with cobots in the workplace, the software itself will be able to straddle cross-team functionality matrices that far outstrip the boundaries of the physical office itself. For example, team member actions in the UAE can be automatically reflected in plans for the UK or US offices in near real-time. The cobot doesn’t sleep, so a new global digital workflow starts to become possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A toast to cobot IPA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With cobot technology now developing fast, we will more clearly be able to understand our transition from RPA to IPA or IRPA. If Robotic Process Automation (RPA) allows us to program home heating controls, for example, based on defined patterns, then Intelligent Robotic Process Automation (IRPA, or just IPA) is one step further, where home heating controls start to program themselves for optimum usage and efficiency based upon observed patterns of use. Cobots have IRPA in their ‘DNA’ from the get-go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re on the cusp of many technologies―perceived today as almost ‘toy like’, such as self-driving cars—becoming quite natural. We will think that cobots and intelligent assistants are quite standard in half a decade’s time. In the same way that you went from reading a map in the car and now automatically turning the GPS on, you get to a point where you just expect a new technology to be there…and cobots will be there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/cobots-ai-future/"&gt;Cobots – How to live with them, work with them &amp;#038; love them&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: Mt Gox Crypto Boss Escapes Jail -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/mt-gox-crypto-boss-escapes-jail-1/</link><description>Karpeles given 2.5 year sentence, suspended for four years</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Post technology-business: Stanford helped pioneer artificial intelligence. Now the university wants to put humans at its center. -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/stanford-helped-pioneer-artificial-intelligence-now-the-university-wants-to-put-humans-at-its-center/2019/03/18/e7d241c3-869f-4b6d-9b63-014d7146d6c1_story.html</link><description>On Monday, the university will launch the Stanford Institute for Human-Centered Artificial Intelligence, a sprawling think tank that aims to become an interdisciplinary hub.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 07:00:53 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Colorado Lawmakers Seek Exploration of Blockchain Use in Agriculture -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/colorado-lawmakers-seek-exploration-of-blockchain-use-in-agriculture</link><description>Lawmakers in the U.S. state of Colorado are eyeing a role for blockchain technology in the agricultural industry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 14:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Bitcoin’s Price and Network Activity: One is Outpacing the Other -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/bitcoins-price-and-network-activity-one-is-outpacing-the-other</link><description>Active addresses on bitcoin's blockchain have increased 20 percent in recent weeks. So, why is the BTC price trading sideways?</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 06:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Sbanken chooses Nets to support open banking -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77689/sbanken-chooses-nets-to-support-open-banking?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Norwegian bank Sbanken has selected Nets to support open banking with Nets Access to Account Service...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: What can the Crypto industry jobs tell us about the future? -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16826/what-can-the-crypto-industry-jobs-tell-us-about-the-future?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The cryptocurrency industry is on the rise, and it is no longer just an industry dedicated to curren...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:37:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: US fintech to buy Worldpay as electronic payments business booms -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/us-fintech-to-buy-worldpay-as-electronic-payments-business-booms-11355734</link><description>U.S. fintech group Fidelity National Information Services Inc (FIS) has agreed to buy payment processor Worldpay for about US$35 billion, in the biggest deal to date in the booming payments industry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 22:10:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Finovate: FIS Acquires Worldpay -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://finovate.com/fis-acquires-worldpay/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Banking technology giant FIS is acquiring payments firm Worldpay via a cash and stock combination – bringing Worldpay’s enterprise value to approximately $43 billion (including the assumption of Worldpay debt, which FIS expects to refinance), reports Henry Vilar of Fintech Futures (Finovate&amp;#8217;s sister publication). According to Bloomberg, FIS is spending $34 billion on this purchase. “Scale &lt;a class="moretag" href="https://finovate.com/fis-acquires-worldpay/"&gt;Read more...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com/fis-acquires-worldpay/"&gt;FIS Acquires Worldpay&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://finovate.com"&gt;Finovate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 14:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Apple Pay and Google Pay now enabled on Worldline payment terminals in Germany -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77690/apple-pay-and-google-pay-now-enabled-on-worldline-payment-terminals-in-germany?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Worldline [Euronext: WLN], the European market leader for payment and transaction services, now supp...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Cyber espionage takes aim at automotive industry -  Puntaje: 3600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/transportation/cyber-espionage-takes-aim-at-automotive-industry/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_741201211-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_741201211-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_741201211-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;As vehicles become increasingly complex and more connected to the Internet, they are also becoming more vulnerable to cyber attacks. Not only are threat actors targeting connected cars, they are also conducting cyber espionage campaigns targeting manufacturers to gain competitive advantage. FireEye has seen multiple intrusions in the automotive industry in Europe over the past few years, mainly from Chinese attackers. Additional activity has been seen from North Korea and Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The threats FireEye is observing targeting the automotive industry include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyber espionage for competitive advantage: Cyber espionage remains a high threat to the industry, given its highly competitive nature and market pressure to deliver the latest technological and mechanical innovations. FireEye has most often observed malicious activity targeting the automotive industry for cyber espionage purposes linked to China, but also found activity from North Korean and suspected Vietnam-linked groups. These state-sponsored threat actors aim to steal information from automotive manufacturers such as proprietary research, development data, and intellectual property that could provide an economic or competitive advantage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyber espionage for military use: Nations also conduct cyber espionage campaigns against the automotive industry to obtain information on technological progress that can be appropriated for military applications. Stealing intellectual property from an automotive designer or manufacturer could provide nations with data regarding variety of technologies useful for militaries, including autonomous vehicle systems, artificial intelligence (AI)-related technologies, and sensor packages, without needing to conduct the often expensive and time-consuming research and development associated with these technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyber threats to manufacturers: FireEye has observed numerous exposed control systems from industrial environments and manufacturing plants in the automotive sector across Europe and globally. While these environments are targets for malicious cyber activity, smaller companies in supply chains have also been targeted, as they are often perceived as an easier target for cyber actors to compromise, then used to abuse trusted connections in the supply chain to access the main target’s networks. The compromise of a manufacturer, whether directly or through a trusted third-party, could allow a range of malicious activities, including theft of sensitive data, disruption of manufacturing processes, and compromise of vehicle-based computer systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyber criminals targeting connected vehicles: As more cars use keyless entry systems and electronic fobs to lock and unlock car doors, criminals have increasingly exploited vulnerabilities in these systems to gain unauthorised access to vehicles. Additionally, security researchers have conducted proof-of-concept (PoC) compromises against vehicles to illustrate how threat actors can exploit vulnerabilities in a car's systems—even if they are not in the target's immediate proximity. Manipulating cars on the road poses an immense physical danger to drivers, passengers, and those in the surrounding area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Risks to autonomous vehicles: As automotive companies begin to develop vehicles with more autonomous capabilities, researchers have found ways to disrupt vehicle sensors, allowing them to interfere with systems such as road sign recognition. While there is only a low likelihood that criminals will conduct this type of activity on a large scale due to the technical complexities involved, the automotive industry's race to develop autonomous vehicles will likely lead to an increase in cyber espionage activity. This activity could include cyber espionage actors stealing a competitor's artificial intelligence technologies from one organization to accelerate a competitor's driverless car research and development, disrupting a company's research operations, sabotaging development efforts, and other similar malicious activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ransomware campaigns on the automotive industry: FireEye has observed ransomware campaigns affecting the automotive industry across Europe, which can cause substantial data loss. This activity includes the WannaCry ransomware campaign, which disrupted the operations of many companies globally, including in the automotive industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“From the Internet of Things devices to connected cars, adversaries are increasingly capitalising on the heightened connectivity of today and using it unlawfully to gain a competitive or financial advantage. The danger to the automotive industry is particularly worrying due to the potential physical safety risk of a successful attack. To combat these threats, the sector must continually improve security measures and build strong, proactive defences into vehicles to protect against these malicious activities,” said Parnian Najafi Borazjani, Senior Threat Analyst at FireEye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/transportation/cyber-espionage-takes-aim-at-automotive-industry/"&gt;Cyber espionage takes aim at automotive industry&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: Tech-driven Oman making a case for a smart future -  Puntaje: 20000</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/oman-iot-tech-innovation-comex/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_792657445-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_792657445-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_792657445-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Dubai is working towards achieving Vision 2021. Saudi Arabia is attempting to bring Vision 2030 to life.&lt;br /&gt;
Meet Oman Vision 2040.&lt;br /&gt;
The Sultanate is firing on all gears, and technology will play a major role in turning the country into a “sustainable knowledge society”, as per the technology-focused Vision 2020 manifesto.&lt;br /&gt;
COMEX 2019 (March 17-19), Oman’s biggest technology show, is one step forward towards this goal.&lt;br /&gt;
Industry 4.0 takes centre stage&lt;br /&gt;
The exhibition's 2019 theme is “Tech Intelligence,” featuring a number of emerging technologies and new initiatives focusing on the Industry 4.0 technologies. Smart cities, blockchain, IoT, and AI are major talking points at this year’s event.&lt;br /&gt;
“Free tech talks, smart city conference with focus on Industry 4.0, e-lifestyle featuring cyberwar hackathon, Augmented Reality/Virtual Reality (AR/VR) zone, gaming area, cyber family awareness zone and smart home technology” are on offer this year, Xinhua news agency reported.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oman Vision 2040 is guiding an advanced technological infrastructure foundation to transform the economy, and society, and government, and enable all sectors, enterprise application software firm SAP said. As Oman’s organizations digitally transform, the Sultanate’s IT market will grow by 8% to $379.2 million by 2021, according to BMI Research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oman Vision 2040 and strong IT growth show that Oman’s leaders are leading the Sultanate in driving innovation to foster diversified economic growth and job creation in the Digital Economy,” said Waheed Al Hamaid, Managing Director, SAP Oman. “Oman can see the biggest benefit in moving from e-government to digitizing the whole-of-government, with cross-collaboration and AI predicting citizen needs in real-time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tech investments are a priority&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oman has been investing in all kinds of Industry 4.0 technologies.&lt;br /&gt;
For its 2019 budget, the Sultanate estimated that total projected spending will amount to $33.5 billion, an increase of 3% against the previous year budget, auditor firm KPMG noted.&lt;br /&gt;
Currently, 74% of the country’s revenue is derived from oil sales, the analyst company said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2016, Oman launched a $200 million investment fund dedicated to tech start-ups in the Middle East and across the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The Oman Investment Fund (OIF), a government-owned investment vehicle, established the Oman Technology Fund (OTF) with the long-term view of investing in the technology of the future,” Al Araby reported at the time.&lt;br /&gt;
The Information Technology Authority (ITA) has put increasing importance on AI, realizing its significance to the country’s future.&lt;br /&gt;
“Artificial intelligence (AI) technology is the backbone of the 4th industrial revolution, according to Dr. Salim bin Sultan Alruzaiqi, CEO of the ITA,” The Oman Times reported him saying last year.&lt;br /&gt;
"ITA also predicts that the savings from the implementation of four AI projects in eGovernment transformation will be equivalent to $46.7 million in four years,” he added.&lt;br /&gt;
Blockchain is also on the country’s mind&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last month, “Oman’s second largest bank by market value, BankDhofar, [began] using RippleNet technology for cross-border payments to India,” Coin Telegraph reported. RippleNet is a global blockchain-based payment network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlock, a blockchain news platform, reported the following this month: "BSS (Blockchain Solutions and Services LLC), Information Technology Authority (ITA) of Oman, and technology service provider Omantel jointly announced the deployment of the national HyperLedger Fabric Platforms to speed the digital innovation efforts in the Sultanate of Oman."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Hyperledger Fabric - a permission-based blockchain platform, developed by IBM under the umbrella of the Linux Foundation, holds 52% of all Enterprise Blockchain projects in production, according to a recent HFS research report," Unlock continued.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The country authorized the establishment of a Blockchain Club during the Blockchain Oman Symposium on November 2017, seeking to “inject momentum and awareness for the Omani society about Blockchain as a step for continued future digital transformation,” as per the Club’s official site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/it/oman-iot-tech-innovation-comex/"&gt;Tech-driven Oman making a case for a smart future&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>