<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 13:35:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>finextra: BME tests blockchain for collateral pledges -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33536/bme-tests-blockchain-for-collateral-pledges?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Spanish bourse BME has completed tests of the use of blockchain technology to eliminate the exchange...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 10:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Cosimo Ventures invests in blockchain and digital assets firms -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/cosimo-ventures-invests-in-blockchain-and-digital-assets-firms/</link><description>VC firm makes three investments in Gecko Governance, Lingar and Oneiro.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 09:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Spanish stock market operator BME tests blockchain for collateral pledge -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/spanish-stock-market-operator-bme-tests-blockchain-for-collateral-pledge/</link><description>BME and Renta 4 Banco have carried out their first digitisation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 15:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: CULedger brings DLT security to voice banking -  Puntaje: 1700</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33531/culedger-brings-dlt-security-to-voice-banking?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Credit union-owned blockchain outfit CULedger has teamed up with Best Innovation Group (BIG) and Con...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: SWIFT Signals Further Openness To Blockchain? -  Puntaje: 6000</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2019/swift-blockchain-dlt-cross-border-banking/</link><description>The movement to bring blockchain to cross-border payments proceeds apace. Might SWIFT be giving a nod, at least partially, toward the use of distributed ledger technology (DLT)? As noted by OracleTimes, it seems the messaging network that ties banks and other financial firms together may indeed be open to DLT — if not directly, then […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: Elasticsearch Crypto-Miner Sinkholes the Competition -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/elasticsearch-cryptominer-1/</link><description>F5 reveals sophisticated "CryptoSink" campaign which kills rival miners</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 10:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Threatpost: GlitchPOS Malware Appears to Steal Credit-Card Numbers -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://threatpost.com/glitchpos-malware-credit-card/142804/</link><description>A new malware targeting point of sale systems, GlitchPOS, has been spotted on a crimeware forum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 15:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: Thai government says cybersecurity bill not used to 'tap' phones -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/thai-government-says-cybersecurity-bill-not-used-to-tap-phones-11345048</link><description>Thailand's prime minister batted away criticism of a controversial cybersecurity law on Thursday, saying it would not be used to "tap phone calls".</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 21:38:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BankNews.com: Need a Way to Educate Your Customers About Phishing? -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.banknews.com/blog/need-a-way-to-educate-your-customers-about-phishing/</link><description>If you&amp;#8217;re looking for a way to educate your customers about Phishing attacks, the American Bankers Association Foundation, in collaboration with the Federal Trade Commission, has released an infographic aimed at consumers. According to the FBI&amp;#8217;s Internet Crime Report, victims lost nearly $30 million due to phishing scams 2017 compared to only $8 million two [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Barclaycard opens up  to Alipay -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33534/barclaycard-opens-up--to-alipay?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Barclaycard, which processes nearly half of the UK’s credit and debit card transactions, has extende...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 09:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Barclaycard brings Alipay payments to UK retailers -  Puntaje: 700</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/barclaycard-brings-alipay-payments-to-uk-retailers/</link><description>To cater to the many Chinese Alipay users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 11:02:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: ICO Raids Nuisance Call Firms -  Puntaje: 100</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/ico-raids-nuisance-call-firms-1/</link><description>Privacy watchdog sends message to dodgy directors</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Crunch: AI photo startup Polarr raises an $11.5 million Series A -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/LAnR1wnJ8wg/</link><description>Bay Area photography startup Polarr announced this morning that it has raised an $11.5 million Series A. The new round of funding, led by Threshold Ventures with participation from Pear Ventures and Cota Capital, brings the startup’s total funding to around $12.5 million, according to the latest Crunchbase figures. At the moment, the company is [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Business: Feeding the machine: Optus partners with AI startup Metigy -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/small-business/feeding-the-machine-optus-partners-with-ai-startup-metigy-20190313-p513qg.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_business</link><description>The social media game is fast becoming about tracking competition using algorithms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 09:32:16 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>Channel News Asia business: China is overtaking US in artificial intelligence: Researchers -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/china-is-overtaking-us-in-artificial-intelligence-researchers-11341770</link><description>WASHINGTON: China is poised to overtake the United States in artificial intelligence with a surge in academic research on the key technology, an analysis published on Wednesday (Mar 13) showed.

The analysis by the Allen Institute for Artificial Intelligence showed China has already surpassed the ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 03:23:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: Naspers Said to Eye Fintech Deals in $1 Billion India Push -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/03/naspers-said-to-eye-fintech-deals-in-1-billion-india-push/</link><description>Naspers Ltd. wants to spend about $1 billion in India this year as it scours the globe for investments that can replicate its blockbuster bet on China’s Tencent Holdings Ltd., a person familiar with the matter said. Africa’s largest company by market value is in talks to inject about $200 million into business loan provider [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: DIFC AUM equal to 30% of combined GCC GDP -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/difc-aum-equal-to-30-of-combined-gcc-gdp/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/DIFC-1-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/DIFC-1-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/DIFC-1-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;The landmark agreements signed by the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC) during its recent Global Financial Forum have the potential to transform Dubai into one of the world’s top financial hubs, according to global accountancy and finance body ICAEW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The forum was held on 11 March and organised by DIFC in partnership with the Financial Times. Key announcements included: DIFC’s rise from 15th to 12th position on the latest Global Financial Centres Index; MEVP (Middle East Venture Capital) and Wamda Capital appointed to manage part of $100 million FinTech fund; and FinTech Hive signing knowledge-sharing memoranda of understanding with three new global Fintech accelerators. DIFC has been bolstered further by its growing wealth and asset management sector valued at around $424 billion, equivalent to roughly 30% of the combined GDP of all GCC countries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on growth of DIFC and its forthcoming initiatives, Michael Armstrong FCA and ICAEW Regional Director for Middle East, Africa and South Asia said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“DIFC’s rise in the latest Global Financial Centres Index highlights the strong momentum in Dubai’s financial services landscape. Improvements in governance standards combined with the progressive forward thinking of the leadership team underscore the government’s willingness to embrace disruptive technology and thrive in this fast-paced, changing world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The launch of a $100m fintech fund and the announcement of FinTech Hive’s MoUs with FinTech Saudi, Milan’s FinTech District and FinTech Istanbul—which bring its growing global network to 14 fintech hubs—is proof of Dubai’s commitment to the future of finance. In today’s globalised world, such collaboration and knowledge sharing is crucial to optimise innovation and generate exciting business opportunities for the region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The financial services sector is highly competitive, innovative and fast-moving, playing vitally important roles in encouraging economic development and investment. The need to incentivise and attract capital, talent and customers in highly competitive markets calls for commercial flair and focus. If regulations are kept up to date, which has been the case, by working together to build confidence and trust, Dubai’s financial services sector has great potential to continue to attract investment and significantly contribute to the region’s economy. Dubai also has the potential to realise its ambition to become among the world’s top financial hubs.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/money/banking-finance/difc-aum-equal-to-30-of-combined-gcc-gdp/"&gt;DIFC AUM equal to 30% of combined GCC GDP&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 11:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Deutsche Bourse FinTech Hub enters the second round -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77665/deutsche-bourse-fintech-hub-enters-the-second-round?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Deutsche Börse is further developing its FinTech Hub: in cooperation with TechQuartier, it is now br...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortune: Fintech Startup Tally Debuts What It Claims Is the World’s ‘Only Free Automated Savings Service’ -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://fortune.com/2019/03/14/fintech-startup-tally-no-fee-savings-account/</link><description>CEO Jason Brown says the company will lose money on each customer, but "not so much that we're ever going to need to charge for it."</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>American Banker: Fintechs look to Mexico for growth; Amex’s next hurdle -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>http://www.americanbanker.com/morning-scan/fintechs-look-to-mexico-for-growth-amexs-next-hurdle</link><description>Fintech investors, including Goldman Sachs, see opportunity in Mexico; firm’s growth in lending could be a problem if economy goes south.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BusinessLine Money &amp; Banking: ‘Report of committee on fintech related issues will be out soon’ -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/money-and-banking/report-of-committee-on-fintech-related-issues-will-be-out-soon/article26535828.ece</link><description>The report of the  committee on fintech related issues is likely to be made public soon, Finance Secretary Subhash Chandra Garg said on Thursday.“The</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 20:41:38 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: DMSniff POS Malware has flown under the radar for at least four years -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82358/uncategorized/dmsniff-pos-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Malware researchers at Flashpoint revealed that at least since 2016, a PoS malware dubbed DMSniff has flown under the radar. Malware researchers at Flashpoint revealed that since 2016, a PoS malware dubbed DMSniff has been involved in breaches of small- and medium-sized businesses in the restaurant and entertainment industries. DMSniff leverages a domain generation algorithm [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82358/uncategorized/dmsniff-pos-malware.html"&gt;DMSniff POS Malware has flown under the radar for at least four years&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 08:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Naspers eyes $1 bn fintech deals in India; seeks to replicate China success -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/international/naspers-eyes-1-bn-fintech-deals-in-india-seeks-to-replicate-china-success-119031400647_1.html</link><description>Africa's largest company by market value is in talks to inject about $200 million into business loan provider Capital Float and payments security firm Wimbo as a first step</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 15:52:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>AMEinfo: The UAE has become the #1 destination for FDI in AI -  Puntaje: 6600</title><link>https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/uae-fdi-ai/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1119927341-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1119927341-150x150.jpg 150w, https://ameinfo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/shutterstock_1119927341-200x200.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Dubai ranked first globally in attracting foreign direct investments (FDIs) for artificial intelligence and robotics; while the UAE ranked sixth in the global Smart Service Index, surpassing the US, UK and South Korea, in a press release published by Khaleej Times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the press release, the Emirate has attracted from 2015 to 2018 $21.6 billion worth of FDI in high-end technology transfers, with the most from the European Union and the US - $5.7 billion and $3.9 billion, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These figures were released in connection with Annual Investment Meeting (AIM 2019), which will be held from April 8-10 in Dubai. The organisers of AIM said that digitalisation is becoming an increasingly important part of globalisation, and the fact that Dubai ranks on the top position for artificial intelligence and robotics confirms that the city is fast emerging as the global destination for investment in smart technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While AI adoption will account for 45 per cent of the world economy's total gains by 2030, the UAE ranks first in the Arab world in terms of expected annual growth of AI contribution to the economy at 33.5 per cent, followed by Saudi Arabia at 31.3 per cent, the rest of the GCC region at 28.8 per cent and Egypt at 25.5 per cent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Digital growth is significant to the growth of the economy. In the UAE, it is in line with UAE Vision 2021, which aims to position the country as a top spot for tech investments," said Dawood Al Shezawi, CEO of Annual Investment Organising Committee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Annual Investment Meeting is the world's leading platform for FDI, aimed at facilitating strategic networking and promoting investments. Power-packed with international investment community, this exalted gathering witnesses high-ranking policy makers, business leaders, regional and international investors, successful entrepreneurs, leading academics and celebrated financial experts showcasing up-to-date information and strategies on attracting FDI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Disruptive technologies like AI, blockchain, internet of things (IoT) boost the productive capacity of countries and also the global GDP. To maximise its benefits, countries need to integrate new avenues that will drive more investments in these solutions," added Shezawi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the upcoming Annual Investment Meeting (AIM), experts will highlight strategies and mechanisms for enhancing tech solutions to draw FDIs, in addition to highlighting internal and external incentives that encourage companies to adopt these solutions. The three-day exhibition will also offer opportunities for governments and private organisations to launch and promote their projects to a vastly diverse audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com/technology/innovation/uae-fdi-ai/"&gt;The UAE has become the #1 destination for FDI in AI&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://ameinfo.com"&gt;AMEInfo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 08:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>