<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Noticias FinTech</title><link>https://github.com/unknomads/Recopilador-de-Noticias</link><description>Noticias FinTech recopiladas durante el día.</description><copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Banco Central de Chile. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:09:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyMediaRSS2Gen 0.0.1</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CoinDesk: Decentralized or Nothing: Song Duels IBM Over Blockchain Hype at SXSW -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/decentralized-or-nothing-song-slams-ibm-over-blockchain-hype-at-sxsw</link><description>An event at SXSW pitted Blockchain Capital's Jimmy Song against IBM's Chris Ferris in a debate over permissioned vs. permissionless blockchains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: TradeIX to hire 70 more staff for Dublin HQ -  Puntaje: 800</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33540/tradeix-to-hire-70-more-staff-for-dublin-hq?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Trade finance blockchain network TradeIX is to hire 70 more staff at its Dublin HQ, in a variety of...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: French NCC Deploy IBM Blockchain For Commercial and Corporate Registries -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/15/french-ncc-deploy-ibm-blockchain-for-commercial-and-corporate-registries/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Fintech-IBM-Blockchain-1440x564_c-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" data-attachment-id="28887" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2018/05/16/deloitte-survey-numbers-demonstrate-executive-faith-in-blockchain/fintech-ibm-blockchain-1440x564_c/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Fintech-IBM-Blockchain-1440x564_c.jpg" data-orig-size="1440,564" data-comments-opened="1" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="Deloitte Survey Exhibits Executive Faith In Blockchain By The Numbers" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Fintech-IBM-Blockchain-1440x564_c-300x118.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/Fintech-IBM-Blockchain-1440x564_c-1024x401.jpg" /&gt;IBM and the French National Council of Clerks (NCC) have teamed up to kick off development of blockchain-based commercial court solution devoted to the clerks of commercial courts’ commercial and corporate registry.  “This project, which is the result of an autonomous initiative between clerks of commercial courts and IBM, is the continuation of our efforts [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/15/french-ncc-deploy-ibm-blockchain-for-commercial-and-corporate-registries/"&gt;French NCC Deploy IBM Blockchain For Commercial and Corporate Registries&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/richard-kastelein/"&gt;Richard Kastelein&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: New Research Argues That ICOs Aren’t as Scammy as Implied. Here’s the Problem, Though. -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29526/blockchain/ico-scam-research-debunk-failure/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In a presentation shared with the attendees of the International Scientific Conference (#ISC2019) organized by The British Blockchain Association in London, researchers Daniel Liebau and Patrick Schueffel revealed a summary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29526/blockchain/ico-scam-research-debunk-failure/"&gt;New Research Argues That ICOs Aren&amp;#8217;t as Scammy as Implied. Here&amp;#8217;s the Problem, Though.&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 07:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>daily fintech: FCA pioneers digitising regulatory reporting using DLT and NLP -  Puntaje: 2500</title><link>https://dailyfintech.com/2019/03/15/fca-pioneers-digitising-regulatory-reporting-using-dlt-and-nlp/</link><description>Too many TLAs (Three Letter Acronyms), I agree. Earlier this week the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) published the results of a pilot programme called Digital Regulatory Reporting. It was an exploratory effort to understand the feasibility of using Distributed Ledger Technology (DLT) and Natural Language Processing (NLP) to automate regulatory reporting at scale. Let me [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Crypto Exchange Bittrex Cancels Its First ‘Initial Exchange Offering’ -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exchange-bittrex-cancels-its-first-initial-exchange-offering</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy81ZTcxY2E3YTMyOGE5Yzc1MDYzNTUxYzUyMThiNzRlYy5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto exchange Bittrex has cancelled its first token sale, dubbed an Initial Exchange Offering, which it had planned to host on its Malta-based platform&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Consensus Algorithm Tendermint Raises $9 Mln in Series A Investment Round -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/consensus-algorithm-tendermint-raises-9-mln-in-series-a-investment-round</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy83NTcwMzU3MzhmM2UxYzQ5MzZiMjRjNzEzY2VhM2E2Mi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tendermint has raised $9 million in a Series A investment round led by cryptocurrency investment company Paradigm&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Japan: Hacker Involved in 15 Mln Yen Crypto Theft Referred to Prosecutors -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/japan-hacker-involved-in-15-mln-yen-crypto-theft-referred-to-prosecutors</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy9lYzdjZjU3OThkNWU3MGYxMzRiNDE3MWUxYWJiYzlkNi5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The alleged Monappy crypto wallet hacker has been referred to prosecutors in the Japanese city of Utsunomiya&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 01:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Yacht Owners Offered Crypto for Geo-Data as Company Tries to Improve Navigation Systems -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/yacht-owners-offered-crypto-for-geo-data-as-company-tries-to-improve-navigation-systems</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy8xZDZiN2RjZTg0YzllNzlhYWVjMTRlMzEwYWVmYjM5OC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A marine navigation company is aiming to create an accurate database of geo-data by enabling yachtsmen to mine cryptocurrency as they sail #SPONSORED&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Gatecoin Crypto Exchange to Shut Down on Court’s Orders -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/gatecoin-crypto-exchange-to-shut-down-on-courts-orders</link><description>Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange Gatecoin will shut down and enter liquidation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Japan to Hold First Ever Trial Over Crypto Hacking Losses -  Puntaje: 1300</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/japan-to-hold-first-ever-trial-over-crypto-hacking-losses</link><description>An 18-year-old Japanese youth has been sent to prosecutors in the country's first ever trial involving cryptocurrency cyber-theft.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 14:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Canadian regulators consult on framework for crypto-asset trading platforms -  Puntaje: 2200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77674/canadian-regulators-consult-on-framework-for-crypto-asset-trading-platforms?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) and Investment Industry Regulatory Organization of Cana...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sydney Morning Herald Business: What crash? The hottest crypto on the market has tripled in value -  Puntaje: 3900</title><link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/markets/what-crash-this-crypto-has-tripled-in-value-in-three-months-20190315-p514it.html?ref=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=rss_business</link><description>The cryptocurrency boom appears to be alive and well for Binance, the world's largest digital-asset exchange by trading volume.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:41:37 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark Reading : Proof-of-Concept Tracking System Finds RATs Worldwide -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/proof-of-concept-tracking-system-finds-rats-worldwide/d/d-id/1334175?_mc=rss_x_drr_edt_aud_dr_x_x-rss-simple</link><description>Using a combination of Shodan scans and data from partners, Recorded Future finds nearly 500 malware controllers for 14 different families of remote-access Trojans, as well as the corporate networks they have infected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:00:00 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosecurity Magazine: DMSniff POS Malware Uses DGA to Stay Active -  Puntaje: 300</title><link>https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com:443/news/dmsniff-pos-malware-uses-dga-to-1/</link><description>Flashpoint said malware has been running for years</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Affairs: GlitchPOS PoS Malware appears in the cybercrime underground -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82412/malware/glitchpos-pos-malware.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A new piece of PoS malware appeared in the threat landscape, the malicious code dubbed GlitchPOS has been found on a crimeware forum. The GlitchPOS malware is able to steal credit card numbers (Track1 and Track2) from the memory of the infected system, it uses a regular expression to perform this task. The malicious code [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress/82412/malware/glitchpos-pos-malware.html"&gt;GlitchPOS PoS Malware appears in the cybercrime underground&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://securityaffairs.co/wordpress"&gt;Security Affairs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 07:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>We Live Security: Week in security with Tony Anscombe -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/eset/blog/~3/IHqR0jP1rEY/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Asian game developers again targeted in supply-chain attacks distributing malware. Facebook suffer most severe outage ever. Plus, over 2 billion records exposed by email marketing firm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.welivesecurity.com/videos/week-in-security-with-tony-anscombe-12/"&gt;Week in security with Tony Anscombe&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="/" rel="nofollow"&gt;WeLiveSecurity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/eset/blog/~4/IHqR0jP1rEY" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: The platform ecology model: A deep dive -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33539/the-platform-ecology-model-a-deep-dive?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Eating the dust of Barclaycard’s partnership with Alipay, Finextra reports on the dominance of Ant F...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: IBM Hints at Stablecoin Cross-Border Payments Solution for Financial Institutions -  Puntaje: 1200</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ibm-hints-at-stablecoin-cross-border-payments-solution-for-financial-institutions</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy85NGRiZTE3OWRhYTM5NTViZWIwYWMyYjM1OGEwODFiZS5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;IBM’s Jesse Lund has hinted that bank-targeted stablecoins will be a major development for the tech giant’s blockchain cross-border payments solution&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Esma issues favourable report on RegTech developments -  Puntaje: 500</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/77679/esma-issues-favourable-report-on-regtech-developments?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>The European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA) has carried out an analysis of the regulatory a...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banking Technology: Top fintech stories this week – 15 March 2019 -  Puntaje: 200</title><link>https://www.bankingtech.com/2019/03/top-fintech-stories-this-week-15-march-2019/</link><description>Catch up on FinTech Futures' top five fintech stories of the week - all in one place!</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 01:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: AR and VR in Fintech: Benefits and Pitfalls -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/16814/ar-and-vr-in-fintech-benefits-and-pitfalls?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Are you using VR or AR in banking? Not yet? Looks like you are not trendy! Virtual reality is commo....</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Standard latest: Fintech sector can't deliver if data is kept personal: Finance Secy Garg -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/economy-policy/fintech-sector-can-t-deliver-if-data-is-kept-personal-finance-secy-garg-119031500604_1.html</link><description>He said Supreme Court's Aadhar judgement was a setback for the fintech industry, and that Aadhar offered an advantage to the industry, but taking it away may not help the sector</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 16:02:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: 9 Startups Inducted Into Inaugural Apollo Munich InspireNext Program -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://gomedici.com/9-startups-inducted-into-inaugural-apollo-munich-inspirenext-program/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/9-startups-inducted-into-inaugural-apollo-munich-inspirenext-program.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;Apollo Munich Health Insurance, a leading health insurance company, has always endeavored to be at the forefront of technology innovation. In alignment with its focus on leveraging cutting-edge technology to deliver world-class banking services to its clients, the company launched its first accelerator program called ‘InspireNext’ on March 12, 2019, at its corporate headquarters in Gurugram, NCR. InspireNext was created by Apollo Munich with a view to support and collaborate with entrepreneurs who are driving innovation in the FinTech/InsurTech ecosystem and to leverage their expertise for co-creating solutions that can benefit the company’s consumer base. The InspireNext program, in its inaugural year, intends to work on areas such as Customer Onboarding, Augmenting Customer Engagement, Claims Management, New-Age Risk Management Solutions, Operational Efficiencies, and HR Tech. This 15-week program will comprise of 5 weeks of on-site interactions and 10 weeks of off-site collaboration, where startups can work from their base locations,...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 18:12:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>FinTech Singapore: Fintech Set to Enter a New Phase in the Philippines -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>http://fintechnews.sg/29514/philippines/fintech-philippines-overview-2019/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Strong fundamentals, a supportive regulator and a comprehensive cell phone coverage, are some of favorable attributes of the Philippine market set to drive the digital transformation of the country’s financial&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg/29514/philippines/fintech-philippines-overview-2019/"&gt;Fintech Set to Enter a New Phase in the Philippines&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://fintechnews.sg"&gt;Fintech Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 07:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>pymnts: FinTech Pressures FI Giants To Strengthen SMB Lending In Mexico -  Puntaje: 1000</title><link>https://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2019/mexico-fintech-startup-funding/</link><description>Some of the largest global financial institutions are taking steps further into Mexico’s small business lending and finance space, the result of heightened competitive pressure imposed by FinTechs and alternative lenders in the market, reports in the Wall Street Journal said Thursday (March 14). The publication pointed to Goldman Sachs as the latest FI giant […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BBC business: AI and spices: Would you put cumin on a pizza? -  Puntaje: 250.0</title><link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-47403689</link><description>How AI is helping to come up with new weird and wonderful spice combinations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>finextra: Danske Bank joins Lighthouse fintech engagement programme -  Puntaje: 400</title><link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/33541/danske-bank-joins-lighthouse-fintech-engagement-programme?utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_source=finextrafeed</link><description>Denmark's Danske Bank is partnering with Mastercard and NFT Ventures on Nordic fintech engagement pr...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New York Times Business: Bits: The Week in Tech: How Much Regulation Is Too Much? -  Puntaje: 500.0</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/15/technology/tech-regulation-antitrust.html?partner=rss&amp;emc=rss</link><description>A screen demonstrating facial recognition using artificial intelligence at the CES tech conference in Las Vegas this year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Innovation: Fears of a Fintech Slowdown? How to Pivot Your Brand for a New Era -  Puntaje: 600</title><link>https://bankinnovation.net/2019/03/fears-of-a-fintech-slowdown-how-to-pivot-your-brand-for-a-new-era/</link><description>For most of the past decade, the fintech sector seemed to have nothing but blue skies ahead. But over the last 12 months, warnings that first signaled in 2016 have been flashing brighter. CEO scandals, pulled IPOs and sinking stock prices, have taken the luster off previously high-flying brands. Big banks have finally woken up [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 13:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDesk: Canada Proposes Regulatory Framework for Cryptocurrency Exchanges -  Puntaje: 900</title><link>https://www.coindesk.com/canada-proposes-regulatory-framework-for-cryptocurrency-exchanges</link><description>Canadian financial regulatory authorities have called for public comment on rules for cryptocurrency exchanges in the country.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>gomedici: When a Dragon Births Unicorns – 5 In 2018 -  Puntaje: 1600</title><link>https://gomedici.com/when-dragon-births-unicorns-5-in-2018/</link><description>&lt;img height="200px" width="600px" hspace="5" src="https://gomedici.com/uploads/when-dragon-births-unicorns-5-in-2018.jpg"/&gt;
                &lt;br&gt;China has always had a solid reputation for high-speed manufacturing, but when it comes to highly-valued ventures, the country may just have outdone itself last year. Consider this: in 2018, in spite of an extended trade war with the US and in the face of an economic slowdown, 25 private Chinese companies were valued at a total of $58.05 billion. In 2018’s H1, China’s FinTech companies raised ~$35 billion (over 80% of the global total) and three giants took more than half of the amount fundraised in China. Which giants? Ant Financial, Du Xiaoman Financial, and the new one on the block, JD Finance, raised ~$17.8 billion, accounting for more than half the total amount of funding in China for the year. A lot has been said about China’s growing tech unicorn culture. Some contend that such growth is inevitable, considering the overwhelmingly massive number of mobile and internet users...&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 09:01:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Blockchain News: DX Exchange and Perlin Network Bring Tokenized Apple and Facebook Stocks to Empower a vast new Population of Retail Investors on the Blockchain -  Puntaje: 2000</title><link>https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/15/dx-exchange-and-perlin-network-bring-tokenized-apple-and-facebook-stocks-to-empower-a-vast-new-population-of-retail-investors-on-the-blockchain/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="150" height="150" src="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/download-150x150.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/download-150x150.jpg 150w, https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/download.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" data-attachment-id="32222" data-permalink="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/15/dx-exchange-and-perlin-network-bring-tokenized-apple-and-facebook-stocks-to-empower-a-vast-new-population-of-retail-investors-on-the-blockchain/download-24/" data-orig-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/download.jpg" data-orig-size="225,225" data-comments-opened="0" data-image-meta="{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}" data-image-title="download" data-image-description="" data-medium-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/download.jpg" data-large-file="https://www.the-blockchain.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/download.jpg" /&gt;  Perlin Network and DX Exchange have announced a partnership making it easy for a whole new community of retail investors to enter both the traditional securities and cryptocurrency markets by enabling the trade of major stocks in digitized form on the Blockchain.  DX Exchange is the world’s first platform that allows investors to own and trade [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/2019/03/15/dx-exchange-and-perlin-network-bring-tokenized-apple-and-facebook-stocks-to-empower-a-vast-new-population-of-retail-investors-on-the-blockchain/"&gt;DX Exchange and Perlin Network Bring Tokenized Apple and Facebook Stocks to Empower a vast new Population of Retail Investors on the Blockchain&lt;/a&gt; written by &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com/author/wieke/"&gt;Wieke Beenen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.the-blockchain.com"&gt;Blockchain News - Security and Utility Tokens, Tokenomics, Cryptoeconomics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cointelegraph: Google Deletes Crypto Malware Targeting Blockchain.com, MyEtherWallet Users -  Puntaje: 2600</title><link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/google-deletes-crypto-malware-targeting-blockchaincom-myetherwallet-users</link><description>&lt;img src="https://images.cointelegraph.com/images/528_aHR0cHM6Ly9zMy5jb2ludGVsZWdyYXBoLmNvbS9zdG9yYWdlL3VwbG9hZHMvdmlldy80ZGZiZGQwZGRlYzAzOGYzYzA1ZjdhNDkxNGUxYTU1ZC5qcGc=.jpg"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latest security mishap sees Google accidently host hacking extension&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>